[♪ "Carte Postale" playing]
-Good morning, Mr. Gabe.
-Good morning.
[music stops]
[Eugenia screams]
[♪ "TELL 'EM YOU'RE MINE" playing]
♪ I came out last night ♪
-[phone buzzing]
-♪ I saw the light shining on you ♪
♪ Don't pretend that I didn't see you ♪
-Good morning, Morgan.
-Good morning.
Uh, hey, my car's on the fritz again.
Do you mind
if I grab a ride to work with you?
I'd love to,
but I'm on the other side of town.
No, you're not. You're at your apartment.
You're in the hallway, aren't you, Morgan?
-Hi.
Ludo's driving the kids to school,
and you are on the way,
-so I just had him drop me off.
-Mmm.
Hope that's okay. Can I come in?
No, no, no.
-What do you got going on in there?
-Nothing. I'm just getting ready.
And lying about where you are.
[gasps]
Is that Lucia?
Well, well, well, well, well.
-Morgan, can we not do this?
-Do what?
Okay, all right, you win.
Let me just say hi real quick.
I will give you a ride to work
if you wait out here in the hallway
until I'm finished getting ready,
otherwise start walking.
-Are you serious?
-Mm-hmm.
Fine.
Oh. I actually grabbed those
for the two of us, but that's fine.
-You can ask three questions.
-Why only three?
-Is that your first question?
-Sto-- Don't do that.
I knew you were gonna do that.
No, okay, fine.
Is that the first time she slept over?
-No. Mm-mmm.
-No?
Okay. Um…
I mean, how does it feel, you know,
is it comfortable? Is it kind of strange?
That's obviously all one question.
Honestly, both.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
It's weird how comfortable it is.
-Huh.
-Yeah.
Are you happy?
Yes. Yeah.
Good. You deserve to be happy.
So when are we all hanging out? You want
me to invite you guys over for dinner?
We can see how she is with kids.
Mmm. Yeah, the question and answer
portion of our morning has ended.
You know, I'm friends with a lot of people
-in the LAPD.
-[phone buzzing]
I can very easily bypass you
and get her number myself.
[Karadec] Okay.
Soto's sending us to a crime scene
in Crestwood Hills.
Oh. Whew. Rush hour.
Well, know what that means.
We got a lot more time to chitchat.
Yay.
Wow.
It's like a hobbit built a spaceship.
Victim's name is Gabe Rafferty.
Fifty-five. Housekeeper found him.
ME says he's been dead
since sometime last night.
This guy was 55?
Wow. Whatever he was doing, sign me up.
Besides the stabbing.
It's an odd choice of murder weapon.
Could be symbolic.
Or convenient.
They're called phurbas.
They are Tibetan symbols of health
and protection against evil.
-Didn't work.
-Yeah.
Someone found a different way to use it.
-Looks like he was into samadhi.
-What's that?
-Deep meditation.
-[Karadec] Mmm.
Went through a yoga thing once.
Oh. How'd that go?
[humming chant]
Okay.
-I won.
-You don't win yoga, Morgan.
-Not with that attitude, you don't.
-[sighs]
No defensive wounds on the body.
No forced entry.
Housekeeper said the alarm
was still set when she got here.
I'd wonder if the killer laid in wait,
but if this was premeditated,
they'd have brought a weapon.
And if it was a crime of passion,
there would be signs of a fight,
so neither one really makes sense.
-The victim's phone.
-Thank you.
Someone named Renata Carlino
really wanted to get in touch with him.
Thirty-five missed calls today.
-I need to see him!
-You can't go there.
-Oh. Oh, no.
-Come on.
Let me guess. Renata?
I've been Gabe's assistant
for eight years.
So, you have access to the house 24/7?
Yes, anyone who works here has a unique
passcode they enter when they come and go.
And is the system gonna say
that you were here last night?
I've been out of town since Monday.
On Catalina Island
for my sister's wedding.
I didn't have any service until
the ferry got back to LA this morning,
and as soon as it did,
I checked Gabe's biodata,
and that's when I saw he didn't have any.
-You checked his biodata?
-Through the GeneGevity app.
That's Gabe's company.
You can share vitals
with other users in your circle.
I checked Gabe's every morning.
Seems very intimate
for an employer-employee relationship.
[exhales] Well, we were so much more.
Not-- Not like that.
When I met Gabe, I was struggling.
I-- I'd just lost my mom
and all my master's degree ever did
for me was land me in a ton of debt.
-What'd you get your degree in?
-19th-century art and textiles.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Well, everything changed
after I went to one of Gabe's seminars.
He was so charismatic and alive.
His mission inspired me
to stop feeling sorry for myself
and make the most of my life,
and I've been working for him ever since.
What exactly was his mission?
Life extension.
GeneGevity is a pioneer in gene hacking.
Gabe believed that with the right diet,
exercise and self-care,
we could bypass the bad genes
and amp the good ones
to slow down the aging process
until eventually it stops altogether.
Gabe made himself the living proof.
He was showing the world that it worked.
In other words, the guy who was
trying to live forever just got murdered.
I wasn't just given the name
Healthiest Man on Earth.
I earned it.
Here at GeneGevity, we strive to create
ethical science-backed practices
tailored to you and your individual needs.
We believe you have
a long life ahead of you.
Live it well.
No, no. This is the kind of thing
that drives me nuts.
We're all supposed to think
that we can live like this guy.
He's got a sauna and a staff.
Give me Gabe's time and money,
and I'll live it well too.
Says the woman with Fun Dip in her purse.
"Biohack Your Workouts."
"Your Refrigerator
is Your Medicine Cabinet."
"The One Gut Worm
Everyone is Talking About."
Oh. Click on that one.
You know, I did a GeneGevity juice cleanse
once and I felt great after.
I even considered
signing up for the program,
but I was not comfortable
sending in bio samples.
-What's a bio sample?
-It comes off of you or out of you.
GeneGevity wants you to pop it
in the mail and send it on in.
-Moving on.
-You don't want to talk about poop?
Nope, enemies.
Other than the postal service,
I'm assuming,
who else might have had
an issue with old Gabe?
Pharmaceutical CEOs and doctors
all spoke out against GeneGevity,
but GeneGevity has done
a lot of good for a lot of people.
That's why his users are all fanatical.
Actually,
not all of Gabe's customers were fans.
I did a public record search.
In the last few months,
GeneGevity and Gabe were being sued
by a woman named Siobhan McBreyer.
-What did she sue them for? Huh.
-Child support.
We haven't seen anything
about Gabe having a child.
If he was keeping the child a secret
and McBreyer's lawsuits
weren't getting her anywhere,
-she may have been mad enough to kill.
-[Morgan] Mmm.
A secret love child and revenge murder.
It's like a telenovela.
Invite her in for a chat.
Oz is taking a day off, right?
You mind going through Gabe's videos solo?
Let's see if there's
any other secrets he's hiding.
You got it.
You wanna check out
this gut worm video first?
Ugh.
Excuse me. We're having a memorial
for my father here in a few days,
but his headstone
still hasn't been installed.
I'm sorry about that.
Are you sure it was ordered?
Yeah, my mother said
she ordered it months ago.
We install the monuments
the day we receive them.
You might want to check on that order.
Thanks.
Assistant's alibi checks out.
Spoke to multiple guests who saw
Renata at her sister's wedding.
Oh.
Siobhan McBreyer's here.
And she's off our suspect list.
-We don't know that.
-We don't?
She's about a thousand months pregnant,
and you think she got the jump
on the healthiest man alive?
Yeah, no.
Ms. McBreyer, thanks for coming in.
I'm Detective Karadec.
This is our consultant, Morgan Gillory.
We understand you are suing Gabe Rafferty?
Did he sic you on me?
Because I am within my rights to mail him
as many notices as I want
until he responds.
Well, that's not why we brought you in.
Mr. Rafferty's dead.
Oh.
Oh. [breathes heavily]
Of course he's dead.
It's great, it's great.
What happened to him? Hmm? Was it painful?
Please tell me it was painful.
Uh, it looked like
it was probably painful. Yeah.
You don't seem very upset for someone who
just lost the father of her unborn child.
Well, Gabe's not the father.
I never met the guy.
But you're suing him for child support?
He wasn't the baby's dad,
but he's still responsible for her.
What does this have to do
with child support?
My ex-husband didn't want kids.
I took the precautions,
and they worked until nine months ago,
and Andy accused me
of doing it on purpose.
So, he left?
Yeah. He was long gone before I even
thought to check the pills from GeneGevity
'cause that's when I saw
that the multivitamin was different
from the originals the company sent.
GeneGevity changed the pills
and didn't tell you?
They switched manufacturers to a cheaper
one that used different ingredients.
Did they add St. John's wort
to this new one?
Mm-hmm.
-And what is that?
-It's an herb.
People take it for depression
or skin irritations,
but it has a lot of drug interactions,
including messing up
your birth control pills,
which I'm assuming are
those precautions you're talking about.
Yeah. And the company
stopped taking my calls.
So I needed to get
their attention somehow.
So you sued them for child support.
First the company, then Gabe.
I didn't think I would win,
but I'd hoped to get him into court
so that I could talk to him face to face,
appeal to his humanity.
Look, I didn't kill Gabe.
I was furious with him, but not enough
to risk having this baby born in prison.
[inhales deeply] Whoa.
You know there's a more
comfortable couch right over here.
-Why don't you go sit down?
-Thanks. Thank you.
What the hell was Gabe thinking?
Herbal drug interactions are no joke,
and he would know that.
And for what?
So his billion-dollar company
could save a few hundred grand?
Well, maybe his company wasn't
as flush with money as we thought.
Let's pay GeneGevity a little visit.
Place doesn't look like
it's hurting for money.
[Karadec] Mmm.
-Ooh. Don't eat those.
-Why?
Bio samples.
Why so close?
I'm sorry,
GeneGevity is closed to visitors today.
We've suffered a loss.
That's why we're here.
We need to speak to whoever's
in charge of GeneGevity's finances.
That was Gabe.
Our board might be able to help,
but they're currently occupied.
They've gathered to share reflections
and grieve as a family.
-[glass shatters]
-[board member 1] Damn it!
-I told you this already!
-[board member 2] I don't believe you!
-You have a lot of nerve, you know that?
-I have a lot of nerve?
-Yeah, you do.
-That's funny…
Suppose every family reflects
and grieves in their own way.
-[board member 1] You do this every--
-No! Your words, your words.
-You knew what you were doing!
-You are delusional!
-The numbers don't lie!
-No! But you do!
Excuse me. Detective Karadec, LAPD.
How about we all just take a step back?
-Tell me what's going on here.
-Happy to.
My dear coworker Leona
is a manipulative resource hog
who had my lab programs killed.
I didn't kill your programs, Carter!
If anything, your bloated budget ate mine!
We were this close to a breakthrough!
Please. All those
secretive meetings with Gabe,
and then, boom, you get a new MRI machine?
I did not get an MRI machine, but you--
-Oh.
-Oh, what?
Neither of you got your equipment,
and I think I know why.
You guys familiar with the old phrase
"the check's in the mail"?
It's been a way to delay payment
since the invention of paper checks.
I'm so sorry. The check's in the mail.
Gabe was taking that old trick
one step further.
Check's in the mail.
On paper, he was buying goods
but wiring the funds to himself.
I sent it. The check's in the mail.
If the vendors got suspicious,
Gabe would just hit him with a…
The check's in the mail.
Gabe kept your department siloed
and the finances hidden,
and so you'd blame each other.
Wait, what are you saying?
Gabe was embezzling?
We're saying your boss
was bleeding GeneGevity dry
one fraudulent transaction at a time.
And if anyone here knew about it,
that's motive to kill.
No wonder Gabe never let anyone
near the books. GeneGevity's broke.
And you have no idea
what he did with the money?
No, this company was his life.
Well, it might have cost him his life.
-Where were the both of you last night?
-Here, working.
You can ask our staff.
Neither of us would kill Gabe.
We can vouch for each other.
You two were about to kill
each other when we walked in.
What's going on with this sudden truce?
'Cause we both care
about this company's mission.
Or what was our mission.
When the investors find out about
this fraud, they're gonna pull the money.
We're gonna need a list
of these investors so that we can--
[computers, phones chiming]
You guys need to get that?
Uh, we got a video message.
It's from Gabe.
If you're receiving this message,
my natural life is over.
Upon my death,
hopefully many years from now,
I've instructed my attorneys to share
this message of love with you all.
What will follow
will be a period of change,
but rest assured, the most important
things will remain constant,
and you won't be out at sea
without a captain for long.
My successor will be in contact soon.
Live well, my friends.
Weird.
Any idea who this successor might be?
-Mom, you home?
-In here.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I would have had some food ready. [kisses]
-It's okay, I'm not hungry.
-Oh. You will eat.
-Oh. By the way, I ran into Nadia…
-Hmm?
…and apparently her son
wants to be a detective now.
Last week it was podcasts.
I can't keep up.
But I told her that
he could call you for advice.
Yeah, sure.
I went to the cemetery today.
Anne,
did you order Dad's headstone?
I know losing Dad has been hard, but we've
moved the memorial twice already.
If you need me to sort out the headstone,
I can do it.
Your father isn't gonna have a headstone.
What do you mean?
There's no money for it.
But you said you used Dad's life insurance
to pay for the funeral expenses.
I did. I-- Well, I-I-I thought I did.
I-I went to--
to meet with the funeral director,
made the arrangements,
uh, then there were more costs and…
so many decisions and…
I don't know what happened, but…
-Anne.
-The-- The money is gone.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I'm embarrassed,
and I didn't want you to worry.
So, you thought it was better
just to wait for me to find out?
I'm sorry, Lev.
But we can still have the memorial.
Without a headstone?
Dad deserves better than that.
[breathes shakily]
[sighs]
So, your mom called me this morning.
She said you two had a fight, and since
you weren't picking up your phone,
she wanted me to see if you were okay.
It wasn't a fight, and I'm fine.
Are you sure?
'Cause, look, it just seems like you--
Daph, I really don't want to
talk about it if that's okay.
-Sorry.
-Okay.
What do you got for me?
Uh, the financial crimes team
looked into GeneGevity's books
and Gabe's personal finances.
Gabe was definitely embezzling
from the company,
but he wasn't keeping
the money for himself.
No vanity purchases like cars or boats.
No gambling debts either.
So, what was he buying?
At first, other companies.
Most of them make sense for him.
Neural brain tech start-ups,
software companies, a skincare brand.
Then a year ago he bought a nursing home
in Santa Clarita. Brookville Manor.
Since then,
all the money he stole went there.
So, a 55-year-old who was healthier
than most 25-year-olds
bought a nursing home? For what?
-No idea.
-Hmm.
Well, I guess I'm picking up Morgan
on my way to Santa Clarita.
Millions of dollars
of stolen money spent on this?
I didn't see anything on the website
about it being closed,
but this place looks abandoned.
[Morgan] Excuse me.
I'm Detective Karadec.
This is Morgan Gillory.
Jesse Lascala.
-Mr. Lascala, did you know Gabe Rafferty?
-Yes, I worked for him.
We have reason to believe that
Mr. Rafferty was funneling
large sums of money to this facility,
but there are no patients here.
Where was the money going exactly?
To the therapy team,
physical, occupational speech.
It's why Gabe purchased Brookville Manor.
We have the best specialists
and equipment in the country.
He relocated the residents
so he could have our full focus.
Okay. Uh, but by all accounts,
Gabe was incredibly healthy.
Why would he need therapists?
To help him reach
his full human potential.
[gasps] Oh. What the hell does that mean?
Let me show you.
Are we in a morgue?
I don't think these are actual bodies.
[mechanical whirring]
Explain. Quickly.
It's best if Gabe explains for himself.
Gabe?
Gabe, you have visitors.
-[machine chimes]
-[Gabe] How wonderful.
Please, join me.
So, how's this work?
We supposed to push a button or something?
We can continue on our own, Jesse.
Thank you.
Ms. Gillory, Detective Karadec,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
How do you know who we are?
I scanned your faces and ran it through
facial recognition software.
Mm-mmm. Don't like that.
Now, I'm assuming
you're here about my death.
You know you're dead?
Well, I know my physical body is gone,
yes, but that doesn't mean that I'm dead.
-No, it does though.
-I'm pretty sure it does.
Perhaps at one time that was true,
but with advancements in technology,
we can exist far beyond
our corporeal reality.
I'm proof of that.
But the lack of a physical presence
can be unsettling,
so I'm taking steps to remedy that.
Aha. So that's why the crash test dummies.
I prefer humanoid robot replica.
Hang on, are you trying to
put yourself into one of these?
Ugh.
[exclaims] Look.
-Weird.
-So this is why you bankrupted GeneGevity?
For some robots?
I regret the steps
I had to take to get here.
It's taken more time
and resources than I planned,
but my depth of knowledge has
the potential to help millions of people.
It would be a waste if it died with me.
Now it never will.
What does that mean?
Every email, text, video
and book I've ever read
or written was uploaded into this form.
Hang on, are you saying that
everything that Gabe knew, you know?
Yes.
Okay.
Um, first question, who killed you?
-I can't answer that.
-[clicks tongue] Shoot.
I can't believe we're doing this.
Okay.
Other than the, uh, users and investors
you've defrauded,
did Gabe have any enemies?
I've received a few death threats
over the years, none I found serious.
May 2011, December 2015, March 2020,
August 2024.
I also received other less
directly threatening messages.
-I've dropped the list to your phones.
-[phones buzz]
-Really? [gasps]
-We'll look at those.
Meantime,
your routine the day you were killed,
was there anything unusual about it?
I assume I followed my normal routine.
Awake at 7:00, self-care protocols,
GeneGevity work,
meditation at 9:00 p.m.,
and then in bed right after.
Well, did you ever go to bed
in your meditation room?
No. A strict sleep routine is essential.
That's why the house is set to go into
Do Not Disturb mode promptly at 10:15.
10:15? No.
The panel at your house said
Do Not Disturb went on at 9:00 p.m.
Why would it be any different
on the day you were killed?
My operating system is connected
to my home's monitoring system.
-Let me check.
-[machine chimes]
My password was used
to adjust the Do Not Disturb at 9:05.
So Gabe did change the settings.
No, it wasn't me. I was in the house.
So, are you saying someone
accessed the panel remotely? Who?
Let me che… Let me che…
[distorted warbling]
Uh, Jesse, Gabe died.
You're telling me
there are no headstone companies
closer to Los Angeles than Italy?
I get that's what she ordered, but I…
You know what, how about I stop
by your funeral home after my shift
as a police detective,
and then we have a chat?
No, it's not a threat,
just a conversation.
-We'll clear this up face to face.
-Detective Ozdil. A word, please.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Lieutenant. I should have
stepped out to take that call.
-Won't happen again.
-You're not in trouble, Oz.
I'm worried about you.
What's going on?
Okay. Um…
The $20,000 headstone my mother bought for
my dad is stuck in a shipping container
in Genoa, racking up export fees she can't
pay because the insurance money is gone.
$20,000.
-I don't know what she was thinking.
-She probably wasn't thinking.
Not clearly anyway.
It sounds like the funeral home took
advantage of her and she was upsold.
It's disgusting.
But unfortunately common.
It's not her fault.
It's my fault.
I wasn't there.
My dad, he was always there for us.
After he died, I should have stepped up
like he always did, but I just…
My mom had to handle everything.
The paperwork, the funeral,
the hospital, all of it alone.
I mean, what kind of son lets that happen?
A grieving one.
When my mom passed, I was lost.
I was suddenly the matriarch
of my big, complicated family.
It was a lot.
And the one person I always counted on
to get me through
when life got tough
was the one that was gone.
How'd you get through it?
The same way you will.
With time.
But healing only happens when you
stop inflicting yourself with new wounds.
Yeah.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
So, the robot gave you the lead?
Yes, and I know how that sounds.
Gabe Two gave us a list of digital threats
that Gabe received.
Over the past few months,
the only person capable
and angry enough to take down the bot
was the founder of a startup
that Gabe bought and then shuttered.
A guy named Mika Astor.
You want me to pick him up for boticide?
[scoffs] The lieutenant's gonna love that.
Actually, we think that Gabe
and Gabe Two's murders were related.
Jesse said when the bot went down,
it looked like when he'd seen
Gabe Two being rebooted.
Only a few people have
the skill to do that remotely.
Whoever overrode the bot's securities
could've done the same
with Gabe's home network.
Okay. I'll bring Mika in
and see what he knows.
I've advised my client not to speak.
All questions are to be directed to me.
Wonderful.
Your client owned a company, Chatabelle,
that was sold eight months ago
to Gabe Rafferty.
-Is that correct?
-Yes.
Chatabelle specialized
in a language learning software
for "companion experiences."
In other words, AI virtual girlfriends.
[chuckles] That is so reductive.
I provided a cutting edge
invaluable service to thousands of--
Mika.
[sighs]
Gabe bought Chatabelle
from you for a hefty price tag.
But then you started harassing him
to sell you the company back.
This is a business matter.
Why is Major Crimes so interested?
Gabe Rafferty was recently murdered
in his secure home.
Your client had the motive and ability to
spoof Gabe's password and enter his house.
[lawyer] That's ridiculous.
Mika's a genius.
He would never throw his life away
over something as trivial as one start-up.
You didn't think it was trivial, did you?
Chatabelle was important to you.
You wanted it back to right a wrong.
-It was my company.
-Mika.
Chatabelle was everything to me.
Gabe said he'd let me come work for him
so I could still be a part of it.
But instead he pushed you out.
After he made me sign a noncompete clause.
Five years.
That's a death sentence
in this industry.
[chuckles]
I brought that stupid bot to life.
And you had every right to take it out.
What about human Gabe?
You take him out too?
According to Gabe Two's records,
someone accessed the panel at 9:00 p.m.
Why are these plants dying?
Gabe's got plants all over the house.
They're as healthy as he is.
What's going on with these?
[door locks]
-[Karadec] Oh.
-What'd you do?
Not sure, honestly,
but I think whoever was messing
with the Do Not Disturb mode
also set it to lock this door.
So somebody wanted to lock Gabe in here.
Why?
Maybe they stabbed him,
wanted him to bleed out
without any chance of getting help.
Did the ME email you the report?
Yeah. What do you need to know?
Did it say anything
about his nasal passages?
Nasal passages showed
signs of inflammation. His throat too.
ME seems to think
it might have been a reaction
to the steroidal nasal spray he used.
No, it was a reaction to something else.
An intruder didn't stab Gabe.
Gabe stabbed himself.
[scoffs] Why would he do that?
Because he preferred it
to the alternative.
Dead bugs, scorched plants.
I think I know what happened.
Someone rigged this room
to fill with toxic gas
and locked Gabe in here with it.
He tried to get out,
but there was no escape.
The symptoms of it
must have been excruciating
if Gabe was willing to choose killing
himself over his dreams of immortality.
[gas whooshing]
You think the gas was set to go off
when the Do Not Disturb was triggered?
And we just triggered it again.
Thanks, Selena.
Soto's sending a team over here to
get us out. They'll be here soon.
-How soon?
-As quickly as possible.
Well, that's not fast enough.
We don't even know where
this gas is coming from.
It could be coming from here,
it could be from any of these things.
[stammers] The vents,
or there could be, like, a-a hidden pipe
that we don't know about, or it
could be coming up through the floor.
I hear you, but still,
it doesn't make any sense to panic.
It's not panic. I'm not panicking.
It's the… That's just math.
It's a ten-by-ten room.
We've got oxygen plus carbon dioxide
times two people breathing it,
plus whatever gas this is.
That doesn't add up to much time
is all I'm saying, okay?
If I knew what the gas was,
I could come up with a plan,
but we don't know that.
But what we do know is that a person
who wanted to live forever
chose to end his own life
rather than suffer
whatever this gas was going to do to him.
-So, what exactly does that do for us?
-Morgan.
-I just ne… Leave me alone for a second.
Please leave me alone for a second.
I gotta think. I just… I need to think.
How do we get out of here?
[breathes heavily]
Morgan, you have to slow down.
Just take a breath.
A breath? Taking a breath is not what
we should be doing right now.
-How are you so calm?
-Because panicking doesn't help.
Okay. Well, neither does
just standing there.
I gotta do the
"five, four, three, two, one" thing.
I need five things I can see. I can see…
Uh…
A salt lamp and a bowl and matches.
A dead…
Dying plants. How many was that?
-Morgan--
-Four. Stop.
I gotta ground. Four things I can…
I can touch. I touch the floor.
I don't know if the floor counts as one.
What is the name of that stool?
That stool has a name.
You know who'd know the name
of that stool?
[crying] Elliot would know the name
of that. He really loves stuff like this.
He's such a smart boy, but he's not
gonna be able to understand this.
Oh, God! Ava already had one parent
leave her. I can't leave her.
-You are not going to leave her--
-Stop! Three things I hear.
Three things I hear.
I can't smell anything.
Chloe is just a baby.
You don't understand.
She needs her mom, and she's a baby.
-You're not gonna be leaving your--
-I can't… I… I can't breathe.
Adam, I can't breathe. Stop! Leave it!
-I can't breathe! Please don't.
-It's okay.
-[crying] It's not okay.
I'm right here.
Morgan, it's gonna be okay. I've got you.
-[breathes heavily]
-I'm not going anywhere.
It's okay. I've got you.
I'm not gonna let you go.
-[breathing heavily]
-I got you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I got you. I'm not letting you go.
It's okay.
You're okay.
[gasps] Oh.
See?
[whimpering]
[phone buzzing]
Selena? Yeah. Yeah, the door is open.
We're fine. Okay.
All right, I will.
Soto got Mika
to, uh, access the doors remotely.
Mirror neurons.
-What?
-It's a…
It's just an unconscious,
empathetic brain response. Like a yawn.
Your breathing
and your heart rate were calm,
so they calmed mine down,
so… [whimpers] …thank you.
So, um, you're good?
Yeah, I'm good. Let's get back to work.
Okay, so we didn't drop dead.
That's exciting.
Maybe the gas needed more time
to fill up the room.
Or maybe the door locking
isn't what triggered it.
[Renata] I checked Gabe's biodata
through the GeneGevity app.
[Karadec] No forced entry.
Housekeeper said the alarm was still set
when she got here.
You're right.
Gabe triggered it.
But he was set up.
I know who did it.
-Thanks for coming in.
-Anything I can do for Gabe.
That's sweet.
That's not anything new though, is it?
You've been helping Gabe out
for about eight years.
Well, I like to think
we were helping each other.
I mean, Gabe was such an amazing person.
That would be much easier to believe
if you weren't the one that killed him.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I wasn't even in LA when Gabe was killed.
You didn't need to be.
The ME confirmed that there were traces
of arsenic in Gabe's airways.
He inhaled it before he died.
Which is an odd way
to get arsenic into your body.
Arsenic was once referred to
as "inheritance powder"
because of its use in getting rid
of unwanted family members.
Then, for a while, copper arsenite
became the dye of choice
for those looking to up
their fashion game.
They called it Scheele's green.
Especially once
incandescent light bulbs showed up.
People really wanted their dresses to pop.
That didn't work out so well.
But clothes weren't the only thing
people used the dye in.
It snuck into candy,
wallpaper, and for a while… candles.
Only trouble was, burning the candles
released arsenic gas into the air,
but you already knew that, didn't you?
Your study of 19th-century arts
and textiles taught you all about it.
The candles provided the perfect cover.
When Gabe lit them and released the gas,
you were at your sister's wedding
on Catalina.
And that timing was very poetic,
wasn't it?
Because your sister is part of the reason
you wanted Gabe dead.
-I don't understand any of this.
-Yeah, you do.
You see this scar?
That's a port scar from chemotherapy.
Your sister is undergoing cancer
treatment. She has breast cancer.
The same cancer that took your mother, the
same cancer you're worried about getting.
GeneGevity was researching the BRCA genes
that you and your family carry.
Or they were
until Gabe started embezzling funds
and they had to shut down the program.
Gabe betrayed you,
and you returned the favor.
Mika's already confessed. He said
he's the one that told you about the box.
He came by Gabe's house looking to get his
company back, and you two hatched a plan.
[Morgan] He had the skills
to clone Gabe's passwords.
All he needed to know from you was when
to remotely deploy the Do Not Disturb.
And since Gabe follows a strict routine,
it really wasn't a difficult ask.
[Karadec] You waited
until you had an alibi
and swapped out Gabe's regular meditation
candles for the ones with the green dye,
knowing his housekeeper
changes them daily.
[Morgan] And Gabe took care of the rest.
I was upset when I found out GeneGevity
had shut down the BRCA research,
but when Mika told me what Gabe
was actually spending the money on,
I was livid.
A robot of himself.
I mean, I… I couldn't believe it.
I confronted him about it,
and you know what he said?
"Sacrifices have to be made."
My sister and I aren't sacrifices
that he gets to make.
He was stealing our future.
So you decided that Gabe
shouldn't have a future either.
Maybe with Gabe
and his bot out of the way,
GeneGevity can get back on track.
They can start their research again
and give people like me and my sister
a fighting chance.
Gabe deserved to die.
[door opens]
[door closes]
You know, I never thought of you
as the sentimental type.
I am so surprised you kept this.
But why? It was a gift, right?
Do you remember what you said
when I gave it to you?
-[sighs] No.
-Nothing.
You just stared at it
for the longest time.
And then when you finally looked up at me,
you had this expression on your face
like you weren't really sure
it was for you.
I didn't think I deserved it.
Or you.
And now?
Lucia, honestly, I don't know.
I hope I've changed enough
to be who you need, but--
Adam, you were always who I needed.
I wasn't the one who needed
to be convinced of that.
You broke my heart
when you called off our engagement.
But I think you broke yours too.
I don't want to hurt you again.
Then don't.
[♪ ballad plays]
-It's--
-Perfect.
Dad would have been proud.
[speaks Turkish]
Rumor is you pulled some strings.
The funeral home just happens to be
-on my way home from work.
-Mmm.
And in violation of the FTC rules
against predatory price gouging.
-That could cost them their license.
-Yeah, it could.
But they generously offered Mrs. Ozdil
a full refund,
and they gave her the headstone
she actually wanted.
I thank you all for being here.
Not all of you met my dad.
But I can tell you
he would have loved you.
Talked your ear off.
Had us all laughing till the sun came up.
He used to tell me that all of this…
doesn't last forever.
That's the point.
It takes loss to really know
what you have.
Family.
Friends.
Friends who become family.
You gotta hold them all
just a little tighter.
Life is beautiful because it's brief…
and death…
is just the beginning of something new.
[♪ song continues]
-It was a nice service.
-Yeah, it was.
It's good that we could be here for Oz.
Okay. You, uh…
have a good day, partner.
-That was really weird.
-Yeah, well, it's weird. I feel weird.
I'm horrified about
what happened at Gabe's.
I just completely fell apart.
And it's not something I typically love
doing in front of other people.
Well, I'm not other people.
I'm your partner.
Yeah, that's worse. You should be able
to count on me when we're in trouble.
I just was a giant useless mess.
Are you really apologizing
for being human, Morgan?
Come on, we're a team.
We count on each other.
-You would've done the same for me.
-When?
In what world is Adam Karadec
falling apart on the job?
Well, just 'cause it hasn't happened yet
doesn't mean that it won't.
And when that time comes, I know that,
out of all the people in my life,
you will know exactly what to do.
[♪ song continues]
Thanks.
Do you need me to punch that
other shoulder to just even you out?
I need you to get out of here
before your car breaks down again.
[♪ song continues]
[song fades]