( Watch on www.kissasia.biz & asiankh.org )
♪ Unable to be forced— ♪
It was nice...
seeing you again.
Wow, Via.
[In Spanish]
How are you, miss?
Look, it’s my dude, Larkin.
He’s here to welcome you.
There. These are the clothes,
and those are
the groceries I bought.
And we’ll also buy you your
own guitar so you’ll have one.
It’s nice.
Aidan, do you need a capo—
Hey, miss.
You forgot something.
Architect, your idea is spot on.
- Are you okay?
- You okay?
- I’m okay.
- Via, are you okay?
Yes, I’m okay. Don’t worry.
We need to go, Clea.
We need to finish
all the sequences
since we won’t have
a shoot until next week.
Thank you so much,
Architect, for today.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you.
We’ll go ahead.
Yeah.
Here.
Looks like the rain is getting heavy.
Thank you.
We’ll go ahead.
Please welcome, Larkin Sanchez!
He’s so handsome!
This song is about someone
who wants to confess their
love to their closest friend.
But at the same time—
too afraid to lose
everything they have.
It was nice...
seeing you again.
Alaris, destination: Lleida via 5.
Why did we even
have to meet again?
Feels like fate is just teasing me.
Thank you—
Alvia, destination:
Irun and Bilbao via 4.
How are you?
I’m fine.
Why did you come here?
I came here to give you this.
You left it.
I meant to leave that behind.
Does that apply to me, too?
Did you mean to leave me, too?
Attention, please.
The train bound for
Sant Vicenç de Calders—
All right, then.
Via 9.
That’s all I need to know.
Attention, please.
The train bound for Sant
Vicenç de Calders, platform 9.
♪ Say it now, ♪
♪ say it’s really over. ♪
♪ That you don’t love me anymore, ♪
♪ and you don’t want
to see me again. ♪
♪ Say it now,
under the moonlight, ♪
♪ where everything started. ♪
- Wow!
- Amazing.
You’ve gotten better now, son!
You really improved.
- Awesome!
- Thanks.
Just like Arkin.
Via, are you busy?
Let’s go to the mall.
They say the store with
my favorite band’s merch is open.
Please, Via.
Papa said we’re going.
Pa, you’re the one who said it.
Go with them to the mall.
Come on.
Go with your siblings.
They’ve been nagging
since yesterday.
Arkin has a mall show tomorrow.
At the same mall.
Should we go out tomorrow instead?
Let’s watch him!
You guys go ahead.
Just kidding.
I keep seeing Arkin, anyway.
You keep seeing him?
Via, you should
also visit Auntie Allie.
They miss you there.
How can I visit if Arkin’s there too?
We need to finish
all the sequences
since we won’t have
a shoot until next week.
All right.
I’ll visit on the weekend.
Come on, let’s go
to the mall now.
Get ready, take a shower.
I’ll need to buy a gift
to take to Auntie Allie.
- Okay, okay, let’s go!
- Okay, Via.
Let’s go.
Hi, Clea. I’m done with
the revisions on the design.
Let me know
when we can meet.
Hi, Architect.
I’ll check my schedule.
Maybe I can go to your office.
Oh, by the way,
Larkin is asking about his umbrella.
Oh, okay.
Arkin said that you
should return his umbrella.
Not you, too?
“All I want is for you
to come back.” — me to my umbrella.
Good morning!
- Good morning.
Umbrella for the bag.
Another umbrella for the bag.
Umbrella for the house.
I’ll never run out
of umbrellas in my life.
Did he really think
I wouldn’t return his umbrella?
Are you okay, Architect?
Of course! I’m fine.
Back to work, guys.
Umbrellas…
Hi, Architect! Sorry,
but can we do the presentation
on set instead?
This is the only
free time I have this month.
I might see him there again,
but I have no choice.
I need to finish this project.
I don’t want to delay it any further.
Okay. See you.
So he’s actually here?
I hope they don’t recognize me.
I don’t want what happened
before to happen again.
Are you Architect Diaz?
I’m Ma’am Clea’s
personal assistant.
She’s just finishing a scene.
This way, please.
For Ma’am Clea.
Is that her?
It is.
Action!
I can’t get you out of my head.
Ma’am, please wait here.
We’re rolling.
In that case—
this will make it
harder for you.
Why am I even here?
Cut!
One more take.
Arkin, I need to feel it, okay?
I’m not feeling it.
You have to kiss her
passionately.
You have to be
hungry for her, got it?
I’m not feeling anything.
All right. Arkin, we’ll pick up
from that last part?
“I can’t get you out of my head.”
Standby slate.
We’ll do another take!
Sound!
Camera? Rolling.
Take two.
Mark—
And—
Three, two, one—
Action!
I can’t get you out of my head.
In that case,
this will make it harder for you.
Cut!
It’s terrible! Damn it!
Arkin, what is happening to you?
Oh my gosh!
We’ve been going over
this again and again.
Where are you even looking?
Do you see something I don’t?
Over and over.
We’re wasting time.
It should be so simple.
What’s happening?
The woman is actually
the one leading you.
Is this your first time
doing a kissing scene?
It’s not, right?
Sorry, Director.
Come on, now!
Why did I even agree
to meet Clea here?
We’re victims of fate again.
Okay, Director.
Focus, please.
I’ll just wait for her outside.
Excuse me.
What a waste of time.
One more retouch.
- This is the last, okay?
- Yes, Director.
So annoying.
This is so great. I love it.
Thank you so much, Architect.
You really captured
everything I wanted.
Is this approved?
Yeah! We can start
the construction soon.
Great.
Finally, I don’t have to go
to their set anymore.
I’ll just be at the construction
site all the time.
Why is he here?
Is this his dressing room too?
What’s wrong, Larkin?
You seem distracted today.
Lack of sleep.
I thought I was
already seeing things.
Like what?
Like my ex.
Now, I know I’m not
seeing things.
Come on.
We’re all professionals
here and also—
Architect Diaz is
designing my house.
Okay.
Miss Clea? You’re called on set.
Sir Larkin, it’s time to
change for the next scene.
Okay.
Thank you so
much again, Architect.
I’ll see you on-site?
Yeah.
I’ll just send my assistant
to show you the way out.
Yeah.
- Thank you.
What?
What are you staring at?
I’m changing.
This is the dressing
room, remember?
Right.
See, I’m leaving now.
What?
Where’s my umbrella?
Of course, I didn’t bring it,
because that’s not
what I came here for.
But don’t worry,
even if I lose it,
I’ll buy you a new one,
as many as you want.
Do you really think I can’t
afford to buy an umbrella?
Give it back.
That was from Mama.
Don’t worry.
I’ll return it. I’ll drop it off
at your place
so you’ll stop sulking like a kid.
Did you say something?
Say it again.
You’re so rude.
I’m telling your mom.
Wow.
So mature, Architect Diaz.
[In Spanish] Whatever.
You’re getting on my nerves.
[In Spanish] Such an asshole.
What are you mumbling about?
You might be putting a curse on me.
Why would I do that, Larkin?
With a face like yours,
the curse has been done.
Wow.
So cocky.
You just went to Spain
and now your comebacks
have gotten so good.
Semi middle finger.
♪ I find myself smiling again, ♪
♪ and you are the reason for it. ♪
♪ I find myself smiling again. ♪
Wow.
So you can sing
while playing now, huh?
Of course.
Who’s that song for, huh?
For my crush.
A crush?
You have a crush now?
No wonder you’re singing
with so much emotion.
This is their favorite song,
and I’m planning to
confess next week.
Oh no, don’t confess.
You’ll just ruin your life.
You’re so bitter, Via!
Check this out, Via.
Just a second.
Luna!
Via! We have a batch
reunion this weekend, okay?
We’re going. Just say, yes.
I don’t want to
get stressed there.
Arkin won’t be there.
He has a shoot, apparently.
Are you sure?
I think so.
Let’s just go!
You’ll be with me and Ke, anyway.
Fine.
Okay, I’ll go.
See you!
- Love you.
- See you.
Why aren’t you singing?
- Should I?
- Of course.
- Are you sure?
- Okay.
I told you, he’s not coming.
Come on, let’s eat.
- Okay.
- You guys, go ahead.
I just need to grab
something for a bit.
- All right.
- Just a moment.
Via!
Hey, you look amazing.
You’re sexier now, too!
Thanks. You too,
you look so beautiful.
Oh, no big deal, but is it true?
You’re an architect
in Spain now?
Yes.
Wow. Nice, Architect Diaz.
How have you been?
I’m okay. We’re currently
living in Italy now.
You, do you have
a family already?
Hi!
It’s Larkin!
Hi. Hi, everyone.
Larkin!
Long time no see.
Hi, hi.
I’m sorry.
Hi!
Good thing you
invited your best friend.
Well, you two were inseparable
back in high school.
I actually thought
you’d end up together.
Hi.
How are you, guys?
What’s up? I’m good.
How are you?
It’s so nice to see
each other again, right?
All right, I’ll go ahead.
Hey, how are you?
I’ll just keep quiet.
It’s more exhausting to explain why
we’re not best
friends anymore,
than to just go along with it.
I don’t really need
to explain to them
what happened
between Arkin and me.
Most of them already know.
It was all over the news.
Via…
They said he had a shoot today.
No one told me he was coming.
No one.
Don’t be mad, please?
Come on. Let’s sit down.
Sit down.
I’m really sorry, okay?
Let’s just eat.
Hi!
Hi, friends!
How are you, guys?
How are you? Have you eaten?
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
- Shot, shot!
- Go, Luna!
- Go, girl!
My turn!
I’ll do it.
That’s it!
My turn now!
Go.
Shot!
- Shot, shot!
I’m sorry, did I hurt you?
If it hurts, you can
just quit if you want.
I’m sorry.
I’m not the type who leaves
easily or gives up,
even when it hurts.
Hey!
Arkin, what the heck?
It was just an accident.
Don’t make a big deal out of it.
Come on.
Drink some more.
Don’t you want to drink anymore?
You don’t want to?
Oh, no. I do. I can handle it.
- You can handle it?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Hey!
- Yes, excuse me.
- Just wanna make sure.
Yes!
Wait.
One more?
So strong!
One more!
- One more!
Is it strong?
I don’t think so.
Are you drunk now?
Am I drunk?
I drank so much because
of someone here
and then he asks me,
if I’m drunk?
You’re really annoying.
You are drunk.
I’m calling Luna.
Luna?
Luna already left with
our other batchmates.
And Ke…
Ke is…
Whatever!
Get out of here.
I’ll go to Luna and Ke myself.
To Luna and Ke.
What are you—
I’ll drive you home.
I’ll take you home.
And I’ll get my umbrella too.
I told you, I’m not drunk.
Be careful.
Don’t touch me.
I can manage.
You can’t.
I can.
- Be careful.
- I’m not drunk.
- Careful.
- I’m not drunk. Don’t touch me.
Don’t touch me.
Ouch!
Why didn’t you hold me?
You said not
to touch you, remember?
I didn’t say that.
I’m not drunk.
Slow down.
You’re so annoying.
When are you going
to leave me alone?
Okay, get in and sit.
Slowly.
Where are you even taking me?
I’m taking you home.
Don’t worry.
Hello, Ke?
Yeah, I’ll take Via home.
I’m bringing her home now.
I’ll drop her off at her place, okay?
I’ve got it covered.
All right.
I’ll just update you guys.
Okay. Take care.
Easy…
I’m gonna go home.
All right, here we are.
Oh my God.
Gonna go home—
Easy, easy.
- I told you, I’m okay.
- Okay.
I’m really not drunk.
I can manage. There’s the door.
Okay.
Easy now.
Where’s the key? Give it to me.
I can do it.
I’ll do it.
This is my house.
Wait.
You’re too loud,
you’ll wake them up.
- Keep it down.
- You’re the loud one, Via.
Oh no.
- It doesn’t fit.
- Okay, I’ve got it.
I’ll do it.
Oh no. Open the door.
Open the door. Door, open!
You’re too loud. Stop it.
- The door won’t open.
- Let me do it.
The door opened.
Because of the key.
Come on.
I told you, I can do it.
Put me down.
- I can manage.
- Don’t move around, you might fall again.
- I can manage!
- Careful now.
I can take care of myself.
I already told you.
I can walk.
I’m okay now.
I’ll just take a shower.
Can you do it?
If not, are you going to give me a bath?
I’m fine. You can go now.
Go home.
Thanks.
I’ll wait for you.
Huh? No, it’s fine. I’m really okay.
I need my umbrella.
You should shower now
because you smell like alcohol.
Okay.
I’ll be right back.
Wait.
What’s the biggest star
doing in my room?
You really don’t want to go
home because of your umbrella?
Good night, Kino.
Look at how well I cooked this.
You’re so boastful, Arkin.
I can do that easily.
It’s not that perfect.
Look, there’s not even
a little bit of burn anywhere.
See?
He hasn’t left yet?
Is it because of the umbrella?
- But, Arkin—
- Thank you.
Thanks for cooking
breakfast for us.
It’s an honor to be cooked
for by a famous actor.
So now you’re teasing me, Ysha?
And because of that,
this one’s for you.
Not a stoated—
- egg.
- Come on, Arkin.
Okay, fine. Toasted. Say it.
- Toasted.
That’s right.
That’s how it should be.
Here you go, your black coffee.
Let me have some.
I don’t know why
you drink black coffee,
you’re still so young.
He really knows
how to cook now.
Feels like just yesterday
he was burning hotdogs.
Here’s your hot chocolate.
That’s your favorite, right?
How do you say it?
Hot chocolate.
He’s still the same as before.
He still takes care of my family.
Arkin, teach me how to
play the piano next time.
I thought you wanted
to learn guitar?
Well, I also want to learn piano.
All right. Come over
to my house,
there’s a piano there,
I’ll teach you. Okay?
Sure.
Should I bring Via, too?
Don’t worry, I’m not coming.
Wait, I don’t think
I said you could come.
I’m just saying. Just in case.
So, you assumed you could come?
I’m just saying. Why?
Am I not allowed?
Via, let’s have breakfast.
Arkin, take a seat.
Let’s eat.
No, it’s okay.
I need to leave anyway
because I have a shoot.
Huh?
Wait, Arkin. We’ll prepare you
some food to bring.
No. It’s okay. There’s food
at the set. It’s fine.
I really just prepared
this for all of you.
- I gotta go now.
- Wow.
Wait, I just need to
grab my cap upstairs.
We’re not getting
back together, okay?
We know, Via.
You’re being way too defensive.
I’m just making sure it’s clear.
Dear sister, it’s as clear as day.
Just eat already.
All right.
I’ll go ahead now.
Finish all the food.
You’re supposed
to finish it all. Okay?
Yes, Arkin.
- Bye, Arkin.
- Bye.
Take care, Arkin.
Bye.
Bye to you three.
Hold on!
Wait a second.
Here’s your umbrella.
So you won’t have to
look for it from me anymore.
Can I have some?
- Thank you.
- You can keep it.
Huh?
Then why didn’t he
just leave last night
if it weren’t for the umbrella?
Hey! Wait! Your umbrella!
Arkin—
Your umbrella.
You can keep it.
I don’t need it anymore.
Take the umbrella.
You might end up looking
for it from me again next time.
I really don’t need it anymore.
Wait.
Here.
I really can’t bring myself
to get close to you.
Cut!
It’s terrible! Damn it!
Arkin, what is happening to you?
Oh my gosh!
We’ve been going over
this again and again.
Where are you even looking?
Do you see something I don’t?
Over and over.
We’re wasting time.
It should be so simple.
What’s happening?
The woman is actually
the one leading you.
Is this your first time
doing a kissing scene?
It’s not, right?
Sorry, Director.
I’ll just wait for her outside.
- All right.
- Excuse me.
We’re wasting time
repeating this scene.
Focus, please.
Last one. Understood?
Yes, Director.
One more retouch,
then we’ll start.
Arkin, you have to imagine
this is the best kiss of your life.
Okay, got it?
Best kiss of my life.
Camera? Rolling.
Take eight!
And—
Three, two, one—
Action!
I can’t get you out of my head.
In that case, this will
make it harder for you.
All right. There you go.
Beautiful.
And cut!
There, perfect! Right? Very good.
If you had done that
earlier, we’d be done by now.
It’s so good.
Let’s move on.
- Be careful.
- I’m not drunk.
I’m not drunk. Don’t touch me.
Don’t touch me.
I said, don’t touch me.
Do not touch me.
Okay, then. Fine.
Don’t touch me.
I won’t touch you?
I can manage.
Ouch!
Why didn’t you hold me?
You said not to touch you,
remember?
I didn’t say that. I’m not drunk.
You’re so annoying.
Come on now.
Huh?
You again?
Why are you
in front of me again?
What are you talking about?
What is it this time?
A standee?
Poster?
Billboard?
Why are you
all over the place?
Because of that face of yours.
That face.
This. This one. This face.
Your face is plastered
all over the whole country.
Everywhere.
On TV, on the radio,
in cinemas, on billboards.
Your face is everywhere.
When are you going
to leave me alone, huh?
I always see your face.
You’re drunk.
I’m not drunk!
- Come on.
- I’m not drunk.
Get inside.
Why?
I’m taking you home.
Hello, Ke?
Yeah, I’ll take Via home.
I’m bringing her home now.
I’ll drop her off at her place, okay?
I’ve got it covered.
All right.
I’ll just update you guys.
Okay. Take care.
Via?
Dan!
You’re here too?
May I?
Yeah, of course.
How are you?
I just transferred today.
Looks like we’re
co-workers now.
Looking forward to working
with you, Architect Diaz.
Same here, Architect Morales.
Hey, come with us
on the beach trip.
You know, it’s been so long
since you’ve hung out with us.
I was even thinking,
he doesn’t want to be
friends with us anymore.
Via might feel awkward.
You know we’re not okay.
All right, bye.
Take care, okay? Bye!
You’re really smiling at
whoever you’re talking to there,
Architect Diaz.
You probably have
a boyfriend now.
Huh?
A boyfriend?
No, I don’t.
Via, by the way, your vitamins.
You looked so pale
at the office earlier.