I came here to give you this.
You left it.
I meant to leave that behind.
Does that apply to me, too?
I can’t get you out of my head.
In that case—
Why am I even here?
Cut!
It’s terrible!
Damn it! Arkin,
what is happening to you?
Miss Clea?
You’re called on set.
Okay.
Sir Larkin, it’s time to change
for the next scene.
Okay.
Thank you.
One more!
Wait.
Here.
Via, you should
also visit Auntie Allie.
They miss you.
How can I visit
if Arkin’s there too?
We need to finish
all the sequences
since we won’t have
a shoot until next week.
Here.
Looks like the
rain is getting heavy.
All right. I’ll visit
on the weekend.
Come on, let’s go
to the mall now.
Get ready, take a shower.
I’ll need to buy a gift
to take to Auntie Allie.
- Okay, okay, let’s go!
- Okay, Via.
Let’s go.
- Via!
- Hi, Auntie.
Come in.
What brings you here?
It’s been a while!
Yes, I was just passing by,
and this is for you and Uncle.
Thank you. Wow.
Mira also mentioned
that you were looking for me.
I always ask about
you from your dad.
It’s a pity
Uncle Orlan isn’t here.
Arkin isn’t here either.
How was Spain?
It’s been such a long time since
we last saw each other and talked.
Yes. I’m sorry, Auntie.
I wasn’t able to keep in touch.
Also…
I felt a bit ashamed, too,
because we’re no longer a couple.
I understand, dear.
I know what you went through.
In fact,
I should be
the one apologizing.
What you went
through was really hard.
And Arkin didn’t
tell us anything and
you know how he is.
Whenever he has problems,
you’re the only one he talks to.
Have you eaten?
Do you want snacks?
Yes, please.
Okay, come.
I’ll make you something.
Okay, thank you.
I’m sure he’ll finish
his shoot late,
so I’ll just leave
early instead.
I’m so happy that
you’re doing well.
You know, I had to ask
Arkin to leave the agency.
So he has a new agency
and management now,
and he’s much happier
and really thriving.
But I actually feel guilty.
As a mother,
I should have known.
But that’s Arkin for you.
He kept everything
to himself and—
It was only after you
left that he finally told us.
That he really could
not take it anymore.
Auntie, I’m sorry.
I’m sorry I was not
able to stay by his side.
Even though I said before
that I would never leave him.
I’m sorry.
Via, I know that
leaving him was the...
hardest decision of your life.
But you know that it
made him a better person.
He learned how to stand
on his own two feet.
He’s more mature,
more responsible.
He’s no longer the
innocent boy I raised.
He knows a lot now.
He understands
how the industry works.
And he’s now enrolled
in film in Diliman.
He’s already in his third year.
He’s close to graduating.
Don’t neglect yourself, don’t
neglect your studies, okay?
Being a director is still
your real dream, right?
Via, I’m sorry.
I can’t handle both acting
and school at the same time.
That’s why my manager
had me stop attending school.
So there’s no need to worry
about Arkin anymore.
He’s doing well on his own.
He’s handling
everything by himself.
That’s good.
Via, I know he
loved you so much.
And even though
you’re no longer together,
I hope you can still
be civil with each other.
It’s just a shame,
because you were
together longer than
you were apart.
That’s what I want, too.
But I can’t blame Arkin
if he doesn’t want to,
or if he’s angry with me.
Something happened between us,
and I left him the next day.
I don’t know how
to apologize for that.
That was so selfish of me.
I think your
Uncle Orlan is here.
Ma, I’m here.
Arkin…
What are you doing here?
I was just visiting Auntie.
Auntie, I’ll get going now.
Why didn’t you tell me, Ma?
I didn’t know you’d be
coming home early.
Don’t worry,
I’m leaving anyway.
Go on, then. Leave.
Yes, I really am leaving. Bye.
Wait a second.
Where’s my umbrella?
I don’t have it.
Ma, it’s the umbrella
you gave me.
She might have already lost it.
Ma, talk to her.
What do you mean?
Of course, it’s not lost.
I’ll return it to you, don’t worry.
I’ll bring it here.
What am I supposed
to do with it?
Arkin—
Please don’t argue.
It’s fine.
I’ll just get it from you
some other day.
Some other day?
Does that mean we’ll
see each other again?
Never mind. Wouldn’t
wanna bother you.
I’ll return it here
when you’re not around.
Auntie, I’ll get going now.
Visit me again, okay?
Yes, it was nice seeing you.
Go see her to the door.
- Bye, Auntie.
- Bye.
Are you gonna pass through?
- Excuse me.
- At least see her to the door.
She doesn’t want to, take care.
Right.
Auntie, bye.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Take care.
Bye, Auntie. Bye.
Go on now.
You miss her, huh?
Come on, Ma.
Have some snacks.
Ensaymada.
This is for you.
Arkin—
Your umbrella.
You can keep it.
I don’t need it anymore.
Wait.
Here.
Via?
Dan!
You’re here, too?
- May I?
- Yeah, of course.
How are you?
I just transferred today.
Wait, you’re back home already?
Just temporarily.
I’m part of the Airport Project in Bulacan.
Me, too.
Really?
- Yeah.
- That’s nice.
So we’ll actually be working together.
Before, we only worked together
on school projects.
Yeah. I’m looking forward to
working with you, Architect Diaz.
Same here, Architect Morales.
So, how’s Spain?
Will you go back there after the project?
Spain? Spain’s really good.
Spain’s great,
and my work there is really good too.
So, yes, I’ll go back there.
Uh...
How about you?
How are you both doing?
Um...
We’re okay, I guess?
Civil.
And I didn’t come here for him.
Clea’s still really beautiful, isn’t she?
Yeah. Of course. Clea’s still beautiful.
I’m the one working on her house.
Really?
Make sure to take me with you
next time you go to the site.
You’re still a huge fanboy
of Clea Aguilar, huh?
Clea? Clea Aguilar?
Oh my gosh, she’s always in the office!
Yeah, she’s really beautiful.
Are they still together,
Larkin Sanchez and her?
I’m not sure.
They’ve been keeping
a low profile for a long time.
Now they’re back in the news
because of a new movie.
Wasn’t there an issue with Larkin before?
Something about another girlfriend?
That was supposedly
just a childhood friend.
Come on, Via, let’s go.
Let’s grab some snacks.
On Saturday,
I’m going to Clea’s construction site.
Want to come?
I’ll bring the car.
Let’s go.
Larkin Sanchez and Clea Aguilar
are building a house together?
Aren’t you Clea’s architect?
Is this true, Via?
Is that Clea’s and Arkin’s house?
I don’t know.
All I know is that Clea is my client.
So what if it’s true?
How would you feel?
Nothing.
Are they really dating off-camera?
Mira, I don’t know.
Larkin and I aren’t that close anymore.
Why don’t you just ask him?
I know you’re still close to him.
Via,
how did you get through
what happened between you two?
Wasn’t it hard?
Do you regret it?
It was hard.
But you know, I don’t regret leaving.
What I regret is
trading our friendship just for that.
Just for that?
Your relationship wasn’t “just that,” Via.
Even if you didn’t ruin your friendship,
you were still in love with each other.
You can’t even call that friendship.
Wow.
You seem to know a lot about those things.
You got yourself a boyfriend?
Via, don’t just change
the topic like that.
But you changed the topic, too!
Whatever—
Why are you smiling?
No reason.
I used to be like that too.
Via! About the beach trip!
You’re still going, right?
Of course. Why wouldn’t I be?
- Well… Arkin’s coming.
- Huh? Why?
Sevi invited him.
And it’s kind of sad, too, since he hasn’t
hung out with the group in a long time.
Should I tell him not to come?
It’s fine, he’s part of the group anyway.
See you, Via. No backing out!
Love you!
Love you, too.
Via! Sorry,
can you pick me up at Arkin’s place?
Our music lesson might run late.
It’ll be hard to get a ride. Please?
Right there.
Hi, Auntie.
Hi.
Have some snacks.
The fried noodles are really good,
and the rice cakes too.
Thank you.
What about Aidan?
Didn’t he use the guitar?
Oh, when he got here he wanted
to play the piano first.
Now he’s upstairs playing the drums.
Wait, I have to go.
I have a meeting.
- Make sure you eat, okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- I’ll see you later.
Hurry up. I’m downstairs.
A glimpse of you in the middle
of the silence.
Listening to the pulse of what I’m feeling.
What was that?
You write songs now?
No. Nothing. It just came out.
Where’s Aidan?
He’s in the music room.
Are you ready to go for it again, Via?
I think music is really meant for you.
You should try it.
I’ll help you. Writing songs, producing…
Have you visited your mom again?
You should go see her.
I can go with you if you want.
I mean, I have some free time in the next—
Don’t interfere in my life, Larkin.
You’re no longer in a position to do that.
I’m sorry.
Stop forcing me into
your world, Larkin.
I’ve been broken for a long time, and I
never want to go back to your world again.
Via, come on.
I’m still not okay, Larkin.
And I’d rather live in a world where
I’m not happy, but I’m not sad either.
I will never put myself out there in front
of so many people again.
I’m more afraid now.
I’m more afraid now than before,
because of you.
So you have no right
to tell me to try,
when you’re the one who opened my wounds
and made them bleed.
Is that all I am to you, Via?
After all the years we were together,
is that the only memory I left you with?
Do you regret meeting me?
Maybe it really would’ve been better…
Maybe it would’ve been
better if we never met.
Wow.
I guess I was wrong about us.
Let’s not see each other again.
Ever.
Oh my gosh! I don’t know what to bring.
This brown swimsuit?
Or this red one?
It’s so pretty!
Or this black one?
Should I just bring them all?
You’re really bringing
three bikinis?
How many outfit changes
are you planning to do there?
Of course! I’ll need
them for photos.
Oh, this one’s mine.
I bought it in Thailand.
- See?
- Wow, that’s so nice. So fancy!
It looks good on you, Yanna.
You’ll look so sexy.
Via, what swimwear are
you gonna bring?
This one.
Just this.
Huh?
Why are you wearing
a rash guard?
No! That won’t look
good in pictures.
I don’t really have a bikini.
Didn’t Sam give you
a bikini as a gift?
Come on, guys, just let
Via wear what she wants.
Via, whatever you wear,
you’ll still look cute.
But if you wanna wear
the swimsuit I got for you,
take a photo, okay?
I wanna see!
Jeez, Sam.
Just come home already.
Seriously, before Via leaves,
this is gonna be the
last time we get to bond.
Yeah, when are you
planning to come back?
I don’t know yet.
Are the guys going, too?
Of course. They’re coming, too.
Good luck, then.
Babe, can you get
my other bikini, please?
Damn it!
Why are you saying
that out loud?
Let’s evict Yanna.
She’s being all cutesy again.
The bitter ones
should just stay quiet!
Bye!
Take care, guys.
Bye, guys!
Wait.
Oh my god.
It’s a beach.
Come on now!
Hi, guys!
You guys took so long.
- These are so heavy.
- Sevi, give that to me.
- I’ll carry my stuff.
- No. No, it’s okay.
Hey, bro, you carry this.
Make yourself useful.
I’m carrying a lot.
What are you talking about?
Did you forget that you were the one
who kept pushing me to come here?
You said she wouldn’t be here.
Why is she here?
If I had known,
I wouldn’t have come.
Well, it’s an honor
to have you with us.
- Exactly.
- Thank you.
I’m sorry.
I only had free time today.
I could use some vacation.
Damn! He’s speaking English!
I’ll twist that tongue of yours.
The way you speak,
we’d think you’re not crude.
- Why so fancy, bro?
- Why so fancy?
Screw you.
Girls, this is the
suite Hiro booked.
- One for you.
- Oh, thank you.
Yanna, please tell Hiro
thanks for treating us
to the accommodation, okay?
Of course. Oh my gosh.
Is ours the penthouse?
I’m with a celebrity, you know.
And as thanks,
let us borrow Avi for a bit.
We’ll take care of her.
You can think about that later.
Let’s just go now.
I’m dying to swim.
- Come on!
- Let’s go!
Let’s go, guys!
- Having fun yet?
- Wait for me.
Come on.
Ouch!
Is this okay?
What if it doesn’t suit me?
Send it to Sam.
You’re so pretty!
Is it okay?
- Is that the one Sam gave you?
- It’s nice.
Yes.
- You’re wearing it!
- It’s so pretty.
Oh, hold on.
Can we open it?
Let’s show the world.
Just one!
Just one, come on.
Just one, I promise.
- Isn’t it—
- Oh my gosh!
Doesn’t it look bad?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
It’s so pretty, it suits you.
I promise!
- You’re so pretty.
- It’s beautiful.
Right?
And Sam will be happy
when she sees that,
so we’re taking pictures later.
Yes!
Via, you’re beautiful. Seriously.
It really suits you, I swear.
I’m not talking crap.
You know what,
I bet an ex is
going to regret it later!
Actually.
- Right?
- For real.
- Now, come on! Let’s go.
- I can’t wait.
Let’s go.
Bro, this place is beautiful, huh?
Look at those rocks over there.
How did that get over there?
- Here, look at this.
- What if we go there?
- It’s Luna.
- Inflatable island.
- Now, that’s nice.
- Inflatable island?
Don’t post that!
Fine, post it!
Our friendship’s over.
Looks like you guys
are having so much fun.
We’ve been waiting for you guys.
- We’re here now.
- We’ve been waiting here for a while.
What do you want to do?
Hey! Me, too.
Put some on me!
Huh? Wait your turn.
Bro.
I’ll put sunscreen on you, bro.
Such an idiot.
Come on, don’t be shy!
Turn around.
You two are so sweet.
Wow, a celebrity’s
- putting sunscreen on me.
- They’re the newest love team.
Take a video of us.
Here you go.
- Let’s share it with everyone!
- A celebrity is putting sunscreen on me!
- There, done.
- We can totally blackmail him now.
- You go in front!
- Blackmail material.
Okay.
- Okay! Let’s just go there. Okay?
- That’s enough.
Oh, yeah. Let’s go!
- So we’ll have somewhere nice to go.
- Shall we?
- Let’s go.
- Come on.
My phone!
- What the heck?
- Wait!
I’m coming!
Shit!
So hot!
Of course!
Hey!
I just wanna smack you.
Here.
Try me!
Here’s your towel.
You’re really feeling yourself, huh?
Oh my gosh. Kierra,
stop hurting him.
He’s already heartbroken.
Hey! Screw you, Luna.
Be quiet.
- Screw you!
- Damn.
With a face like that,
you’re still single?
You deserve it!
Yes!
Jerks! Everyone who teases me
will have nightmares tonight.
Shit!
I know this guy.
What’s your name, bro?
You’re famous.
Can we take a picture?
I’m joining your fan club, okay?
Stop it, Luna.
Hey, watch what you post, okay?
Oh, come on.
Sevi, take a picture of him while
he’s asleep with his mouth wide-open.
- Right.
- Take a picture while he’s snoring.
- Full of drool too.
- Who are you?
Right. We’ll make money,
let’s sell it to the fans.
What’s your name?
Who are you?
Larkin Sanchez.
He’s so full of himself, damn.
Whatever!
Take a picture of me.
Let’s take a pic together.
Shit, why am I staring?
Good thing I’ve got my shades on.
This is fun.
Okay, that’s cute.
Thirst trap.
- Thirst trap.
- Find me a boyfriend here.
Hey!
Aren’t you both going
to talk to each other at least?
- No.
- Sevi’s so stubborn.
Hey, you’ve got a
booger in your nose.
Can you take it out?
I can’t see it.
- There, I’m posting it.
- Gross. Don’t just blow your nose.
We’re posting it.
Where’s your camera, boy?
Someone took—
- Where is it?
- You lost it, huh.
I’ll take that seat!
Ma’am, I’ll just grab
your juice, ma’am.
Okay, thank you.
Shit!
It’s hot! It's really hot today!
So hot, right? So hot.
- It’s so hot.
- Maybe you have a fever.
You shouldn’t have come.
Wow.
Wow, Sevi, maybe you
should just stay quiet
since you’re not
contributing anything here.
Wow! Did you even
contribute to the suite?
You haven’t contributed anything.
All you do is gossip!
Weak gossip at that.
Weak gossip, huh?
- You want to hear some gossip?
- Yeah, let’s hear it.
Well, your fifth anniversary—
Shit.
My makeup.
Hey, don’t fight.
See? Now Via’s mad
because you two are too loud.
These two are so annoying.
- You just talk too much!
- Jeez.
Luna?
- I’ll get the food.
- Damn it, Sev.
- Don’t start with me.
- Luna—
Luna!
It smells so good!
Sisig.
Don’t give food to Sevi,
he doesn’t deserve it.
But that’s actually my favorite.
Chicken and—
Takoyaki.
Yes.
Ma’am, here’s your juice.
- Okay.
- Here’s the juice.
Yes!
Sevi, can I have
some blue lemonade?
I’ll get it.
Put it down first.
Let go.
Me, too, please.
You can manage.
Thank you.
Give me some of that.
Give me some.
Whoever holds it first.
Wait!
Put it down.
I’ll get it.
I love this lunch!
Let go.
This lunch is giving.
I’ll have this.
- Sev.
- My turn.
You’re so stubborn, I’ll get it.
I don’t want to go there!
- Let’s go, bro.
- Yeah.
Hey, you two!
Come back here.
Are you both afraid of the sun?
- Let’s go.
- Hurry up!
There they are!
Sorry.
These two.
It’s Sevi’s fault.
- Via!
- Kino!
Kino!
Help!
It’s just seaweed.
I wonder how long
I’ll be hugged here.
So cute!
The bikini looks nice on you, Via.
Thanks, Sam.
Miss you, Sam!
Just come home already!
Arkin, you’re the only
one without a photo taken.
Come on, I’ll take a picture of you.
- No need.
- Yeah.
I’ll do it.
They might find out I’m with you.
Huh?
None of your die-hard
fans are here anyway.
I just don’t want to be noticed
in the photo, you’d all look bad.
Wow.
- Fine!
- Then don’t!
Come on.
Let’s see each other at the bonfire.
- Okay?
- All right.
Let’s go.
Don’t tag me in that, okay.
Why?
You’re so dramatic.
The fans might find out
that Via and I are together.
I just don’t want the same thing
from before to happen to Via again.
I know she’s not okay yet,
so I’m being careful.
Oh, right.
Okay. Sure, bro.
Sevi, can I have
some blue lemonade?
I’ll get it.
Do you regret meeting me?
Maybe it would’ve been
better if we never met.
I guess I was wrong about us.
I need to apologize.
What’s up, guys?
I’m wearing the new sunglasses
sent to me by Sunset Avenue today.
It’s so nice.
Wait for this to
come out the market.
Larkin.
Do you want me...
take a picture of you?
It’s okay. I’m done.
I just did a product post shoot.
Here.
No, it’s fine. Thanks.
Why do you have a hair tie?
A habit.
You always forget to bring one.
Why do you have one?
I always bring one
just in case you need it.
I’ll fix your hair.
Your hair’s a mess again.
Give it to me, I’ll tie it.
I’ll go ahead.
Can we talk?
Sure.
Let’s go somewhere.
Let’s go.
Um...
I’m sorry.
I didn't mean what
I said the other day
that maybe I shouldn’t have met you.
I just got carried
away by my emotions.
It’s okay, Via.
I understand.
Still—
I’m sorry.
And if it’s okay…
What?
Can we just...
act normal in front of our friends?
I feel like they’re uncomfortable.
With how we act
towards each other.
Okay, sure.
Also, I don’t know but—
are you mad at me?
I’m not mad.
You’re so cute.
Thanks.
Let’s go.
They might be looking for us.
- Cheers!
- Cheers, guys.
Are you okay?
I mean, I saw you guys talking.
Yes. We’re okay now.
That’s good.
Bro, sing for us.
Sing that song,
the “Golden Scenery”.
That one’s nice.
Come on, I haven’t
heard it live in a long time,
and it’s my favorite.
All right, since it’s
your favorite, I’ll sing it for you.
Really? For me?
I’ll sing it, but—
It will be a different
version of the song.
Shit. You might start
charging us later.
Of course, it will be
free for you guys.
You’re some of the first
people who listened to my music.
Go, Arkin! Let’s go!
Left thinking in the
midst of the chaos,
utterly bewildered by
the world I’m living in.
I can't tell if this is a dream,
as if my heart
was searching for its home.
In the daylight, I stand dazed.
Just staring at the
line where we once met.
I don't know anymore,
I get confused whenever
I look for you in…
A golden scenery
beneath the sky,
wishing you were with me.
As the wind blows,
along with the song, I long for you.
May my prayer be heard,
that you answer my plea.
With the orange sky above,
I won’t impose myself on you.
Wow.
- So beautiful.
- You’re really good.
- My best friend really is the best.
- Amazing. I got goosebumps.
- Your voice is really beautiful!
- Next level talent!
You really could be
an actor and a singer.
- Five stars from me.
- Wow.
Definitely, five stars.
And because of that, Via…
Please do the honors.
Yeah, Via.
What? I don’t even sing anymore.
I don’t want to.
Come on, Via!
Just this once.
We’re not strangers, you know.
Come on, Via.
- You can do it.
- Come on.
Please?
Pretty please?
- Take it already.
- Do I have a choice?
Yes!
- Is there a capo?
- Yeah.
Same spot?
Here.
I find myself smiling,
and you’re the reason why.
The colors of our world return anew.
I find myself smiling again.
Wow!
Your voice is so smooth.
Thank you.
Did they hear me?
We greeted them, too.
Hey, come with us
on the beach trip.
You know, it’s been so long
since you’ve hung out with us.
I was even thinking,
he doesn’t want to be
friends with us anymore.
Right.
- So dramatic.
- Right?
You guys are so dramatic.
You know I’m busy.
Busy?
Then why are you such a killjoy?
Is your name Kalix or something?
Huh?
Wow! Sevi, you’ve been
saying that for years
and you’re still not
done with that joke.
Move on already.
I am moving on.
Maybe next time, bro.
Via might feel awkward.
You know we’re not okay.
Uh... Via’s not coming, right?
Yeah, Via’s not coming because
I know she has somewhere to go.
- To the site in Bulacan.
- Yeah, in Bulacan she has—
- She has something to do.
- Yeah, she has—
something to do.
Yeah.
- So, come with us, bro.
- Come on.
- We miss you.
- Yeah.
Via’s not coming.
If Via’s not there, then okay.
- Right?
- Great!
Right?
Yay!
Ouch!
- Come on, let's go!
- Let's go!
- Let’s go.
- Come on.
- Hurry up!
- Come on, let's go!
I’m coming!
Ma'am, here's your juice.
Oh, yes.
It’s Via’s favorite.
Sevi, can I have
some blue lemonade?
I’ll get it.
Put it down first.
Let go.
Show your eyes a bit.
Perfect!
Don’t smile.
I can’t help it.
Don’t, this is supposed
to be a thirst trap photo.
There you go.
- Wow, bro.
- Ready?
It’s been so long
since I’ve been to the gym.
- What am I going to do with this?
- Don’t put your hand on your waist.
That’s it!
I think it’s time to get ripped.
You’re way more
ripped than me now.
Are you still working out there?
So cute.
Bro, I know I’m cute.
Moron. I’m not referring to you.
Huh?
Who’s cute then?
- I’m shy.
- My turn!
Just do it like
that and add this.
All right, it’s you.
Whatever makes you happy.
You’re so cute!
I just want to pinch you.
Thank you.
So cute!
Move over. One more.
- I’m shy. I feel embarrassed.
- One, two, three—
There, just a candid shot.
You should add
a little something—
Bro, the sand here is so nice.
Ah, bro, yeah.
Totally. It’s nice.
Hey, you two!
Come back here.
Are you both afraid of the sun?
- Let’s go!
- Come on!
How’s the movie?
That movie was so good.
You and Clea were so cute together.
You really like her, huh?
Take this before lunch, don’t skip meals!
- Kino
Via, Arkin brought so much food.
I’ll get your food ready.
Take this.
Drink water all the time
so you don’t get dehydrated,
and bring an umbrella so
you won’t get wet if it rains.
Eat already, you’re so stubborn.
You’re the one being stubborn.
I’m so tired from work,
and you’re still bothering me.
You’re so relentless.
Here, take this.