♪ Get your motor runnin'
♪ Head out on the highway
♪ Lookin' for adventure
♪ And whatever comes our way
When your
kitty's left the city.
When your moose is on the loose.
When your cow has said ciao,
you need me.
My friends call me-
Wait, I don't have friends.
I call me "Hitpig."
♪ Born to be wild
You see,
I was raised by
the legendary pet bounty
hunter, Big Bertha,
and I was her super
cool sidekick.
You know, like Batman
and Robin, Ben and Jerry,
Aquaman and whoever the heck
Aquaman's sidekick was.
Fish? No. Doesn't matter.
We caught cats, hamsters,
snakes, all that for money.
You get the idea.
She taught me everything
I needed to know
about the bounty biz.
How to dress.
I mean, yeah,
she got this at an
American Girl store, but..
She trained me how to
be half Dr. Doolittle,
half James Bond,
half Mandalorian.
And yes, I know
that's three halves.
She wasn't great at math.
And she taught me
how to make an omelet
without breaking any eggs,
which is impossible.
So I guess it was a metaphor,
but it doesn't matter.
She was a good business woman.
- This business can
be very rewarding.
Then one day a call
came in, Tiny the Lizard,
a thousand bucks,
which seemed high for a lizard.
- It's just an easy peasy,
tiny lizard.
I'll be right back.
Here, Tiny, Tiny, Tiny.
Turns out
Tiny wasn't so tiny.
Tiny was a crocodile.
Just like that, Bertha was gone.
♪ Start wearing purple,
wearing purple ♪
♪ Start wearing
purple for me now ♪
- All right, here we go!
Mr. Secretary wants
us to run a test.
Wakey, winky,
stinky tubes skunk.
- Call HR! My coworkers
are trying to kill me!
- Gotcha! Right this way.
- Not this again, please!
- You know the drill.
Skedaddle down the tube
to the plutonium room.
Do not touch the glowy thing!
Then you come back and we
test your radiation levels.
Pieces of cake. Remember,
do not touch the glowy thing!
- Do not touch the glowy thing?
Honey, that's my
ticket outta here!
Go left!
I love that game.
I knew I
shouldn't have traded shifts
with the hamster!
- Bullseye!
Do not touch the glowy thing!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Hey, I feel all tingly
and now I'm glowing pink?
Ooh, new look. Who dis?
- Bad tube skunk!
- Uh, pole cat, not tube skunk!
Woo-hoo, freedom!
- Oh, hello. Oh, everything's
fine, Mr. Secretary.
How's the radiation level?
Oh, fine.
What's up?
What's up? What's up?
Oh! It's big!
- Freedom!
Woo-hoo, hello world!
Here I come.
I got a glowing bum,
full of plutonium!
What?
Party's over,
pole cat.
- Hey! Hot truffles, not me!
You need therapy!
Where's your humanity, pig?
Oink.
- Wow! Ex-squeeze me.
I'm not quite sure
what happened there.
- Whoa. Some guys cut
the cheese, but you, brother,
you destroy the cheese.
You cut the cheese, then you
go find the cheese's family,
and then you cut them.
- Peter Parker gets
radiation poisoning
and shoots webs
out of his wrist.
Me, apparently I shoot
nukes out of my-
- Hey, be careful
with that thing.
- Look, your cousin Porky.
Adios, cocktail fake.
- Not so fast, Radiation Rump.
I had it
on selfie mode.
- That's nasty.
- Consider yourself... hit.
Whoa. What was that?
That was terrible.
Lemme try that again.
Consider yourself hit.
Boom! Nailed it!
The newest
show in Vegas,
featuring Pickles
the dancing elephant
will be out of this world,
so says the Leapin'
Lord of the Leotard.
He has staged some of
the worst animal acts ever.
He trained his three
ton elephant Pickles
to leap into his arms,
breaking every bone in his body.
After two years in the hospital,
he trained Pickles
to leap into the arms
of his poodle.
A far worse idea.
The Leapin' Lord squandered
his family's reputation
and fortune, and they
have disowned him.
Undeterred, the Leapin' Lord
guarantees
no one will walk
out of this show.
We saw hope Pickles
will be okay.
It's showtime!
Dancers, take positions!
- And now, Pickle the Elephant!
Psst. That's your cue,
Poodles.
- Where's the motivational
coach?
Okay, enough with the dancing.
Cast your eyes to the heavens.
The one and only me!
People of the earth,
I present to you
the otherworldly
Leapin' Lord of the Leotard!
Drum roll.
Here we go!
Whoa.
Oh, blast you, Pickles!
You have one job!
Why didn't you catch me?
Nevermind.
Wait until you see what
I have planned for us
opening night!
I will reach for the stars
and soar to heights
never before soared!
I'll fly. I'll glide.
I'll float and swoop
and flit and whoosh.
And give gravity what
it's given me, contempt.
- A billion dollar dynasty
flushed down a crapper
by the Leapin' Lord
of the Lunatics.
- Hey, six generations
of animal acts
are not ending with me!
Okay, rehearsals over!
Everyone out!
♪ I'm a real wild one,
wild one ♪
♪ Wild one, wild one
♪ Well, I'm just out of school
♪ Like I'm real, real cool
♪ Gotta dance like a fool
♪ Got the message that
I gotta be a wild one ♪
♪ Oh yeah, I'm a wild one
♪ Gonna break it loose
♪ Gonna keep being a wild one
♪ 'Cause baby,
I'm a real wild child ♪
Escaped
pet alert. Escaped pet alert.
Hey, Gordon Hamsy. Shall I
keep saying escaped pet alert?
- Gordon Hamsy. I get it.
'Cause I'm a pig that cooks.
That's the best you got, huh?
Chef Boar RD.
Sty Fieri. Wolfgang Pig.
- Hilarious.
Who says computers
can't be funny? Not me.
Oh wait, yeah. No, it is me.
I say computers can't be funny.
Zoo surveillance
caught an animal rights
activist freeing the koala.
- Leticia.
Our paths cross again.
Catch van to
the land down under.
We'll check the outback,
the front back,
the inside out,
and the upside down.
Activate propulsion boosters.
Activated.
- Weapons systems online.
Locked and loaded.
- And pump up the rock 'n roll.
- Greatness is so close
I can smell it, Pickles.
The eyes of too many
lords and ladies
are looking down on me!
They said I didn't fit in.
That I was an untalented,
tubby failure.
That I'll never
leap into anything
but an all you can
eat buffet table.
And while I do love
a complimentary Vegas buffet,
I mean, who doesn't?
I'll show them
what I'm capable of!
Mummy and Daddy
dazzled audiences,
riding lions through
hoops of fire.
Grandmama was blasted
from a howitzer cannon
over a swimming pool
filled with hungry sharks.
My dearest uncle
was a bullfighter.
And not with a red cape.
He fought them with his fists.
You see, to have the next
great animal act is my destiny!
Ugh, elephant snot.
I lock you up because
I love you so much.
I mean, I don't know what I'd do
if anything ever happened
to you, Pickley-poo.
Who would catch me then?
Oh, get real, Alligator Arms.
I know you're a crocodile.
It's just a figure of speech.
Now eat your lunch.
Open it yourself.
I gave her your dog food.
You buggies missed
your cue on stage,
and I know you're laughing
at me behind my back.
I just can't prove it yet.
No food for you!
- Hey, don't worry, guys.
I'm gonna get us out of here.
You'll be free soon and I..
I can find my family.
Door ajar.
Door closed.
Hooray. You did it.
- Don't you have a stealth mode
or a shut up mode or something?
Croc? Ugh.
No guns, no nuns, no lil' ones.
Any other nuns here?
- Hey, keep an eye on that,
would you, Sister?
All right, koala. Where are you?
Here, koala, koala, koala.
Bingo, Dingo.
- Thought I smelled bacon.
- Let's go, koala.
- Not going back there, Hitpig.
- You escaped.
- I had to escape!
Do you know who comes
to petting zoos?
- Kids?
- Yeah, kids.
Filthy, slimy,
sticky, smelly kids.
They wipe their snotty noses,
then pet me with
those same tiny hands.
They're disgusting!
- Ah, you got a little something
stuck to the back of your head.
Whoa.
That's gonna leave a bald spot.
- For the love of goon bag.
- Cute little Sheila.
- If you pet the fur,
I'll drop kick you to-
Whoop whoop!
Oh, boy.
- I never asked for this
adorable face, Hitpig!
I don't wanna be cute.
I'm not cute.
Hey!
- Don't take me back!
- Hey, I got a job to do.
- Get another job.
- Look, this is the only
job I know how to do.
- Animals are meant to be free.
- Get a taste of my
world famous pork chop.
Hiya! Ow!
Your, uh, shoe's untied.
That's right.
Go way, way, way,
all the way home.
Ah, son of a beach nut.
- Thank you, Sister.
You are one bad habit.
I know. Forgive me.
- Thanks, mate. $10,000 in dues.
- I hope someone turns you into
a ham steak one day, Hitpig.
Put a little ring
of pineapple on you
and stab you with a fork!
- Thanks, mate.
- This is no life for you all.
I wish I could free you.
"Famous Panda walks off
popular kung fu set,
says eight films is enough."
Oh man, I liked those films.
"Animal Rights activist,
Leticia Dos Anjos
frees tigers
for Las Vegas show."
Oh man, I liked that show too.
I don't get it.
Wait a minute.
You want me to call
that critter liver,
Leticia, to free you.
Brilliant!
By golly, I've never done
anything important in my life.
That changes today!
- We're almost free.
I can feel it.
Hey,
you're looking good.
A super cock-doodle-doo!
Super Rooster!
- Super cock-doodle-doo!
Oh, man.
Now that is a catchphrase.
Ah, you know what? Maybe I could
try something like that.
You know, like a super
oinkety-boinkety-boink!
Ah, who asked you, Henry?
- Welcome to
"King Chef For A Day,"
the show where our
contestants have five minutes
to make a delicious meal from
the ingredients we provide.
- Yeah, boy! Oh, another
great catch phrase.
You know,
I could win that.
When pigs fly.
- Oh, come on. A pig
can dream, can't he?
Incoming call. Incoming call.
- Oh, will you leave
me alone, Morticia?
- It's Leticia.
And are you proud of yourself
for messing up all those
poor animals' lives?
Locking them away like
they were criminals?
- Yeah, 'cause they escaped!
- They should never have
been captured at all.
- Hey, it's just business.
You set 'em free,
I bring 'em home.
- You're such a pig. And that's
all the time I needed.
- Needed for what?
- Gain access to your
bank account and take
three, two, one,
all your money, sucker.
- What?
No, no! No, no, no, no, no, no!
Thank you
for your donation.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- It's dirty money and it
needs to be used for good.
- I'm good, I'm super good.
I'm so good.
- I'm off to free an elephant.
Thanks for the money.
Ciao.
Come on!
Hey.
Did someone call for a rescue?
Not sure I can
locate your family,
but I can get you home to India.
- Anywhere is better than here.
- Don't worry, poodles.
I'll be back for you guys soon.
Woo-hoo,
I'm free! I'm going home!
Suppertime!
But not for you.
What the elephant?
Someone pilfered Pickles!
Who steals elephants?
I mean, besides me.
- Hitpig. Lost your dog?
You called the right hog.
How can I help you?
- Aha, bounty hunter.
I hear you're the best.
At least that's what
it says in your ad.
- Who are you?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe I'm only the Leapin'
Lord of the Leotard!
- And I'm Baron
of the Boxer Shorts.
What'd you lose?
- My dance partner!
Somebody stole her!
- Wrong number, pal.
Sounds like you
need a dating app.
She's an elephant.
- Leticia.
- No, Pickles.
I'm launching my show
in Vegas this weekend.
A guaranteed blast.
I'll be leaping,
I'm the Leapin' Lord after all,
but you knew that.
Pickles is the only
one who can catch me.
I have to be caught!
So catch her!
- Hey, don't worry,
I'll catch her,
but you know,
I charge by the pound,
so I'm gonna need you to make
me an offer I can't refuse.
- One million bucks.
- Whoa, that's about
a hundred times
more than I was
thinking, so yes.
- So we have a deal, Hitpig.
Bring her back to me.
- Woo! Looks like this little
piggy is back in business.
- Who's got egg
on their face now?
Cock-a-doodley-doo!
Super Rooster!
That's something you
don't see every day.
We'll be
landing in London momentarily,
on our way to India.
Unfortunately, we have to stop
our in-flight entertainment.
I know, I love
"Super Rooster" too.
Downloading all
train, plane,
and truck manifests.
- All right,
where are you big girl?
Cargo,
one dog, 62 cats. Poor dog.
- No, no, no.
Okay, train.
A baboon, two rabbits.
Check that, two rabbits
now with 27 bunnies.
- No. Vegas to India,
layover in London.
Cargo four dogs,
two cats, and one elephant.
- Ah, there you are!
My pachyderm payday.
Target acquired.
Off to jolly old England.
- Ooh, some sort of elephant
party going on there.
Be right back!
I'm gonna scope this out.
After party with my peeps.
Wow, wide load coming through.
I'll be there in a minute.
Sorry about that.
- We're so fired.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Nice.
Ooh, that's nice.
Loving the new elephant
fashions, so exciting!
Pickles, you deserve a new look.
Elephant pheromones detected.
Warning, warning.
No parking zone.
Have I ever
gotten you towed?
Wow.
I'm gonna blame that
on poor craftsmanship.
- Aha, Pickle prints.
Free?
Memory is yours.
Your better recollection
is pure perfection,
'cause an elephant never,
'cause an elephant never...
Line!
- Forgets!
- Oh, yeah.
- Pickles, you devilish
smoke show.
- Like shooting
fish in a barrel.
Really fat fish.
- As queen of the elephants,
it is I who wears the pants.
So as your queen,
I command you all to dance!
- No, wait!
- Did someone say dance?
- Stop that elephant!
Hey, hey, Pickles!
♪ I know you can't control
yourself any longer ♪
- This is exactly what
I was not expecting,
but I've always wanted
to dance with other elephants!
♪ Come on, shake your
body, baby do that funk ♪
♪ I know you can't control
yourself any longer ♪
♪ Feel the rhythm of
the music getting stronger ♪
- Consider yourself hit.
Ah, dang it.
- Come here, you weird
looking elephant.
I just wanna hug you
and never stop.
Oh, going up.
That tickles.
No, no, no, no!
- Yes!
- Wow. There's so much.
There's so much world,
and my family is out there.
- Well, well, well.
- No more cages for me.
Ever!
Are you...
Ouch!
- Are you a little elephant?
- Elephant? No, I'm a pig.
A pig-my elephant.
Yeah, no, you're right. Yeah,
no, a pigmy elephant, yes.
Hey, we're twinsies.
I feel like I'm
looking in a mirror.
- Whoa. We're a perfect fit.
I know, it's like we're
made for each other.
What happened
to your nose?
- Well, you know,
I was at the back of the line
when they were
passing out trunks.
I'm a little sensitive about it.
- Ugh, you're right.
That was rude.
Let's start over.
I'm Pickles.
- I'm Hitpig.
Which is short
for Hit Pigmy Elephant.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
You know,
you missed your flight!
- Oh, are you
friends with Leticia?
Leticia? I mean, yes.
Yes, Leticia and I are
great friends, actually.
Yeah, no, she had
to go do a, you know,
rescue a porpoise
or something, I don't know.
She asked me to help, so.
- Leticia was
taking me to India.
India?
- Hey, we're sliding, Hitpig.
- No kidding!
Give me my catch gun.
I love slides.
Hold on.
- They towed my van!
Ah, come on!
Think I just cracked
a baby back rib.
- Whoa.
That was fun. Let's do it again.
- And now my gun is broken?
What else could go wrong? Oh!
How do you sneak onto
a plane with an elephant?
- Why are we dressed like this?
- Subterfuge.
- Oh. I don't know French.
- What do you mean check
the last and found?
It's a two ton elephant.
- All right, try not to call
attention to yourself.
- Excuse me!
- Emotional support,
you know, dog.
I am a work in progress.
It's a very fancy hairdryer.
It's from Europe.
- Of course it is, ma'am.
Lip balm.
- Leapin' Lord here.
- Hey, your package is shipping
overnight air to Las Vegas.
- Goodie.
This show is going to rocket me
to stardom, Hitpig.
Her understudy,
well, let's just say
it's a little like
putting lipstick on a pig.
So don't let me down.
Sorry, cutie.
Help! Save me,
Super Rooster!
Look up in the sky!
It's Super rooster.
- Super cock-a-doodley-doo!
- Ah, how this guy never
won an Oscar is beyond me.
You know, politics.
- Hey, would you mind
letting me scooch by?
I've gotta tinkle.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
By the way, could you
ask the stewardess
for a couple dozen more
bags of those peanuts?
They roasted them in honey!
I mean, what?
Yikes. That little toilet is not
designed for what I have to do,
but girls gotta do
what a girl's gotta do.
Ow!
Right in the ham hocks.
Tranquilizer dart? Leticia.
- That dress really brings
out the rump in your roast.
- Hey, who does your makeup?
Cirque du Soleil?
- Listen, Hitpig.
I should be taken seriously.
- For what?
- Stealing back stolen
mooses and hippopotamuses.
- And rhinoceros.
- Plus elephants!
- Elephant? Never!
- Oh.
Okay, so here's
the big girl bathroom.
- No!
- Okay, okay.
This is not what I thought
would be behind that door.
Grab my tail!
- Pickles! I'll pull you in!
Her tights are coming off!
You've gotta let the pig go!
- Why would I let
your friend go?
- He's not my friend!
I can be!
No!
Eat your
heart out, Dumbo!
- No, he can actually fly!
We're toast. We're toast.
- You'll think of something.
- You're right.
I'm thinking you're about to see
how the sausages are made.
Ow, ow, ow. Ow!
- Hey, I knew you'd
think of something.
It's called flying by the seat
of your pants.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please excuse
the flight turbulence.
Jackpot.
Ugh.
- Oh, well, that
worked out nicely.
Yay! There's more.
Ow.
Now I know what Spam feels like.
So really, that emergency
exit looked like a toilet?
We could have been killed!
- To be fair,
it was an emergency.
- How were you so sure that
I would think of something?
- Because I trust you.
- Yeah, all right,
well, you shouldn't.
- But we're friends now.
- What?
No, I don't have friends.
Not since Bertha.
- Who's Bertha?
- Doesn't matter.
We're hosed, okay?
I'm way off course.
- To India?
- Yeah, to bringing
you home, yeah.
But we need wheels.
All I see is junk.
- You have to free your mind!
It's all caged up.
And trust me, I know cages.
Hey, what about this?
Catch!
- Will you stop
throwing junk at me?
- Hi, little friend.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Hey!
♪ You're a real tough
cookie with a long history ♪
♪ For breaking little
hearts like the one in me ♪
♪ That's okay,
let's see how you do it ♪
♪ Put up your dukes,
let's get down to it ♪
♪ Hit me with your best shot
♪ Come on, hit me
with your best shot ♪
♪ Hit me with your best shot
♪ Why don't you hit me
with your best shot ♪
♪ Hit me with your best shot
♪ Fire away
- Bye, little friend!
- Catch you later, Fuzzball.
All right,
sit down and buckle up.
We got a long way to go.
Oh!
- Do you know any show tunes?
- Do I look like
I know show tunes?
♪ Clang, clang, clang
went the trolley ♪
♪ Ding, ding
Whoopsie. Oh, a button.
See you later.
Oh, you're back!
Oopsie.
Sorry about that.
Look, another button. Woo!
So many buttons and levers.
So fun!
Isn't today like
a dream come true?
- Look, I don't have
time for silly questions.
- Come on.
You must have a dream.
- Fine, sure.
To have a million dollars.
- And what would you do with it?
- I don't know. Retire.
- And then?
- I don't know. I'd cook.
- Okay.
You dream of being a chef.
- Me, a chef?
- It's pretty dumb, right?
- No!
No?
Look, an elephant!
Pickles, stop!
There are no words
for how I feel right now.
- Just trying
to get a closer look!
- Pickles!
- Get back in the UFO!
- Coming down.
Whoa!
An octopus and a chicken!
There are no words
for how I feel right now.
- Pickles! Do not
push or pull anything!
- Push and pull everything,
you said? Okay.
- No! I'll get ya!
♪ Now baby I'm sure ♪
- I can't believe they had
a pigmy elephant balloon.
Stay there!
♪ I just can't
wait 'til the day ♪
Croc!
- Ooh, that's fun. I wanna try!
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna get you! Whee!
Whee!
Just the most fun ever!
♪ I'm walking on sunshine
- No! No, no, no, no, no!
- Gotcha!
- Ow.
- I like your style.
You know, you don't show it,
but you know how to have fun.
- This is a disaster.
- If this is a disaster,
disasters are wonderful!
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Everything.
- Anything to do with Leticia
saying she's not your friend?
- Yeah, a little
to do with that, yeah.
- I figured.
Well, you're both
very nice to fight over
who gets to take me
back to India.
You know, it makes me
feel kind of special.
- Yeah.
Well.
- I wonder what it'll be like.
- What?
- Family.
I left when I was a baby.
- Me, too.
I haven't
seen my family in years.
- Same here.
- The Leapin' Lord wanted
a cute little elephant
for his show, and he found me.
My parents tried
to stop him, but they..
I've been locked in
a cage ever since.
Until you guys rescued me.
And now, wow.
Now I've never felt more free.
All thanks to you.
Is that Orion's butt?
Oh,
I think you mean belt.
- Pretty sure it's his butt.
India has a Golden Gate Bridge?
- Wait, what?
- Ah!
We overshot home a smidge.
Going down!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Ow, ouch!
Ow!
My hand!
- Whoa. That was
our next contestant.
- Help me.
- You're wounded. Medic!
I guess you'll have to do.
- Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, I couldn't.
No, I'm in a hurry
and I need to-
- Get dressed.
We're about to go live.
- Live? Wait, wait,
hold on, what is this?
- Is this a show?
- Stay in!
"King Chef For A Day?"
How about that?
- This is it!
- This is your chance!
- What?
- Come here!
- We need to get going.
- Pump the brakes!
This is your dream come true.
- Don't be silly.
- I'm not silly.
Dreams are what give us hope.
You dream to cook, so cook.
- But I mean, I hurt my hand
when that 15 ton beam
fell on it, okay?
I can't!
- But we can.
- Why are you helping me?
- That's what friends are for!
I'm helping you, just like
you're helping me
find my family.
- Oh, boy. Look, Pickles, I-
- Welcome to
"King Chef For A Day!"
The show where our
contestants have five minutes
to make a delicious meal from
the ingredients we provide.
The only rule is...
- Use every ingredient!
- And tonight's contestant
literally just dropped in.
Give it up for Hitpig!
Yeah, boy.
- They're waiting for you!
Hitpig! Hitpig!
Higher.
Higher! Higher!
- Hitpig! Yeah, boy.
- Hitpig?
Where's my stolen elephant?
He doesn't have
time to cook on TV!
He needs to bring
my Pickles back to me!
- Hey, watch the trunk!
- Hey!
Looks like it's omelet time!
- Showtime, Hitpig! We got this.
- Go!
- Hand me the eggs.
Oh!
Whoopsie!
Egg on your face.
- Follow my rhythm!
Whisk, stir, whisk.
Chop, slice, dice.
There we go.
- And now,
today's mystery ingredient.
Oh, hi.
How's things?
- You can't cook him!
- All right, put him in the pot.
- He's got eyeballs! No!
He's one of us!
Don't hurt him!
- No, no, no, no!
- What?
- You can't boil him!
He has feelings!
- And a name! Louie!
I don't wanna die!
- You save animals!
That's your thing, right?
- Well, I..
Ow!
- Free Louie!
- Get that? Free Louie.
Free Louie!
- Oh, come on.
Throw the lobster in!
- Make love, not lobster!
♪ Rock lobster
- Stop!
Oh, no, look out!
- May I, Louie?
- They grow back, huh?
Don't they?
- Every ingredient!
Taste it! Taste it!
- This is a dream come true.
Thank you.
- Well, so is you rescuing me.
- Pickles, no, I mean,
there's...
There's no reason to thank me.
You know, for real.
There is no reason to thank me.
Weapon systems online.
Ow. What is going on?
Target obliterated.
- Whoops!
Autopilot to catch gun
coordinates engaged.
Ooh.
- Yes!
So you're in San Francisco?
I'm coming, Pickles.
- Hey.
- Hello?
- Listen, Porky McPorkFace.
You overshot the handoff
by 400 miles.
It seems you've lost your way.
- No, I'm finding it actually.
- Well, I'm coming
for my dance partner.
She and I will soar
to heights never before seen.
Don't move.
All right, move.
Move, move, move, move, move.
- Where are we going?
- Anywhere but here.
- Well, how about India?
- Yeah, okay, look,
we need to talk about that.
I, I need to come
clean about something.
- Clean? I get it.
- What, you do?
- Oh, always happens
after several months, yep.
I need a bucket.
- Wait, what?
- You need one of those.
- A bathtub? Ooh, nice!
- I'm not really who you,
well, who you think I am.
I mean, being Hitpig isn't
necessarily a good thing.
You know,
it's actually impressive
how much trouble she can cause
in less than two seconds.
- Yeah.
Warm water
feels pretty good.
- Oh, sure, sure.
That's how it always starts!
Then comes screaming,
and then the lemon butter,
and then them
nut cracker things!
I don't even have nuts!
- Hey, Pickles, we gotta go!
People that come home
to an elephant in their tub
tend to get a little upset!
I'm coming!
- Well, would you hurry
before someone finds us?
- Ooh, that tickles.
- Oh, okay, what am I gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
What am we gonna do?
Okay, let's think here.
All right, this couch is comfy.
Didn't sleep too well on
the old balloon last night.
You know, I just, one minute
to think what to do.
And, you know,
maybe if I close my eyes,
it'll all come to me.
The answers will just
come right to me.
Bertha?
What?
How have you been?
- Dead, kid. I've been dead.
- Yeah, no,
I've been better too.
- Oh, no.
What's wrong, little buddy?
- Well, for one thing,
someone stole all my money.
- Here, try this.
And the van got towed.
- You lost your money, your van.
- And my catch gun.
- Well, at least you
haven't lost your way.
- Well, I mean, you know,
that's the thing.
I'm supposed to take this
elephant back to her owner.
You know, she's worth
a million bucks.
- Wow. Prices have
really gone up.
- Yeah, yeah.
Anyways, she doesn't
want to go back.
Frankly, I don't blame her.
But the reward
is just so big, I..
- We never did this
for the reward.
- But you said our business
was very rewarding.
- Oh, little buddy. Because
of all the animals we helped.
- But the last one ate you.
- Yeah, you win some,
you lose some.
Hey, little buddy.
A long time ago
I got the call to return
an escaped piglet
to a bacon farm.
He was so scared and so cute.
I knew I couldn't
return him, so I didn't.
And over time,
we became best friends.
You, Hitpig.
You were my greatest reward.
Now time to eat.
- Lucky for me,
it's only a dream.
Wakey-wakey.
- Ow!
- We're in a lake-y.
- Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no.
What happened?
- Sprung a leaky.
- Pickles! Pickles,
what did you do?
- Got a bathtub
stuck to my butt.
Did you have a nice nap?
- Okay, we gotta go up.
All right, just swim.
I thought elephants could swim.
- Not if they don't have
a mom to teach them.
- Okay, can you reach it?
- No. But I think you can.
- What are you doing?
No! Come on!
Pickles.
We can do it! You're so close.
No, no, no, no, no! Pickles.
Pickles!
No! No, no, no, no, no, no. No.
Pickles, wake up!
- Hello, Pickles.
Ready to go home?
Come on now. Up, up.
Oh, and you, Hitpig. You had me
worried there for a moment.
I suppose I should deduct
some money for the delay
and change of drop off location.
But I want to support
your business,
returning escaped
animals to their owners.
- What? No, no, no, no, no.
He's not returning me to you.
He's my friend!
You're my friend, right?
- Yes. Yes, no, now I am.
I mean now I want to be.
I wasn't bringing
you home to India.
I was bringing you to,
well, to him.
- Let's go, Pickles.
Our show launches
in less than four hours.
- Deals off, Leapin' Lord.
Take your money back.
Her home is in India,
not in Vegas.
And certainly not with you.
- I'm not going
with either of you.
- You'll get in
your cage right now.
Stop!
- Get your hands off her!
- Fluffy, a little help, please.
- Oh.
Fluffy's a croc!
- Well, that was easy.
Fluffy, teach pickles a lesson.
Don't ever run away again!
Come on, Fluffy.
- Ow!
That's enough!
- I think not.
- That last slap felt good.
- You did all that for a salad?
This lettuce
don't even taste good!
- Okay, look, you were right,
I was wrong.
- Where's Pickles?
- The Leaping Lord took her.
- He abuses her!
- I know.
And I need to save her.
- Really? Looks like you
handed her over and got paid.
- It's not like that, okay?
I tried to stop him, but-
Give me my van.
- We're going with you.
- Who's we?
- Say hello to my
little friends.
- Surprise, swine!
- Hitpig.
- Couldn't help it.
Had to free them, too.
- Brazilian chicks rock!
- I'm gonna drop kick your
ham hocks, bounty hunter.
- You know what?
I probably deserved that.
- Take that! Hiya!
- Ow. Okay, are you done?
Got it outta your system now?
No, no, no, no.
Not that. Not, no.
That, I don't deserve.
When I said get it out of your
system, I didn't mean that.
- That's not even just,
he tried to boil me alive.
- Ow!
- By the way,
my favorite food is bacon.
- Are we even yet?
- Not even close.
But we feel a lot better.
- Shall we go get Pickles?
- Yeah. Let's go
rescue an elephant.
- Let's roll.
- You better not mean
lobster roll, sister.
- I like this sassy crustacean.
- Move over.
- I'm driving.
You got a plan,
pork chop?
- That depends.
How do you define plan?
♪ Pop, pop, pop music
♪ Get down
- Look at that crowd, Fluffy!
Clamoring to see me!
Yes, I know I'm paying
them a hundred bucks each,
plus a glow stick,
but a crowd's a crowd.
Fluffy, the show
is about to start
and you forgot to comb
your eyebrows, again.
Oh, nevermind. Tonight we soar!
- All right.
And that is why Taylor Swift
would be a great president.
Now anybody got any ideas
how to save Pickles?
I'm just joking, no.
Using a combination
of intelligence,
counterintelligence,
and counter counterintelligence,
we will have
acquired our target.
Oh whoa, and to make
matters worse,
there's a crocodile and he's
gonna try and eat all of us.
He might even get one of us.
- Crocodiles?
I thought little pigs
and was scared
of big bad wolves.
- Okay, first off,
I'm not a little pig.
I'm a perfectly
average sized pig.
Secondly, the three
little pigs were not
scared of the big
bad wolf, okay?
Remember the tune?
That was their whole thing.
They didn't even know who's
afraid of the big bad wolf.
- Well, it just seems like
a lot of work to nab a pickle.
- Not a pickle.
Pickles the elephant.
- Oh, we going
to need a better team.
No offense, losers.
- I already called for backup.
- Who?
- Take a look up in the sky.
- Is that a bird?
- Is that a cat?
- Oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness.
It's Super Rooster!
- Super cock-a-doodley-doo!
A super
cock-a-doodley-doo to you.
And you and you.
Super Rooster!
- Well, you know,
I'm not really a hero.
I just play one in cartoons.
But the producers
have permanently sewn
the suit to my body, so I get
to fly around whenever I want.
- Thank you for coming.
And look, I gotta just
get this outta the way.
I'm your biggest fan.
You know, "Nuggets of Glory."
Oh, for me, honestly,
your best work.
- No need to thank me.
I gotta say, if this is really
about saving an elephant,
eh, I'm in.
Plus, you know, you said
something about a million bucks.
- You're giving him
all your money?
- Well, not all of it, no.
Louie ate a bunch of it.
I think he thinks it's salad.
- I've never been more regular.
- I'll take almost any
amount at this point.
You know, my third wife
ran off with a penguin.
You know, he's a sharp dresser,
I must say,
but the whole split
has cost me a bundle!
Anyways, should we get the
autographs outta the way, huh?
- Thanks, mate.
- Can I touch your wattle?
- All right guys, come on.
Focus on the plan.
But could you sign one more?
It's to my nephew.
- Yeah, what's his name?
- My, his name, yeah. Hitpig.
- All right. What's the plan?
- We're winging it. Let's go!
- Time to kick butt!
- We're outta here!
- Let's cock-a-doodley-doo!
- Ladies and gentlemen, prepare
to have your minds blown.
Blown like they have
never been blown before.
And now let
the mind blowing begin!
Hello, dance fans!
The Leapin' Lord welcomes you.
It's the moment
I've been waiting for.
- We're coming for you, Pickles!
- Is this part of the plan?
- Why would a theater
have steel doors?
- Well, mission
not accomplished.
- Countdown?
Our show launches
in less than four hours.
Soar to heights
never before soared.
A guaranteed blast.
It's going to rocket me
to stardom.
Oh, no.
- Fasten your seatbelts!
This show is going
to be out of this world!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
- This isn't a theater,
it's a rocket.
- Say what?
- He's totally nuts! Run!
- Five, four, three, two, one.
Blast off!
- They're all gonna die!
- Not on my watch.
- And how do we stop a rocket?
Rocket systems engage.
- Why did I have to ask?
You might
wanna hold on.
This is great.
- I need more power!
- On it!
This is why I get paid
the big bucks, baby.
Cock-a-doodley-doo!
- I'll soar! I'll fly!
I'll glide.
I'll float and swoop
and flit and whoosh.
I'll give gravity
what it's given me!
Contempt.
Warning, critical power loss.
- We're losing them!
- The catch van's
boosters failed.
- Okay, okay!
Step aside, people.
It's my time to shine.
A tube, please.
Now hand me that chimichanga.
Fire in the hole!
- Oh, goody!
It's starting!
♪ From the floors of Tokyo
- Back off, Fluffy.
This is my special moment.
The Leapin' Lord of the Leotard
and Pickles the Dancing Elephant
will be the greatest
show off Earth!
♪ I'm dancing with myself
- Hit the gas!
- 10-4, good buddy.
♪ Dancing with myself
♪ Well, there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪ When I'm dancing with myself
It's showtime!
♪ All over the world
♪ And there's every
type of girl ♪
♪ But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
Oh, Pickles!
♪ It'll give me time to think
♪ If I had the chance,
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪ Oh, oh
- Almost there.
- Just gimme a little squeak.
- Are you ready
for my destiny, Pickles?
I'm leaping!
- He came back for me.
Catch me!
Get back here, Pickles!
Hitpig!
Now what?
My sensors detect
their oxygen levels dropping
and I don't see a way
for them to return
to Earth on their own.
- Can we push 'em back?
Not
without smashing into Earth.
- We need a parachute. Grab
whatever fabric you can find.
Curtains, costumes,
even underwear.
- That ain't new
territory from me.
- Oh, how exciting.
- Feel like pulled pork
for dinner, Fluffy?
Then go get that pig.
- We need to divide and conquer.
Can you fly around the outside,
see how we might be able
to pull these people back?
- Can do!
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
- I'll keep control
of the catch van.
- Okay guys, let's save Pickles
and everyone in that theater!
- Aye aye, Captain!
- Roger, roger.
- Over and out.
Really?
Hitpig!
- Go help Pickles, now!
I've fought bigger lizards
than you in the Outback.
Come at me!
- You came back.
- I'm so sorry, Pickles.
I should have told
you the truth.
Can you forgive me?
- What are friends for?
- You're ruining
everything, Hitpig!
- I'm ruining everything?
You're going to get us all
killed!
I'm actually trying
to unruin everything.
- I'm giving them
the greatest show off Earth!
Yeah, but you don't have
a way to bring 'em
back to Earth!
- Well, I can't
think of everything!
Do you know how hard
it was just to do all this?
Ding ding!
In the left ring we have
the croc versus a koala.
Common sense says
koala's gonna die!
- Do you think this is
scripted or all improv?
- In the right ring,
we have a pig versus a lunatic!
- Now even the lack
of gravity mocks me.
Come at me,
you toothy turd!
Watch out, Hitpig!
- This is for Bertha!
Consider yourself hit.
Oh, no.
- I never cut
corners on costumes.
The audience is applauding
my exit, Fluffy.
I can still hear them.
- Whoa!
- Pickles!
- Right!
- Like we're made
for each other.
- A perfect fit.
- A super cock-a-doodley-doo!
I'm coming for you!
- Hi, Hitpig.
- How you doing, pig?
And I thought you just
played a superhero on TV.
- You really are one.
- Aw, shucks.
- You're alive!
- Oh, thank goodness!
What do you say we get
everybody back to Earth now?
- I need more horsepower!
- I need more chimichangas!
Approaching Earth's atmosphere.
We're coming in too fast.
- Panties, jock straps,
boxers, just send them on over!
Come on!
This is going to hurt.
Warning, impact imminent.
Well, it was nice knowing you.
- Deploy the parachute.
Whoa.
Can I get my thong back?
- Well, I guess it's time
to all go home, huh?
- I'm heading to Australia if
you wanna ride with me, koala.
- Yeah, great.
I'll show you my digs.
Throw some eucalyptus
on the Barbie.
- I'm going to introduce polecat
to some Hollywood agents.
He's a star
if I've ever seen one.
- Thank you.
- Oh, I'm staying here.
We're in Vegas, baby!
And I got me a date!
Well, everyone
loves my hard body.
- You sure you
want these poodles?
If they want me.
- Pickles, may I take
you home to India?
- Yes. Yes, you may.
- Frittata!
- Omelet coming up!
Of course.
- Oh, we got a wise guy here.
Hey, look kid,
no bacon ever. Capiche?
- Ciao, Hitpig.
- Surprise!
So, how you doing?
Living the dream.
How was India?
- Beautiful. But I couldn't
find a family there
quite like our friends.
- Yeah. Yeah, I guess friends
are the family we choose.
- So what's it like
living the omelet dream?
Is it all it's cracked up to be?
- Yeah, you know,
it pays the bills
for an even bigger dream.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- See, on weekends
we do some volunteer work.
We?
How was Indiana?
- Hey, everyone, hi!
You got room for one
more on that thing?
- You bet we do.
Lower the tub!
- I love a family outing.
♪ Born to be wild
- So if you're a kitty
who's left the city
or a moose on the loose
or a cow that said ciao,
call us.
Your happiness is our reward.
♪ Born to be wild
- Ooh, I'm feeling
a little bit toasty here.
How about you, Fluffy?
Son of a sun!
And scene.
♪ Born to be wild
♪ Get your motor running
♪ Head out on the highway
♪ Looking for adventure
♪ And whatever comes our way
♪ Yeah, gotta go
and make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
in a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all your
guns at once and ♪
♪ Explode into space
♪ I like smoke and lightning
♪ Heavy metal thunder
♪ Racing with the wind
♪ And the feeling
that I'm under ♪
♪ Yeah, darling,
gonna make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
in a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all of your
guns at once and ♪
♪ Explode into space
♪ Like a true nature's child
♪ We were born,
born to be wild ♪
♪ We can climb so high ♪
♪ And never wanna die
♪ Born to be wild
♪ Get your motor running
♪ Head out on the highway
♪ Looking for adventure
♪ And whatever comes our way
♪ Yeah, darling,
gonna make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
in a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all your
guns at once and ♪
♪ Explode into space
♪ Born to be wild
As queen
of the elephants, it is I
who wears the pants,
so as your queen,
I command you all to dance.