Ooh. Ooh-la-la.
Illumination!
And now for a bedtime story.
- ♪ ♪
Once upon a time,
there was a beautiful pond.
It was paradise.
- Everyone was happy there.
Well, not everyone.
For two ducklings
were suffering
from a strange condition.
They were bored.
And they were eager to
discover what lay beyond
their cozy little pond.
Come on. Let's have a look.
But Daddy says it's dangerous
to leave the pond.
We're brave and strong.
We ain't scared of nothing.
So they decided to go for it,
- straight into the arms of...
predators!
- They were
surrounded, trapped.
But the ducklings
were not afraid.
The tiny heroes attacked
the predator, and...
they died.
The end.
Uh, that's all? They're dead?
Oh, yeah. No survivors.
But how?
Oh, you want details? Okay.
So, first,
the heron cut them in half...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second here.
Your father got
the story wrong-- again.
What really happened was:
The heron saw
that they were lost,
so she offered to help them.
Pam, it's a heron.
A psycho killer
designed to eat ducklings.
All right, fine.
The heron was about
to eat them.
But their parents arrived
just in time and saved them.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Their parents arrived,
but it was too late.
Oh, Dax, don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
Really, Dad?
Yeah, sure.
Squished ducks, they can
achieve great things, too.
As long as they stay in the pond
far from the dangers
of the world,
such as herons
and bears and wolves
and storms and cyclones
and tornadoes and crocodiles
and poisonous mushrooms...
Okay. I really need
to get to bed now.
...and saber-toothed tigers...
What happened to
the other duckling?
- Was she squished, too?
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't worry, Gwen.
The ducklings were both safe.
They just went on their way
right back to the pond.
But another predator
came in and...
And wished them good day.
-  The end.
- That's it.
Okay.
Good night, Mom.
- Good night, Dad.
- Good night.
- What?
Every time you tell a story,
Gwen wets her twig bed.
Does she? That's great.
See? That means
she's learning, Pam.
Oh, learning what?
That she should never
leave the pond?
Exactly.
Trust me, I'm teaching her
very valuable fears.
I should know. I've lived
with them my entire life.
So have we all.
Good night, honey.
Good night, sweetheart.
Ready, set, go!
Come on, Gwenny! Come on!
Let's go. Let's go.
Beat Daddy. Beat Daddy.
Go, go, go, go! Oh, yay!
- Yes!
- Aw, I lost.
Whoo! Yes!
- Whoo...
- Hey.
- Huh?
- Hello!
Huh?
- Yay!
- Mine!
- You're the worst!
- That's mine!
- Got a thousand of 'em!
- Whoa.
- Thanks, Dad!
Whoa!
Okay, guys.
Remember to pick
the fresh leaves.
Okay, Dad.
Is this one good, Dad?
Perfect.
Keep looking for more.
Guys!
Guys, you have to see something.
It's incredible.
Come on, come on.
Everybody, come. Come on.
Whoo! Oh, look!
- Oh, I told you.
- Yeah!
Isn't it beautiful?
This is awesome!
Oh! Have you ever seen
ducks like that?
Look at that.
- They must be migrating.
- Whoa.
They seem so mysterious
and exotic.
I wonder where
they flew in from.
Maybe we should go say hi.
Should we?
No. Oh, look at these feathers.
No, I want to know.
Let's go ask 'em.
Mack, come on.
Yeah, no, I'm good.
Ugh. Come on.
We never meet anyone new.
Okay, fine.
All right, kids, let's go meet
Mom's new friends.
Kids?
Kids? Kids?
Pretty good progress, huh?
Yeah. Got to love a tailwind.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Hello.
- Ah. Hello.
Welcome to the pond.
- Thank you.
- Hey there.
- Oh, hi.
- Nice feathers.
We shouldn't be here, Dax.
- Shh!
- Dad is gonna be mad.
- Go back to the parents, Gwen.
- Hey there.
- Dax!
What are you doing?
I don't want to be
psycho-killed!
Let me go,
you little feathery wart! -Oh.
Okay, I'm a feathery wart?
You don't even know me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
She's a feathery wart.
You're a very nice wart.
I-I mean wart duck.
- I mean...
- I'm kidding.
Oh. Right.
Hi. I'm Kim.
Hi. I'm Dax.
Welcome to Moosehead Pond.
"Welcome to na-na-na."
You and your flock can stay
here as long as you like.
- I could show you around.
- Hmm?
I mean, this is
pretty much it, but...
Mmm. Thanks.
But we're just passing by
on our way down south.
We're gonna spend
the winter there.
Where are you guys going?
We spend winter here
to avoid psycho killers
like your...
- Sorry. Wart.
Wait. So you don't go anywhere
for the winter?
Uh, nope.
You should
totally come with us.
- What? Really?
Yes! Your flock could
totally join ours.
Oh, my gosh,
this will be so cool.
You will love migrating.
The sun, the sand.
Wait. Do you like tropical food?
- What's your take on bananas?
- Oh. I don't...
Ah, you're gonna love 'em!
You hold this.
I'll go ask my dad.
Dad! Dad!
- What just happened?
- Dad!
I don't know,
but you're in trouble.
Dax! Gwen!
Are you crazy? You can't
just take off like that.
- He made me do it!
- What?
And he talked to a girl.
- A girl?
- Gwen!
Yeah, and he told her
he wants to marry her.
What? I didn't say that!
You said it with your eyes.
Dad, he's hitting me!
He's hitting me!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Enough! Enough!
- Sibling cruelty!
- Enough.
Okay. Hello.
Hi. Hi. Big hellos.
And we're good. Let's go.
- Mack.
- What? I said hi.
I smiled. I made eye contact.
I checked all the boxes.
Hey there.
I hear you want to join
our migration.
Sorry?
Oh, we're going back to Jamaica.
Have you ever been?
No.
Oh, it's just magical.
I swear, there's even
a luminous lagoon
where the water glows.
Oh, wow. Oh, I really
want to see that.
Well, then it is settled.
Your whole flock can join us.
This is gonna be great.
Oh, gosh. That's...
That's just so nice of you.
Wait, wait, wait.
I think there's a slight
misunderstanding here.
Unfortunately,
we're just slammed this winter.
Aren't we, Pam?
'Cause we've got the thing,
and then the...
We got the thing after that.
So, you know what? We can't go.
But you guys go.
Have a great time.
And, you know, tell
the glowing water we said hi.
Uh, well, maybe next year, then?
You got it. Next year!
Uh, well, I guess
it's time for us to go.
Uh, have a nice trip.
Thanks.
Have a nice... pond.
I'm so sorry you can't
have babies with her.
That was so... rude!
I know.
"Have a nice pond."
Who says that?
That's just poor parenting.
Not them. You.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Okay. So I got
a little carried away.
But migration?
What a stupid idea.
- Ugh. Okay. You're impossible.
- Why?
Because I found
a safe place for us to live
and we're happy here?
You mean you're happy here.
What?
I-I want us to get out
and see the world.
- Me, too, Dad.
- Yeah.
I want to go to Jamai...
Jam... J...
where they make jam.
You-you really want
those things?
Yes.
- Really?
No home improvements?
- PAM and DAX: No!
Yes.
I mean... I mean no.
D-Do you know what can happen
on a trip that long?
What sort of father would I be
if I put my young fowl
in harm's way
for no reason except a chance
at a Caribbean vacation?
A father who knows
it's important for his kids
to see other parts of the world.
Mack, I don't want
to miss out on life
because you're afraid
to leave this pond.
This isn't about migration.
It's about adventure.
Seeing what else
life has to offer.
Is that a little scary? Sure.
But isn't it worth it?
No, Pam.
Not really.
You really need to open
your eyes, Mack,
before you miss it all.
Come on, kids.
- Hmm?
Huh? Huh?
Uncle Dan,
what are you doing here?
I don't know.
I must have drifted
from my nest again.
Be a good boy
and get me back there.
Give me a little push.
All right.
Thank you.
I heard the little family tiff.
I got to say...
you're right.
Wha... I am?
Please.
What's all the travel talk?
I mean,
why can't we be satisfied
with what we already have?
Well, yeah.
I mean, you got food right here.
We got a pond right here.
Right?
Yeah. Food, the pond.
Why go anywhere else?
Stick to your beliefs, kid.
- Don't change for anyone.
- Exactly.
And you'll end up just like me.
- Happy.
- Yeah.
- Healthy.
And totally alone!
Yeah! Wait, what?
That's right.
You'll be living the dream.
Whoa, that was exhausting.
I'm gonna just rest here.
Rise and shine, Mallards!
We're burning daylight.
Up and at 'em.
Let's go, go, go!
Here's breakfast.
Dad, what are you doing?
Getting your sorry feathers
out of bed.
Come on. We got to get ready.
Mack, ready for what?
Nothing. Just, you know,
for our big,
super fun family migration!
What?
Ha! Bet you didn't
see that coming.
- Are-are you serious?
- Yep.
An adventure into
the totally unknown.
And I'm gonna love it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. I-Is this real?
What do you mean,
"Is this real?"
We're really going?
- Yes.
- On a migration?
- Mm-hmm.
- To Jamaica?
- Yeah.
- Together?
- Yes.
- Like, everyone?
- Including you?
Yes! We are all going
on a migration to Jamaica.
In which language
should I tell you?
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome.
Oh!
I knew there was
some adventure left in you.
Wait, wait, wait!
Uncle Dan, you're coming, too!
- Gwen, no, no.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're going to Jamaica.
No. I don't think so, kiddo.
Oh, please, Uncle Dan.
Nah.
Oh, too bad he doesn't want
to come, honey.
We tried. What else can we do?
- Let's leave.
Please...
Pretty please?
Whoa. That did it.
I can't refuse her.
Look at her.
Look at how cute she is.
Yes! Uncle Dan is coming!
No, he's not.
Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan.
GWEN and UNCLE DAN:
Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan...
- Oh, for real?
Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan.
- Uncle Dan, that's me.
- Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan.
Yeah!
MACK and PAM
Yay.
Here we go.
Let's do the final check.
Tail feather torsion?
Check.
Wing deployment?
Heads in takeoff mode?
Check.
Let's fly.
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Whoa! Whoo!
Yeah!
Okay, everyone,
enough fooling around.
"V" formation.
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
- Look at me!
- Thanks, Dad!
- Whoo!
- Yeah, this is awesome!
Well, better get used to it.
Huh. That's weird.
My inner compass may be
a little rusty,
but I'm sure
we're heading south.
Yeah, we are, but why are we
the only birds heading this way?
Hey, kids, don't worry.
We're gonna be all right.
Here we are together.
We're on an adventure.
I promised adventure,
and this is exactly
what I promised, huh?
We're not gonna make it, are we?
- Uncle Dan!
- You can tell me. I don't mind.
I'm a big boy. I'm a big duck.
No, Uncle Dan,
things are gonna be fine.
- Isn't that right, Mack?
Uh, I, uh...
I mean yes, Mom's right.
This is fun.
This is the kind of thing we'll
remember for years to come.
We'll look back and laugh.
- A heron.
- The one from Dad's story.
The ultimate duck killer.
Don't panic.
Herons can't see
their prey if you stay still.
Hello, little ducks.
She's bluffing.
So, tell me, what's a nice
little family of mallards
doing down here
all cold and wet?
Nothing. We're good.
We're enjoying it.
But you must be freezing here.
- Oh, no, we're not.
- Come.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- Come, come.
Let Erin take care of you
in her comfy little nest.
In you go. Hup, hup, hup.
Harry!
Harry, look.
Look what I found.
A nice little family
of traveling mallards.
Mallards.
Uh, okay. Nice meeting you all.
Bye-bye.
In a rush, are you?
Oh, we don't want
to be a bother.
You look busy decaying.
You're not bothering at all.
But maybe herons are not
good enough for you, mallards?
No, of course not.
We're happy to stay.
Good!
Let me get your bed ready.
What do they do,
rip you apart, then eat you?
- Dan.
I don't know how they do it.
What's the method?
- Hey. Zip it.
Wake me up when it's
my turn to be eaten.
- What?
- What are you doing, Pam?
Well, I don't know. I just...
I don't want to offend them.
Can't you see
they want to eat us?
I don't want to be eaten!
Well, she can't eat us.
She doesn't have teeth.
Well, what if she cuts us
into pieces first?
I don't want to be cut
into piece...
I-I-I beg your pardon?
Oh, what's that? No, no.
We were just saying
your nest is just so charming.
Weren't we, kids?
Oh, thank you.
We moved here a few years ago.
We used to migrate
all the time like you.
Harry was such an adventurer.
Fierce predator, too.
He could catch any prey
with a single swift peck.
Those were the good old days.
Now Harry's too old.
I'm the one who brings food
back to the nest.
But, anyway,
you must be exhausted.
Here's your bed.
There's no way
we're sleeping in that.
But it's our finest bed.
And it is perfect.
Thank you.
Wow, huh?
Hey, feel this.
Even comfier than our own nest.
Yeah, sure.
It's greasier, too. Oh!
Looks like your last guest
is still here.
- And dead.
Thank you.
You're welcome, sweethearts.
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Okay. Storm is over.
Let's go. Kids, kids, wake up.
- Pam, we got to go right now.
- What?
- Right now!
- Now?
- What about Uncle Dan?
- It's fine.
When they wake up,
they'll eat him.
That'll give us more time
to lose...
You're awake.
Looking right at us, too.
- Bonus.
- Shh!
You shouldn't have gotten
out of your beds.
Nighttime is when
predators like to feed.
Stay away from my kids.
Let's do this quick!
Run, kids, run!
Let me get them!
Harry, catch them!
- Head for the door!
Go, go!
Hands off!
- It's okay, kids.
Just hold still.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please don't eat us.
We haven't finished molting yet.
Pretty please?
I promise you this won't hurt.
- No!
Gotcha!
He was about to gulp you
in one bite.
Bad fish.
Ooh, bad fish!
You... you saved them?
Oh.
It was nothing.
And we have breakfast
for tomorrow.
Right, Harry?
Into beddy-byes now.
Are you sure
you have to go already?
I'll miss your kids so much.
They are so adorable.
Mmm. And you taste so good.
- Maybe I'll eat you.
Uh...
I'm kidding.
- Or am I?
- Huh?
- It's a joke!
- Oh.
- It's a joke.
So funny.
All right.
Time to go.
Thanks for everything.
Oh, goodbye.
Uh, I haven't kissed
Harry goodbye!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Blow him a kiss.
- MACK and GWEN: Mwah. Mwah.
No, no, no, no,
you don't have to walk closer.
You're good there. Bye, Harry.
Thanks so much. Mwah.
Don't forget,
drop by on your way back.
Whew.
Wild night there, huh?
Yeah.
How about when she pulled out
that pan, though?
Oh, my gosh! With the dead fish
still in the pan?
- The dead fish.
- Terrifying.
Right? Still, lovely birds.
Oh, lovely.
Lovely birds.
Guys! Come up!
You have to see this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
Dax, let's keep the adventure
where I can see you.
Whoa!
Woo-hoo! Come on!
Try it, Dad!
Okay, okay,
this is pretty cool,
but we should probably
get back on...
Don't be such
a stick-in-the-mud.
Woo-hoo!
Whoa!
Ah, yeah!
- Woo-hoo!
- Hello!
- Peekaboo!
- Whoa! Dad!
Ow. Hey, watch out.
Hey!
- Aha! Whoo!
Gotcha! Whoo!
That was fun.
Let's go down
before we lose our way.
Please, Dad, come on.
- Just a bit more.
- Please, Dad?
Okay, okay,
just a little bit longer.
What is that?
- Whoa!
Guys, you okay?
Yeah! What a ride.
Let's do it again.
Yeah!
Your mother.
- Where's your mother?
Pam?
That is not your mother.
Up here! Fly up.
We can see so much better
from up here.
- Pam! Are you hurt somewhere?
- Oh! What?
- Do you feel pain?
- I-I'm fine.
What's your name? How many
feathers am I holding up?
Hey. I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Okay. Come on, everyone.
Prepare for takeoff
so we can get out of...
...here.
What is this place?
I... I don't know.
We've never been
this far before.
Uncle Dan, have you ever
been here before?
Uncle Dan?
Hello? Guys?
Anyone?
I don't like heights.
Oh, whoa!
Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
Uncle Dan?
Yeah, it's me!
- It's Uncle Dan!
Uncle Dan!
Well, he led a good life.
What?
We're coming for you, Uncle Dan!
He would have wanted us
to go on without him.
Come on, he was kind like that.
Ow!
Oh. Well, hello there.
- Ah...
Get away, get away!
Pigeons.
Mmm.
Ah...
Uncle Dan!
- Uncle Dan!
- Uncle Dan, where are you?
Uncle Dan?
What if something ate Uncle Dan?
Honey, I promise you,
nothing would ever
want to eat Uncle Dan.
- Uncle Dan.
Get off me!
I'm coming!
- Hey, wait! Wait!
Get away from me!
It's my sandwich.
I licked it, I licked it!
You can't touch it
with duck spit on it.
Uncle Dan!
Get your wings off my uncle!
Dax, Gwen, wait!
Stay away from my family!
Back away!
Back away! Back away!
Get out of here,
you trashy, trashy vermin!
PIGEON
Who said that?
I asked, "Who said that?"
Huh?
Come here, bumpkin.
Uh... Oh.
Say it again.
Uh, which part?
"Trashy, trashy vermin."
Let the record reflect I just
meant to say "trashy vermin."
Which I'm not saying
that's good,
but I wasn't doubling down
on "trashy," vermin.
You ducks make me sick,
you know that?
You're fed all day
by the humans in the park,
but that's not enough for you.
No, no, no.
You got to come
to our territory.
You got to steal our food.
And then you insult us?
What? No, no, no, no,
I wasn't...
- Name!
- Uh, Mack.
Well, "Uh, Mack," I'm the Chump,
and I'm the leader of
this group of hardworking birds
you just called vermin.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
So listen, Chump...
- What did you just call me?
Sorry.
I thought your name was Chump.
Yeah, Chump, yeah.
That's my name. Why?
Right. So listen, Chump...
- What did you just call me?!
- I'm sorry.
Is everyone else
hearing "Chump" or...
- What did... What?
- Okay, okay.
I think there's a slight
misunderstanding here.
Excuse me. Will you excuse me?
Coming through.
Uh-huh. Thank you.
Okay. Hi there. I'm Pam.
I'm sharing my life with him,
so I'm painfully aware
of all the stupid things
that come out of his mouth.
Hmm?
Oh, yeah, that's true. She is.
But I assure you,
he meant no harm.
And to show our gratitude
for your understanding
in this matter,
how about we share
the sandwich 50-50?
- 80-20.
- 60-40.
- 70-30.
- 65-35.
- 68-32!
- 67-33!
You got yourself a deal.
Uncle Dan, cut the sandwich.
Uh...
You don't want to try
50-50 again?
- Uncle Dan!
- All right, all right.
You, I like.
Thank you, Chump.
Sorry for busting your bills
over here, but, uh...
sometimes
I get sensitive, is all.
Us pigeons,
we got big hearts, too.
Ain't that right, guys?
- Oh, for sure.
- We just want to be loved.
- And respected.
Yeah.
So anything you need--
I mean anything--
Chump's got ya.
Oh, really?
Because we are completely lost.
We're trying to get to Jamaica.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's in Queens, right?
Uh, more south.
Uh, like, the Caribbean.
Oh, that Jamaica.
I got a buddy
who knows that place
like the back of his wing.
You-you think he'll help us?
Yeah. I mean, it's a bit
of a sore subject for him,
but, uh, I'm sure
it won't be a problem.
Come on, lovebirds,
we ain't got all day.
It's this way.
Wow. Mom, you rock.
Yeah.
- 60-40!
-  70-30!
60,000-3,500!
I didn't know
you could be so tough.
Really, Mack?!
You didn't know that?
Oh, no, I...
Oh!
I get it.
That's good.
That's very good.
Okay, my little bumpkins,
- let's get a move on.
Whoa.
Are you kidding?
We are not flying through
this crazy death trap
of a city again.
Oh, come on. It's nothing.
Just stick close to me,
and everything
will be all right.
I'm okay. Yeah, no, I'm okay!
- Yeah.
I'm okay.
I'm still okay.
- We can do this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ha-ha! You missed, bus!
Maybe don't stick too close.
- Whoa.
Aw.
Here you go, my little princess.
Thank you!
- Woo-hoo!
Whoa, Gwen! I got you, Gwen.
I got you.
Look! Look, there it is.
That's Jamaica.
What?
Here we are.
Okay, so...
Wait, where's our guy?
And what is that?
Huh? Oh, that?
Don't worry about it.
But I should probably warn you,
Delroy's owner is a chef.
A-A chef?
Yeah. A-A chef.
Like a predator
except instead of eating you,
he feeds you to a group
of much lazier predators.
Right this way.
After you.
Hey. Shh!
Coast is clear.
Hey, Delroy.
How's it going?
It's been a while.
You look good.
Slip me some feather.
I brought you
a nice family of mallards.
They need to ask you something.
Oh. Well, Mr. Delroy,
so nice to meet you.
Do you know the way to Jamaica?
Do I know the way to Jamaica?
Told ya.
He's a little sensitive
about it.
He was born and raised there.
What happened?
The chef snatched him up
in the middle of the night.
Next day, old Del's gone
from free bird to jailbird.
Come on, D.
Just tell them how to get there.
Fly to the big green statue,
fly due south for three miles,
then due east for one mile,
due west for ten miles,
then you southwest for one mile,
south-southeast
for two miles... -Uh...
...and south-southwest
for the rest of the way.
And don't stop
until you see that mist
dancing atop
the beautiful blue mountains.
You can't miss it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, don't cry, Big Red.
It's all right.
We didn't mean to upset you.
Jamaica!
I miss my family.
Devon.
And likkle Donnie.
Dolores. Deedee.
Winston!
That me cousin.
Dad, we're not really gonna
leave him here, are we?
He looks so cramped
in that cage.
- Come on, blow it out.
- Blow.
There's nothing
we can do here, Dax.
We could get the key.
No, kid. That's impossible.
Why? Where is it?
Down there.
The chef keeps that key
on him at all times.
And trust me,
you don't want to go
anywhere near that lunatic.
Him catch ya, him turn you
into duck à l'orange.
What's duck à l'orange?
It's you with l'orange on top.
You know what?
Guys, don't worry.
- I'll go get it.
- Uh, what? No, no, no, no, no.
Dad, it's okay. I've got this.
No, you don't got this.
But just because you're scared
of everything in the world
doesn't mean I have to be.
Okay. You know what?
I will go get the key.
Cool. I'm coming with you.
- No. You stay.
- Dad!
Ah-ah-ah. Stay here.
Hmm?
Huh?
- How's it going?
Shh! What are you doing here?
I told you to stay back there.
Oh, there's no way I'm
letting you have all the fun.
Let's go.
There.
Here.
Grab my tail
so I can get the key.
Hurry.
- Pam.
- Almost there.
Look.
-  Pam.
- Almost there.
- Pam.
- A little closer.
Pam!
Got it.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Duck à l'orange!
♪ Keep on surviving ♪
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Salsa Tuesdays.
♪ Now that you're out of
my life, I'm so much better ♪
♪ You thought that I'd be weak
without you, but I'm stronger ♪
♪ You thought that
I'd be broke without you... ♪
- We're doomed!
- Don't panic, Mack.
I can't help it. It relaxes me.
Mack, we're gonna make it,
all right?
We have to be optimistic.
Optimistic? How can we
be optimistic right now?
Well, I don't know,
but if we are panicking,
we'll never find our way out!
That's it.
- What's it?
- Whatever you're doing,
keep doing it.
You mean like this?
Yes, Mack. It's working.
♪ Sobreviviré, sobreviviré ♪
♪ No se puede apagar ♪
- ♪ La esperanza ♪
- ♪ Sobreviviré... ♪
Oh, we can do this, Mack.
Whoo!
Okay, follow my lead.
♪ Yo sé ♪
- ♪ I'm a survivor ♪
♪ I'm not gon' give up ♪
♪ Ya lo verás, voy a lograrlo ♪
♪ I'm a survivor ♪
♪ I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ Es la verdad, yo sobrevivo ♪
♪ I'm a survivor ♪
♪ I'm not gon' give up ♪
♪ Ya lo verás, voy a lograrlo ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ Es la verdad, yo sobrevivo. ♪
Dad, Mom, you were amazing.
Thank you, Gwenny, but we're
in a bit of a hurry right now.
- Pam, key.
- Here.
Okay. Let's do this.
Hurry! Hurry!
No, more to the right.
To the right, and twist.
No, no, no, no, no.
My right, Dad.
- Mack! -Down, down.
- No, push.
- No, to the right.
- That's it!
- Now, hold it and twist it.
- No, Dad.
- Come on!
- Do I just have to do it?
- Push!
Oh. What happened?
Wait, wh-where's the k...
Where's the key?
- I swallowed it.
- Oh, that's a bummer.
Spit it out.
You need to spit it out!
I'm on it. I'm on it.
- Come on, Mack.
Okay, he's really close,
and he really looks mad.
- Mack!
- Spit it out already.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Come on! Hurry up!
Come on, kids.
Together.
Spit it out!
This isn't working!
- Bird eater incoming!
Got it!
Oh!
I'm free!
Whee!
Ya mon!
We did it!
Thank you!
Whoo! Oh, you did it.
I can't believe it.
I was in a cage,
and now I'm not.
In, and now not.
And you did it!
All of you.
But you...
- you wild duck, you.
You must be the bravest duck
me ever meet.
Oh, I'm not that...
I'm not that brave.
What?! You knew the danger.
You did it anyway.
What do you call that?
Yeah, you're right.
I guess that is the only word
that describes who I am.
Did you hear that?
He called me brave.
So you want to go
to my island, eh?
I will be honored
to take you there myself.
You'd do that?
For you, me do anything,
because I can do anything!
Woo-hoo!
I can go here,
or I could go here.
Free as a bird!
Right.
'Cause I'm a bird!
I didn't think
I'd ever say this, but, uh,
you are one heck of a bird.
Oh. Well, thanks, Chump.
You're not so bad yourself.
Yeah, you know, I'm getting
a little waterwork-y up here.
Scram, you crazy ducks.
Get out of here.
- Bye, Chump.
- Bye-bye, Chump.
- Thank you!
Thanks for everything.
So long, Chump.
Don't forget
where you got that sandwich.
Bye-bye, you country bumpkins.
I love you.
I can't believe it!
In a few hours,
we'll reach the coast.
Then a little hop
over the ocean,
and we'll finally get
to my homeland!
Hey, uh, Delroy, uh, is it true
that the sea glows at night
in Jamaica?
Because that sounds
incredibly magical.
Ah.
You hear about that, eh?
Whatever you're expecting
over there...
it's going to be even better.
Jamaica, I'm coming home!
- ♪ I'm coming, I'm coming ♪
- Mom?
- ♪ I'm coming home. ♪
- Hmm?
It's really bad.
Oh. It's okay, Gwen.
You can do it while we fly.
Here? But anyone could see me.
No one's watching, Gwen.
You know what?
I'll go up front.
-  What's happening?
We have a number two situation.
Oh.
- Everything okay back there?
- Dad! Don't look!
- Oh! Sorry, Gwen.
- What are you doing?
My bad. My bad.
Mom, I can't do it here.
Can we land?
No, we won't land, Gwen.
You're old enough
to do it in the sky now.
But it's too much pressure,
and it's gross.
It's not gross. We're birds.
Every bird does it in the sky.
What if someone is looking
down there?
No one is looking down there.
I told you, we are not landing.
There is no way we're landing.
Are you sure no one's watching?
Gwen Mallard!
Do it now
or we leave without you.
- Okay, okay.
- Ugh!
She's perfectly capable of
doing her business in the sky,
- and yet here we are.
- It's okay, Pam.
Just let her be.
Does anybody have a soft moss?
Just use a leaf!
Someone's watching!
- There! Someone's watching!
- Where? Where?
Huh.
Hmm.
Follow me, and stay close.
Whoa! For real, Dad?
Mm-hmm.
Cool.
I like your spirit, duck man.
- Um...
- Hmm.
Guys?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, are you sure this is safe?
Don't worry.
That wild duck is on
a journey of the soul,
and I say we follow him.
But just in case,
get out your talons.
I ain't sure ducks
have talons, though.
Shh, shh.
GOOGOO
Now stretch your back
and move your wings
up to the sky.
Breathe in.
- And breathe out.
Excellent, class.
And now the egg position.
And we hatch
with a newborn quack.
Quack.
Very good.
And repeat.
Quack.
Hey, what's going on here?
- Visitors!
Brothers, brothers.
Sisters, hold your enthusiasm.
We-we don't want to scare
our guests away, do we?
Hello, friends.
I am Googoo.
Welcome to our humble abode.
Abode? What is going on here?
Our morning relaxation
as we prepare for
the glorious Earl and Mae
to open the gates to paradise.
- Oh, you're so lucky.
You're just in time.
My friends...
welcome to
the Garden of Harmony.
I don't understand. It's...
Heaven for ducks?
Yep, pretty much.
Ah. Perfect.
Whee!
You came to the perfect place,
my friends.
Here, humans spare no expense
on our well-being.
And they just finished building
our brand-new slide.
Yeah!
So please be our guest.
Feel free to enjoy our place
- for as long as you like.
Whoa.
Well, I guess we could
take the afternoon.
- Come on. Please.
- Come on. Come on, Dad, please.
- Come on. Let's stay. Stay.
- Please, please.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I don't think
we can possibly stay here...
...without having
the best time of our lives!
Now, get out there
and have some fun.
Slides, here I come!
Wait for me!
Slippy slides!
Woo-hoo! Whoa!
Here comes the sea dragon!
We're gonna get you!
We're gonna squish
your sea dragon face!
Sea dragon is hungry.
Hi-yah!
We need to slay the sea dragon!
Ow. Gwen.
- Gwen, be more careful.
- We need to slay him gently.
Really? Okay.
Ow! Uncle Dan.
What? I want to play, too.
Sea dragon needs a break.
- Ow! Gwen!
Brothers, sisters, great news!
Earl and Mae are taking us
on a field trip.
- I'm so excited.
It's so great. Hurry, guys.
Hurry. It's time.
You don't want to miss this.
Come on, everyone. Let's go.
No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to get started.
Googoo, stop!
What is it, my little friend?
The-the chef. The-the...
You want to come, too?
- Come on. Let's go.
- You got to stop.
- Last one is a rotten egg.
- Googoo! Stop!
- Googoo!
- Kneel, sea dragon, kneel!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, Gwenny.
- Googoo, no! Stop!
- No. Don't hit your father.
- What?
- We're not hitting fathers.
Googoo! Googoo!
- Where are you going?
Uh, Delroy is
the sea dragon now.
Of course. I'd love that.
- You're next!
- No, no, no.
You're gonna be gentle.
Okay, no... -
- Ow!
- Gwenny, come on!
- He said "gently."
Googoo, he's gonna take you
to his kitchen.
- Come on.
- He's gonna serve you
to people, with oranges.
Hey, hey. What's happening?
Dad, it's the chef. He's back.
Earl and Mae are giving
those ducks to the chef
so he can cook them.
I beg your pardon?
Dax, go back to Mom.
I'll handle this.
No! I can help! I can just...
Go back to Mom now!
Googoo, do not get
on that truck.
Look, I understand this is all
new to you--
bit weird, bit strange...
Don't you get it? It's a trap!
We've got to get your ducks
out of here!
Everyone, get off the truck
unless you want to be cooked!
- Cooked?
- What?
- Wait, what's that?
Come on! Hurry!
You got to go
before he comes back.
Let go!
- Earl and Mae are our leaders.
- Dax?
- They massage us.
- Dax!
Everyone, run! Now!
- Pam, the chef!
- What?
We have to get out of here now!
Go, go, go!
Okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Everyone, take off!
Dax, on my back!
Hurry!
Guys, we need to rest.
Follow me.
Guys, are you okay?
What happened?
- Mom, he was coming for the...
- I'll tell you what happened.
I told him to stay back, and
he almost got himself killed.
But, Dad, I was trying to help.
I don't need your help, Dax.
I need you to do what I say!
Do you understand?!
Listen, Dax.
Just let us grown-ups
figure it out while...
All right, everyone,
let's call it a night.
We could use the rest.
Gwen, you scared me.
You look mad.
You need a hug!
No, Gwen, I don't need a hug.
- Whoa! I said no hug.
Don't fight it.
It'll make you feel better.
Can you let go now?
- You feel better?
- No.
Then it hasn't kicked in yet.
- What about now?
- No.
- Now?
- Mm-mm.
- Nothing.
- A little?
- Nope.
I felt something.
Mm-mm.
- Oh, no, he's back!
- Every duck for himself!
- Kids!
- Dax! Gwen!
- Mom! Dad!
No, no, no!
- No, no! Dax, Gwen, stay back!
- No! Stop!
- Get out of here now!
- Go hide!
- Hide, kids! Go!
Go, go!
No.
No, no, no.
Mom!
- Mom, Dad, no!
- Daddy!
- Oh, kids! Oh, kids!
- No!
He's gonna cook Mom and Dad,
isn't he?
And he's gonna come back for us.
- And he'll cook us, too!
I wish we tasted awful!
Gwen, we're not giving up, okay?
We're-we're gonna
figure something out.
We are?
Yes. There has to be a way.
But-but how?
You can't even fly.
Oh, we're doomed.
Gwen, you're a genius.
Am I?
We are not getting cooked today.
Come on, Pam, keep going.
Pam?
It's hopeless, Mack.
What? No, no, no, no, no,
it's not hopeless.
- We can do this.
- No, we've lost them.
Mack, we've lost the kids.
You were right.
We never ever should have
left the pond.
Pam, enough.
This isn't you.
You're the adventurous one,
the-the-the brave one.
You never give up on anything.
You-you haven't even
given up on me.
Come on, Pam.
You've proven
over and over again
that when everything
is hopeless, we have to be...
Optimistic.
Yes. And now you and me are
going to get our kids back
so we can finish this crazy,
wonderful adventure.
And we are going to show them
that when danger strikes,
you do not run from it.
You take a stand.
That's it! Look, Pa...
- Shh! Shh, shh.
We can do this.
Mack, Mack, we can do this.
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
- Left, Pam.
- Just... You do your left.
- No, no, no, no. Right.
Okay, you're moving
on the left. Move on the top.
- Just set...
- Okay, no, no, no, no, no.
- Psst. Hey. Over here. Here.
- Hey. Hey.
- Here.
- Do it together.
- Ya mon. Together.
Wh-Wh-What?
Together.
Hmm?
You trap me for years,
now you're trying
to cook my friends?
Enough!
It is payback time!
Payback!
Reload.
Ah...
Eat this.
- What?
We're coming!
Dax!
- We got this, guys.
We can do this!
Mom!
Kids! Oh, kids.
Woo-hoo!
Ya mon!
Everyone!
Delroy, you made it!
- You're alive!
I'm so happy to see you.
And you, all dressed up
for Jamaica.
- Look at you!
Well, come on.
Let's go, go, go, go, go!
We're almost there, everyone.
I can feel it!
Okay, so we're a bit lost.
Must have missed a turn
somewhere.
But don't worry.
We just have to go back
to the big green statue.
- Pam?
- Hmm?
Mack, the water.
It's glowing.
It's real.
The water is glowing!
Dad. Dad!
Come look.
That's it.
That's Jamaica.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Lead the way.
- Gwen, final check, please.
Aye, Captain.
Tail feather torsion?
Check.
Wing deployment?
Heads in Bake-Off mode?
- Takeoff mode.
- Takeoff mode?
Check!
Let's fly.
Woo-hoo-hoo! Yeah!
Let's go! Come on!
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Whoa! Whoo!
- Whoo!
- Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Look at me!
Whoa!
Yeah!
- Woo-hoo!
I am back!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Hey, Devon!
- Deedee!
- Delroy!
- Winston!
Whoo!
- Whoa.
Wow.
- Whoa! Woo-hoo-hoo! Yeah!
Hey!
Hey, you changed your mind.
Better late than never, right?
Kim!
Dax!
Dax, you're here.
Wow.
Your wings, they're beautiful.
Thanks.
Dax kept saying your name
while he was sleeping.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Whoa!
Delroy!
- I'm home!
- Delroy! Delroy!
What?
Thank you.
For what?
Opening my eyes.
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky,
find the sun... ♪
Uncle Dan!
Mm-hmm?
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
- ♪ On a cloudy day ♪
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
♪ On a cloudy day ♪
♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
- ♪ But your mumma always said ♪
♪ Look up into the sky ♪
♪ Find the sun
on a cloudy day ♪
♪ On a cloudy day. ♪
Pretty please?
No, Gwenny, you cannot take
Toothpick back home.
But Toothpick wants to come.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mm, I think it's time
to let him go.
Okay, honey?
Okay.
So, we're ready for takeoff?
Wait. Where's your father?
Guys! Guys!
Guys!
I just met these birds
who are totally lost.
I said we'd help 'em get home.
What do you say?
Hello.
- Hi. Hello.
Hi.
Mack, you do know
that penguins are from
the South Pole?
I know! Isn't that great?
GWEN and DAX:
Yeah!
We're going to the South Pole!
No, I'm not going. No way.
Oh, please, Uncle Dan.
Please...
ALL
Okay, okay.
We're going to the South Pole.
- Yeah!
Come on, Pam.
We're going to the South Pole.
I've created a monster.
Okay, so let's talk itinerary.
I say Costa Rica, Panama,
Amazon River.
- Any other ideas?
Oh, oh!
I want to see Titicaca!
Titicaca! Great.