Even though he’s hurting,
Arkin always thinks
about how you’re doing.
Cheers.
- Surprise!
Wait! Don’t leave yet.
Good thing you’re available.
Via—
What should I do
if I see you again?
Hug me.
Then let go of me again.
Hey! Why are you so quiet, Luna?
I’m just feeling a little sad.
Sam’s leaving for New York,
and then Via’s
leaving soon, too.
You’re making me cry, too.
Go see Arkin to say goodbye.
It’s okay, Arkin.
I want all my firsts to be with you.
Via is leaving now.
She’s going to Spain,
and she’s going to work there.
- Cheers!
Cheers.
Wow. We’re so,
so proud of you guys.
Too bad the three
of them aren’t here.
It’s annoying.
Come on, let’s take a photo first!
So I can send it to them.
Sure, let’s take a picture.
So, Via, what were you
going to say again?
First, congratulations to all of us.
We’re finally all architects now.
I just want to thank you
guys, because
you never left me.
Thank you...
for sticking with me,
no matter what.
I really want to keep working
with you guys as workmates…
but—
I’m leaving next week.
Where to?
For vacation?
For how many weeks?
The way you announced it,
it’s like you’re going
to be gone forever.
Where to? Boracay?
Siargao? Bangkok?
- We’ll go with you.
- Yeah. We’re coming with you!
To Spain.
I have an opportunity
to work there.
Maybe for a few years?
Or maybe for good.
- For good?
Hold on—
To Spain?
Huh?
You’re moving to Spain?
Yeah.
I already booked a flight.
It’s next week.
I already have a flight…
Sevi,
please don’t tell Arkin.
He doesn’t need
to know about this.
What kind of job
do you have there?
Do you have an agency?
This better not be a scam.
I’ll be working with my aunt.
My aunt helped me
get the job there,
so don’t worry.
Wait, what about
Sam and Yanna?
Do they know about this?
I already told Yanna before.
I talked to Sam earlier.
Does it have to be next week?
Yeah.
I didn’t want to tell you yet.
I wanted to tell you
only when it was final.
Now, it’s really final.
Damn, you’re actually going
to study in Spain,
not just España Boulevard.
But, no kidding?
You’re leaving next week?
- You’re leaving already?
- Sevi, come on!
Stop repeating it.
Yes, it’s next week.
This makes me sad.
Sam’s already going,
and now you’re leaving too.
Hold on, I’ll just
message the group.
We need to see each other
before we all go our
separate ways, okay?
Yeah. Let’s take a picture
so we can send it.
- Come on…
- Okay.
Look here.
One—
What? You’re not including me?
Never mind.
One, two, three—
Come on, Sevi. One, two—
One, two—
Awesome. I’ll send this, okay?
Oh, come on…
Guys, Sam and Via
are leaving soon.
Let’s do a farewell party, okay?
All right. Cheers, hurry up.
You’re making me cry, too.
Let me hold you, bestie.
You’re making us all cry.
We’re going to miss you, Sam.
Don’t go.
I have to.
Visit me sometime, okay?
Via.
Yeah?
I’ll take you home.
Huh?
Sure, thanks.
Oh, it’s nothing.
I won’t be able to do
this often anymore.
Via.
Are you really not going to tell Arkin?
Doesn’t he at least
deserve to know?
I already ended whatever we had.
There’s no connection
between us anymore.
Don’t you regret that
it just ended like that,
the connection between
the two of you?
After spending almost
your whole lives together.
I mean, I’m just worried
as a friend to both of you.
With me, it was only five years,
and it was already so hard.
What more with you two?
He’ll be fine.
He can handle not having me.
And I’ll manage too,
so don’t worry, okay?
Besides, you can
tell him anyway.
After I’ve left.
Don’t you want to see him
one last time before you go?
Even just as friends.
Okay.
I’ll just get the car.
Have a safe flight.
I’m sorry, sir. I can’t let you in.
- Sir.
- Via!
Sir, please just listen
You’re really not allowed.
- Sir.
- Via!
You’re really not allowed, sir.
I’m sorry.
This is as far as you can go, sir.
Please stay there, sir.
You really can’t go
past this point.
Sir, please don’t force it.
Please don’t force it.
I just need to stop
someone from leaving.
I’m sorry, sir.
You’re really not allowed.
I wonder what he
looks like in person.
- I’ve waited for this my whole life.
- Yes! Me too.
Good thing he came
here to Spain, right?
- If not, we’d be the ones going there.
- Perfect timing that we’re here.
Oh my gosh!
Larkin Sanchez is so handsome.
Oh my gosh, I’m so happy
we got great seats.
- Exactly.
- We’re right in front!
Come on, Via, let’s go.
We’re so excited for you
to meet Larkin!
Let’s go.
You guys go ahead, I’ll follow.
- You sure?
- Okay then.
- I can’t wait anymore.
- Make sure you follow, okay?
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
♪ Left thinking in the
midst of the chaos, ♪
♪ utterly bewildered
by these feelings. ♪
♪ I can't tell if this is a dream, ♪
♪ as if my heart was
playing in the heavens. ♪
♪ In the daylight, you are there, ♪
♪ beside me, and I gaze at you. ♪
♪ I don't know anymore, ♪
♪ I get confused whenever
I'm with you in… ♪
♪ a golden scenery beneath the sky. ♪
♪ - Having you with me. ♪
- Kino!
♪ - As the wind blows,♪
- We’re married! We’re married!
♪ along with the song,
I feel your hand. ♪
♪ May my prayer be heard, ♪
♪ that you love me in return. ♪
♪ An orange sky, ♪
♪ painting the
beauty of your eyes. ♪
♪ A hidden longing
quietly peeks through— ♪
♪ Wanting to be with you
and hoping to stay by your side. ♪
♪ Singing along with
the sparkle of your smiles, ♪
♪ only wishing that, at the very least, ♪
♪ you’d look my way. ♪
♪ In the daylight, you are there, ♪
♪ beside me, and I gaze at you. ♪
♪ I don't know anymore, ♪
♪ I get confused whenever
I'm with you in… ♪
♪ a golden scenery beneath the sky. ♪
♪ Having you with me. ♪
♪ As the wind blows, ♪
♪ along with the song,
I feel your hand. ♪
♪ May my prayer be heard, ♪
♪ that you love me in return. ♪
♪ An orange sky, ♪
♪ painting the beauty of your eyes— ♪
♪ My mind keeps wondering, ♪
♪ do you want to hold me too? ♪
♪ Is this really as far
as our friendship goes? ♪
♪ A golden scenery beneath the sky. ♪
♪ I hope you know, ♪
♪ As the wind blows, ♪
♪ along with the song, can you feel me? ♪
♪ May my prayer be heard, ♪
that you love me in return.
♪ An orange-colored sky, ♪
♪ unable to be forced
to receive your love. ♪
Thank you very much.
It was nice
seeing you again.
Kino…
What an amazing welcome.
I wonder if his fans
still remember me?
Will they still recognize me?
Are they still mad at me?
You didn’t even
remove the traced letters.
You’ve got some nerve.
- You didn’t even help, girl.
- What?
- Don’t start a fight with me.
- I came up with the concept. I did!
You came up with it, but—
Via!
What—
- You smell like Spain.
- We missed you!
Is that what Spain smells like?
Stop, this is so embarrassing!
- Hide this. What the—
- Huh, why?
- Hide this. It’s embarrassing
- We worked hard on this. Look.
- We really put effort into this—
- Why—
- And now you want it hidden.
- Yeah, right.
- It’s beautiful.
- It’s really beautiful!
- So beautiful!
- Look at it.
Pretty, right?
It’s so beautiful.
I missed you guys.
Hey, let’s go eat at the mall.
Oh yeah. Sevi and Yanna
are going there too.
Let’s go.
Oh!
Who’s this handsome guy?
- Let’s go.
- Come on.
Fine.
Wait, my suitcase—
- I’ll hold on to it.
- Her bag might fall off—
Yeah, we’ll hold it. Come on!
- Careful now.
- Be careful with that.
- Be careful. I’m sorry. That’s heavy.
- Yes, I got it.
Oh my gosh.
Via, you have to tell me
about your love life there.
So, have you already given
in to the Spaniards?
Are they good? Are they big?
Oh my gosh!
Hey, Luna! Seriously…
I don’t have time for that.
It’s all just work.
Huh? Why? Don’t you
get bored there?
Right?
They say there are a lot
of handsome guys there.
True.
But it’s not like I’m looking
for good-looking guys.
I’m not interested.
I’m really just focused
on work there.
Really?
And I don’t want to flirt.
Life doesn’t revolve around flirting.
I can’t relate.
I’m just kidding.
I got it. All right, fine.
Okay.
By the way, your ex
is super famous here.
You know, we don’t even get
to hang out with him anymore.
Even Sevi barely
gets to see him.
Actually, that’s true.
You know, when he
switched agencies,
his opportunities
really exploded.
Now he’s mostly focused on
music rather than acting.
- Right?
- Yeah.
And then he even
had a concert.
It was awesome!
Tickets were sold out!
He even did a world tour.
Shit. So cool!
Our solo artist is
really something, huh?
Good for him.
Also, I heard he has
a movie with Clea.
It’s a new movie.
Yeah, like their
comeback movie,
and people are excited.
It’s been so long since
they last did anything, right?
You’ve got a lot
of updates, huh, Luna?
I don’t even want
to hear about it.
Yeah, she’s not interested,
so stop it.
- Let’s go.
- All right, I’ll shut up.
Come on.
- Come on.
All right, fine.
- Don’t get mad.
So, really nothing?
Are you guys hungry?
- Yes.
- Tell me about it. I’m so hungry!
- Hi!
Wow, Via. I thought
you were a celebrity.
- Your skin is flawless!
- You guys are early. Hi!
Clearly coming from
a country with no polluted air.
[In Spanish] How are you, miss?
You’re annoying, Sevi!
Right? Seeing him now
just ruined my day.
Oh my gosh, same.
I just saw him.
No more. I’m done.
You guys are too much.
All right. I won’t
bother you guys.
I’ll try to do better.
Such a sad boy.
So dramatic.
- Sad boy.
- Geez.
He’s saying so much again.
- All right, fine.
- Look at that face!
Bullies! It’s just Sam and
Avi on my side now,
and the other
one isn’t even here.
Say, hi.
Avi!
Hello, Aunt Via! Welcome back.
I missed you.
How have you been?
You keep getting taller, huh.
At this rate, we’ll be
the same height.
Hey, Avi.
Show Aunt Via
what I taught you.
Come on.
Got something for me?
You’re teaching her
all kinds of nonsense.
Ouch. Gag—
Gag reflex.
Right!
- Hey!
- Oh.
Look, it’s my dude, Larkin.
He’s here to welcome you.
Stop being silly.
Mommy, let’s take a
picture with Uncle Arkin.
Sure. Baby, go on,
stand there.
Wow.
A picture with Uncle Arkin.
- There you go.
- Smile.
With Uncle Sevi too, okay?
Okay, smile!
- One, two, smile!
- Why’d you join too, Sevi?
You weirdo.
- You?
- Me?
No.
Come on now. Let’s go inside.
I miss Uncle Arkin.
I rarely see him nowadays.
Baby, your Uncle Arkin is busy.
Come on, let’s eat.
- Okay, let’s eat.
- All right!
Come on now.
We’ll go ahead.
- I really need to pee, too.
- Avi’s already hungry.
Okay, I’ll follow.
Okay.
Could it be that
I’m one of the reasons
they don’t get to hang out
with Arkin anymore?
Did he distance himself
from the group because of me?
That makes mefeel really guilty.
I feel like I’m the one who
ruined our friend group.
Our breakup kind of forced
Arkin to leave the circle.
I just hope he still has
someone to talk to
when things get hard.
I’m hungry already.
Isn’t there anything else—
It’s taking so long.
Hey, can I borrow that for now?
We’re getting really hungry now.
This is starting to get annoying.
Ever since I arrived,
all I keep seeing is his face.
Look at my dude, Larkin.
He even has a bundle deal.
Wow.
You really picked the
wrong restaurant, Sevi.
How was I supposed to know
he’s an endorser here?
But wait, Via…
Have you not moved on
from Larkin yet?
Huh?
That was a long time ago.
I’m fine now.
Of course, I’ve moved on.
Okay.
So...
we can invite Arkin here now?
Sure. Invite him if you want.
But what if Arkin’s the one
who hasn’t moved on yet?
He might totally lose it
when he sees Via here.
Are you saying Arkin
hasn’t moved on yet?
No.
No, I’m just saying maybe.
You never know, he might’ve
moved on already.
Via said that it was
a long time ago.
And because of that,
let’s just invite Sam instead.
Call her. Isn’t she in New York?
Hey, call her.
My phone’s charging!
Mine too.
No. Let’s order first.
Waiter! Sir…
Do we get a discount if
we know the endorser here?
Can we order him instead?
- Yes.
- The endorser himself.
Sure.
- Is that okay?
- They said it’s okay.
Where is he?
They’re looking for—
- She’s looking for him.
- There he is. That’s him.
- Come on now. Be serious.
- No, I’m just joking.
One what, Bundle A, B, C.
Is it your treat?
There. These are the clothes,
and those are
the groceries I bought.
That’s a lot, sweetheart.
You didn’t spend all your
salary on gifts, did you?
Oh no, Pa. No.
Some of those
are from Auntie, too.
Thank you, Via.
I’ve got something
nice to wear now.
Is it like that?
You just have a classmate
you’re trying to impress.
No, I don’t.
Aidan’s a big boy now.
- He has a crush on someone.
- Big boy!
I don’t, okay?
So, how long are
you staying here?
Do you plan on
working here again?
Just until the project
is finished, Dad.
That’ll probably take a few months.
Well, I hope the project
takes a long time
so we can have you here longer.
You brought this too, Via?
Oh.
There’s another guitar here.
Who does that belong to?
That’s Mr. Benito’s, our neighbor.
I borrowed it because
I’m learning how to play.
You’re learning?
Someone teaching you?
No. I’m learning
from online videos.
But since you’re here now,
you can teach me.
Of course. I’ll teach you.
And we’ll also buy you
your own guitar
so you’ll have one.
There’s no need, it’s too much.
You already brought me
so many gifts.
It’s all right.
It’s your reward for
getting high grades.
- Wow.
- Thank you, Via.
- Nice.
If Aidan wants to pursue music,
I want to support him,
because that’s something
I wasn’t able to do
before with Arkin.
Aidan, just put the guitar
in the bedroom, okay?
Okay.
This goes in the fridge.
- This is my favorite.
- That’s a lot, Via.
What does that taste like?
It’s so annoying.
Even in my own room,
there are so many
reminders of him.
Maybe I need to rearrange things
so there’s no trace of him left.
Hi. I’m looking for Ms. Marj Garcia.
Sure, ma’am.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Architect Diaz?
Hi!
- Hi, ma’am. Hello.
- Finally.
Hi. Hello.
Everyone,
meet Architect Avianna Diaz.
She’s one of
the architects handling
the Bulacan Airport Project.
And she’s from Cuesta Architects
Barcelona branch—
and she’s one
of the top architects there
so I know we’re in good hands.
Thank you so much, ma’am.
Hi, nice to meet everyone.
I’m excited to work with all of you.
Same here, Architect.
This airport renovation
project is a big one,
and I’m glad they sent
someone skilled to help us.
Well, that’s a lot of pressure,
but I’ll do my best.
So, tell me, how’s your stay in Spain?
Yeah.
It’s okay.
Good.
Is that Clea?
Yes. That’s her.
She’s our big client.
And she’s looking for an architect
to design her new house.
What a small world.
Via, no backing out, okay?
You’re going to buy me a guitar.
Pick the guitar you want
before I change my mind.
Actually, I’ve had my eye
on a guitar here for a while.
There, see?
This one, sir?
Yeah. Please.
It’s nice.
Come on, sir,
let’s try the guitar.
Take a look.
Should I buy it?
I don’t really use it.
All right, fine,
since I’m here anyway.
I’ll also get Aidan a pick.
Aidan?
Aidan, do you need a capo—
Go ahead and take the guitar.
Let’s pay, Aidan.
Okay.
Take care, Arkin.
This, too, please.
Total of 13,800, ma’am.
- Thank you.
There. All set.
Thanks. Let’s go.
Yup.
Let’s go.
Hey, miss.
You forgot something.
Thank you.
Take care, Aidan.
I thought I wouldn’t be
surprised anymore
seeing him in person,
since I see his face
everywhere all the time.
And did he reallyjust call me miss,
like I don’t evenhave a name?
Let’s go…
Miss.
Come on.
There. What chord is that?
G.
That’s it. Strum it.
Did he inherit
Mama’s musical talent?
He learns so fast.
Admit it.
Have you been taught already?
Taught?
Taught how to play
the guitar before.
I actually learned
from Arkin before.
I ran into him at the music store
when I was looking
for the guitar I wanted.
He goes there a lot because
that’s where he buys his stuff, too.
And you brought me there?
I didn’t mean to, Via.
I also didn’t know he would
go there yesterday.
And just because you’re
no longer a couple,
that doesn’t mean
we lost our connection.
He’s been a good older
brother to us, too, Via.
That’s the hard part with
my relationship with Larkin.
We got too close
to each other’s families.
I can’t really blame my siblings.
It’s fine with me if they
still talk to each other.
That’s what I want
for my friends, too,
but Arkin is the one distancing
himself from them.
I feel bad that he had to lose
friends just because of me.
All right.
Just play something for me
so I can hear what
you can already play
and know where to
start teaching you.
Okay.
Later, I’ll help you with
a room makeover, okay?
Sure.
All right.
You already know how to play.
Excuse me.
There you go, Via.
Your room looks amazing now.
Thanks for all your help, guys.
Why did you suddenly decide
to rearrange your room, Via?
It looks completely different.
A breath of fresh air.
And I’m an architect, remember?
I want my space to be organized.
Via, I noticed you look skinnier now.
Probably because you’ve been
exercising a lot in Spain, huh?
Exercise? No.
Just walking.
In Spain, everything
is so walkable,
and wherever you look,
it’s beautiful.
I hope I get to go there too.
Of course. Come here,
I missed you all.
You’ll be able to go
there too. I’ll take you.
Really, Via?
Of course!
You’ll get to go anywhere.
Just study well, okay?
And I’m sure that
wherever you want to go,
you’ll get there.
I promise, I’ll study hard
so all the effort you put into
our education won’t go to waste.
Only the last two
years of college left!
Me too, Via!
I’ll make you proud, too.
I’ll work even harder, Via,
so I can help you and Papa.
You’re so inspiring.
I’m so proud of you all.
And I’m sure you’ll achieve
even more than I have.
But promise me, okay?
That you’ll put your own dreams first.
Yes, Via.
- Okay?
- We promise.
I missed you guys. Come here.
We missed you, too.
Wow, you’re so sexy now, Via.
- Wow.
- Oh, come on, you guys!
Wow!
Wow. She’s really sexy.
And you,
have you been good?
– Maybe not.
- Yeah, why?
He’s picking on me.
Wait, why—
Are you—
Are you two fighting?
No.
I missed you all.
You can do this, Via.
Just finish this project,
and then you’ll be back in Spain.
You can do this.
Okay—
Can I see?
Okay. This looks right.
But let’s just make sure the
quality of the materials we’ll use
matches what
we discussed, okay?
Then we’ll follow up with
the engineers on the presentation
so we can proceed.
Yes, ma’am.
I’m planning a European
structural style.
Good thing we’re not working together.
It might get awkward.
There’s apparently
a high school batch reunion.
Are you going?
I’ll think about it.
I might be busy with projects.
Architect Diaz?
Can you come with me?
Yes, ma’am. Sure.
Hmmm...
What’s this about?
Please excuse me.
Hi, ma’am.
Please sit down, Architect Diaz.
How can I help?
Are you open to taking on
an additional project?
Huh?
I’m asking because
we have our VIP client here,
the famous actress, Clea Aguilar.
She’s looking for an architect
to design her house.
Hi, I’m Architect Diaz.
Hello. Clea.
Hi.
Clea wants a European-style house,
and I realized that it’s your forte.
You see, Architect Diaz is originally
from our branch in Spain.
She’s one of the best over there.
That’s why she was sent here
to Manila for a big project.
So, Architect Diaz, what do you think?
Are you up for the challenge?
Ma’am—
It’s fine, Marj.
I think Architect Diaz has
her hands full right now.
It's fine.
What a shame, Architect.
I think you’d be perfect for this.
Don’t worry about the workload.
We’ll be partnering you
with Architect Herran,
so it won’t be too heavy.
This opportunity is too good to pass up.
Avianna,
stop letting your
personal feelings affect your work.
You need the money
for your family.
You’re helping Papa
put your siblings through school,
so you don’t have
the right to turn this down.
Architect Diaz?
I will take it, Ma’am.
Great!
I think Clea is
available tomorrow.
You can meet
and discuss the details.
Great.
Excuse me,
I’ll just take this call.
Yes?
Via—
I hope doing this project doesn’t
make you uncomfortable.
I know there were things
that happened before and I—
Oh, no. It’s totally fine.
And let’s just leave
everything behind.
I’m really happy that we’re
doing this together now.
All right.
Perfect!
Okay. So, I’ll see you soon.
Yeah.
I’ll go ahead.
Thank you so much for
accepting the project.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the trust.
Bye!
Bye.
Why did I accept that?
But they said I’ll just
be helping anyway.
Yeah, that’s my forte.
I’m used to that kind of design.
Right.
It’ll only be for a short time.
This is for my siblings
and for Papa.
It’s just temporary.
Just work, nothing else.
Thank you.
Okay. So for the exteriors,
I want a European countryside feel.
Maybe think Spanish farmhouses.
Lots of stone details,
warm and earthy tones.
But I also want to see
your take on it, too.
Your vision, Architect.
I’m thinking we can still
do more landscaping here.
And is the size of
the pool okay for you?
I think I can finish the sketches
and the full concept
in about two weeks.
Would that be okay?
Perfect!
I’ll be busy with filming,
but I’ll message you where
we can meet for the design.
Yeah. You can message me here.
You can contact me anytime.
All right. Thank you so much.
Also, please don’t hesitate
to message me
if the schedule gets tight.
I don’t wanna overwork you.
Sure, thanks. Okay.
Just to finalize—
I worked on this for several days.
A house isn’t just a project.
This is a home.
Someone will live here
and make memories.
So even if it’s hard
and exhausting,
I have to give it my all to
make it feel like home.
Hi, sorry. I have a
shoot this Friday.
Can we meet at a cafe near
our shooting location?
Okay. No worries.
See you.
Let me present to you,
Casa Aguilar.
Here’s the other side.
There. What do you think?
I love it!
It really feels like a Spanish
farmhouse in Manila.
Though, I just have
a few comments.
So, maybe the outdoor patio
could be a little bit wider.
Okay.
Since we do have the
square footage after all.
Okay.
And then just
a reminder about the—
- the living room.
- Okay.
I want it a little bit bigger.
- That’s it.
- Okay. Got it.
Anything else?
That’s it.
- Okay.
- It’s so pretty.
It’s taking so long.
Shit.
Hey!
Are they still setting up?
Yeah. That’s why
I stepped out for a bit.
Okay.
Can you get my order,
the croissant,
from the counter, please?
Real bossy now, huh?
Okay. Sure, madam.
Thank you.
Are they a couple now?
I’m sorry. Where were we?
If you have
any more comments…
No. That’s all.
Just a few comments.
That’s it.
Okay.
Sir, Clea’s order please?
Please wait—
Architect, your idea is spot on.
You really got exactly what I want.
I think we have the same taste.
Here’s your order, ma’am.
Thank you.
Shit. I’m sorry.
- Are you okay?
- You okay?
- I’m okay. I’m fine.
- Are you okay?
- Do you have ice? Sir?
- No. It’s all right.
Are you okay?
- I’m okay, it’s all right.
- Get some ice, please!
Yes, sir.
- It’s all right.
- Please wait...
- I’m okay.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I’m okay. Don’t worry.
Are you sure?
- Yeah!
- Okay.
It’s all right. I’m okay.
Wait a minute.
Lea is calling.
Our producer.
I’m sorry.
Yes, Lea?
We’re going back now.
Okay.
I’m sorry.
We need to go, Clea.
The director is about to lose it.
We need to finish all the sequences
since we won’t have
a shoot until next week.
Okay, got it.
So, are you guys done?
Yeah.
Thank you so much,
Architect, for today.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
We’ll go ahead.
Yeah.
Here.
Looks like the rain is getting heavy.
Thank you.
We’ll go ahead.
Did Arkin ask her to give this?
Just a quick glance.
Just one smile from you, and I’ll leave.
- Cheers!
Why did you suddenly
ask me out for drinks?
Am I not allowed to?
Of course, I missed you, bro.
We just don’t get
to see you anymore.
By the way, Mom had
your favorite dish cooked,
it’s in the car.
So you’d have something
to eat at the condo.
Perfect timing.
I missed Auntie’s cooking.
Tell her thank you.
By the way,
Via’s coming back to Manila.
Saturday. 11 AM. Terminal 3.
Luna and Ke will pick her up.
No big deal.
Just sharing, bro.
All right, I’ll grab the food
so I can give it to you.
Hi.
Please cancel all my schedules
this Saturday morning.
Got some important errands.
All of them, sir?
All of them. Yes.
All right, sir. I’ll clear
your schedule on Saturday.
Thank you.
Come on.
- Come on.
All right, fine.
- Don’t get mad.
So, really nothing?
- Nothing.
- Seriously?
Welcome home, Via.
Via, no backing out, okay?
You’re going to buy me a guitar.
Pick the guitar you want
before I change my mind.
Arkin?
Hey! Aidan!
Arkin!
What’s this? Are you buying it?
Yes. This is the one I want.
I already know how to play.
You taught me.
- Can you help me out?
- Now you know how.
Don’t talk about… You know what.
- It’s a secret.
- It’s our secret.
All right, then.
Who are you with?
Aidan, do you need a capo—
Go ahead and take the guitar.
Let’s pay, Aidan.
Okay.
Take care, Arkin.
There. All set.
Thanks.
Let’s go.
Hey, miss.
You forgot something.
Thank you.
Take care, Aidan.
Miss…
I miss you.
Are you Architect Diaz?
This way, please.
And—
Three, two, one—
Action!
If that’s the case, then—
Cut!
It’s terrible! Damn it!
Arkin, what is happening to you?
I told you he’s not going.
Hi!
How are you?
- Shot!
I’m sorry.
I’ll see you on-site?
What are you staring at?
I’m changing.
This is the dressing room, remember?