ADVANCED PROGRAMMING
How late did he stay up working yesterday?
Past midnight, I guess. Let him sleep.
GOOD MORNING
JIAJIA
Daddy, get up.
It's seven o'clock.
- Back from your walk?
- Yeah.
- Come eat.
- Okay.
Let's eat.
Zhilei.
Remember Uncle Qin from my old shipyard?
How's his son's job coming along?
I've already got him an interview.
Isn't that Wang Haoyu?
He's selling crabs now?
He got fired.
Wasn't he a core member in R&D?
Your husband is
the only one core member in R&D.
The store is out of soybean oil.
I need to go to the wholesaler.
Mineral water too.
Tell them to deliver more.
You can't rely on insulin shots.
You need to exercise.
How do I find the time?
It's parents' meeting next week.
Don't forget.
Okay.
Liu Yunong got in.
How's your English reciting?
We're leaving now.
- Bye.
- Bye, Pa.
- Bye, Dad.
I'm leaving.
- What's this?
- For your health.
Chinese medicinal drink.
Will it make my nose bleed?
Keep dreaming.
You think you're in your 20s?
Don't just drink it.
Chew on the ginseng too.
Wait.
Thank you.
Slow down, easy.
You're late.
Please deliver the order ASAP.
Check-in successful.
Check-in successful…
Morning, sir.
FOODIE DELIVERY
Closed beta is the third day
of next month.
The scheduled test has been advanced.
Other teams work hard too.
We must work harder.
How can you lose such an important update?
I forgot to change the date
and deleted it by mistake.
Don't tell people you did this.
Blame it on me.
What will you do?
What else? Redo it for you.
Thanks, boss.
Boss.
Cigarette break?
Is there still a market
for the app we're developing?
There certainly is.
But development costs too much.
Should we take over the project
Team A is working on?
I'm overworked already.
Are you trying to kill me?
I worked until midnight last night.
Then I tested my blood sugar.
- How was it?
- It was 18.
We should have more projects
and get more bonuses.
How many projects do Team A have?
Three, working 16 hours per day.
Do you see them smoking here?
Not even in the toilet. They wear diapers.
That's insane.
They are all fucking insane.
They are just like you, Sun Fendou.
A fighting grandson, you know.
A fighting grandson.
Mr. Gao.
Mr. Shi wants to see you.
Bye.
OLD COMRADE
So, you're letting me go?
Yes.
Are you crazy?
- Call security.
- I work my ass off.
Overtime everyday.
I've been here for ages and got diabetes.
Now I can't outlast Sun Fendou,
so you're firing me?
What's wrong with you, you bastards?
This is ageism. I'm telling you.
You're ungrateful bastards.
Let go of me.
Stop looking.
I've worked here for 11 years.
Now you're kicking me out.
I did the math.
- The compensation would be 700,000.
- 300,000.
That's the most we'll offer you.
If you agree, take the money and leave.
I'll file for labor arbitration.
Labor arbitration?
No problem.
We'll drag it out.
Gao.
The downsizing list
came from our HR Optimization System.
The system was actually designed
by your team.
Remember?
You even said that we must…
respect the algorithm.
Stop staring.
Is that my order? You are…
- I've been calling.
- What's the rush?
The front desk wouldn't take it.
You don't have time
to come get your coffee?
I don't understand your accent.
- Li Shulin.
- Here.
How old are you?
I'm 23.
I've just graduated.
And you?
I'm only 21. I'm here for the internship.
I'm young. I can try different jobs.
NO NEW MESSAGE
Gao Zhilei.
Here.
I'm Gao Zhilei.
I've got a degree from Tongji University.
- I'm proficient with Java--
- Hold on.
You were born in 1978?
Why is he even here?
I'm sorry.
I mistook it for 1998.
I once led a team…
You can't tell 7 from 9?
I'm sorry.
I once led a team to--
Can we do our job or not?
It's not your fault.
A programmer in his late 40s.
Can you still stay up late?
How much should we pay him?
Are we a nursing home?
You're so early today.
Dad, you're not at the store?
You're not at work either.
I was supposed to meet some clients,
but it got cancelled.
Qin went to interview at your company.
They said you were fired.
Is that true?
Actually, I quit.
- That company--
- Still lying?
How long has it been?
You're still hiding it?
Zhilei.
You asked Xiao Ni
to be a full time housewife.
Can our whole family
rely on the convenience store?
A big company wanted to recruit me.
Don't tell them.
I haven't told Xiao Ni yet.
You're unemployed.
What will happen to our family?
Don't run.
Stop.
Run? Where can you run now?
- You promised to find me a P7 job.
- I did, bro.
But with your age and your salary,
I couldn't find any.
Give me back my money.
All of the 30,000.
Fine.
I'll give it back.
Just let me get up.
I'll transfer it to you.
Let me up, please.
I'll get my phone.
- Is this your number?
- Yeah.
You called the cops?
Got stuck?
Try taking off the backpack.
Looking for a P7 job?
Kiss my ass.
If you want a job,
you can be a cab driver,
a delivery man for construction sites
or a janitor.
Idiot.
Hello?
- Where are you?
- What is it?
Your dad collapsed.
How is he?
He's taken to the hospital.
Come as soon as you can.
He wanted to save some money,
so he carried the stocks himself
and collapsed.
It's a stroke caused by fatigue.
We've cleared the hematoma,
but he still has central hyperthermia
and severe pneumonia.
His condition is quite special.
He has thick sputum
that requires a ventilator.
I don't know what got to him.
Take it easy.
He's practically living in the store now.
- The total is 240,000?
- Yes.
We've paid 100,000, so another 140,000?
You've paid for the surgery,
anesthesia, equipment and ECMO.
That's 70,000.
The 240,000 is for the ICU
and the deposit.
That much?
My dad has health insurance.
Mostly, the ICU is not covered,
neither are the imported drugs.
Of course, you can opt for domestic drugs.
It is fine.
- When do I have to pay?
- Within three days.
Hello.
The 300,000 for my severance.
Can you wire it to me now?
Yes.
I'll do the paper work tomorrow.
What is it?
I'm on a work call.
Yeah.
No labor arbitration.
Right.
Right!
Who were you talking to?
What labor arbitration?
Gao Zhilei.
Your salary for the last two months
hasn't come in.
The bank sent me a message
saying that our mortgage payment failed.
Zhilei.
I'm talking to you.
What's going on?
I lost my job.
It's been two months.
We lost all our savings
when P2P industry collapsed last year.
We just paid off the debt
we owed Qiang last month.
These cards have 32,000.
Monthly spending of the family
is 21,100 at least.
Mortgage payment is 14,900.
5,000 for necessities.
400 for medical bills.
500 for Jiajia's tuition.
300 for your insulin.
I'll reopen the drum class for kids.
It'll bring us
around 7,000 in a good month.
Okay.
So you'll have to bring in 15,000.
15,000 is not a problem. I can do it.
No problem.
And the 4,000.
After Dad's hospitalization,
his rehab will cost 4,000 a month.
The international school called me.
Jiajia is accepted.
That's great.
We should forget it.
We won't get the deposit back, though.
Don't do that.
I'll work something out.
Like what?
Just something.
What thing?
I'll find a way.
- I can handle it.
- Can you?
I can.
With what?
How?
Look at me.
With Dad's situation,
we can't afford more trouble.
I know.
If we can't keep the house,
we'll have to move.
Jiajia will have to change school.
- I know the house is our bottom line.
- You don't!
If you do, you would have told me
when you got fired.
Why didn't you believe that I could help?
I could reopen the drum class.
I could share your burden.
Why didn't you trust me?
I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at anything else.
We've been together for 15 years.
I'm fine if you got fired.
I can accept it.
But I can't accept
that you kept it from me.
Why did you keep it from me?
Are you the only one in the family?
I didn't want you to worry.
This is our family.
I can handle the 15,000.
I can.
I really can.
Cui, I'm in a hole.
P2P collapsed.
My dad had a stroke and I got fired.
Mr. Gao, you're 7 days
behind your mortgage.
If you keep stalling,
the bank will take legal measures.
I never missed a payment.
Could you give me…
I told you! It's the bank's rule.
Okay, I see.
Many thanks to Lovesick for the Porsche.
Guys, I have good news.
Last month, I've made 1,750 deliveries.
It's 10,042 in total for me.
Three delays and one bad review.
My monthly salary is 1,800.
The night shift bonus is 180.
The performance bonus is 600.
I've made 12,700 in total.
This is nothing.
The top guy at my station makes 16,000.
Young man, you're a delivery man?
Yeah.
You can make 12,000 a month?
- Yeah.
- And who makes 16,000?
The top guy at my station.
If someone like me becomes a delivery man,
will I make 15,000?
Sure.
But for that much,
you must do it full time.
It is not so easy.
You want in?
No, just getting a sense of the job.
You can scan my code if you want in.
It's on my bike.
I'm Yang Dashan.
That dude is pretty cool.
YANG DASHAN, THE ROMANTIC RIDER
Sterilize the box properly.
Spray the ethanol,
wipe the inside with the white towel.
Use the colored towel for the outside.
Foodie Delivery.
Loved by all.
Faster by each call.
You did well yesterday.
The number of orders is most important.
When the delay rate goes above 3%,
our ratings go down.
When it happens,
our fee goes down.
That will affect everybody.
Our station used to be
number one in this area.
We dropped to number two last month.
Will we be number three next month?
And then number four?
Then we will be shut down.
Then you're out of a job.
I don't want that.
Then move faster.
Move faster…
A round of applause for our hard-workers.
Good. Dismissed.
Listen up, guys.
Over the past year,
the local deliveries here
have had over 300 traffic accidents.
You must be safe out there.
Sir, hi.
I want to join.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from here.
Local.
- You can't do this. Go home.
- Wait.
Are you saying I'm too old?
- Zhang.
- Here.
- How old are you?
- I'm 57.
My wife is 56. My son works here too.
Enough. He's not a cop.
He's 57 and working.
It's not about the age.
I know.
Sir.
I delivered 35 orders yesterday.
Bravo. Keep it up.
You got this.
We don't discriminate here.
We're all delivery riders.
White-collar city elites can't do this.
- Too much hardship.
- Look. Here's my health certificate.
This job is exhausting.
- Forget it.
- I can do it.
Bro, you came.
You really came.
- Did you tell him to come?
- Yeah.
Aren't we short on staff?
But him?
Look at his belly. Can he do this?
Talk to him.
Bro.
I…
I can't find any job.
I need money.
Take him to suit up.
You train him.
Thank you, sir.
Bro, this is our platform's app.
Log on every day before you start.
It will give out orders.
The second you take an order,
the timer is on.
Pickups and deliveries
both count as time taken.
Order confirmed,
please head to pickup spot ASAP.
Your rider has arrived at the shop.
- Take a look.
- Thank you.
Your rider has picked up the order.
Do not be late.
Your pay will be cut.
- Delivery for 6983.
- Thanks.
We're out of jackets. Wear this.
All right.
Bro, tuck your belly in.
I'll get you a larger size tomorrow.
- What's this?
- It's our ranking at the station.
The manager designed it.
It's updated monthly.
- You're number 10?
- Yes.
Who's this Big Black at the top?
That's him.
30 years old.
From Alxa Right Banner, Inner Mongolia.
He's dark-skinned, tall and strong,
hence the nickname.
He doesn't talk much and rarely smiles.
But he's good, a born delivery rider.
He used to to herd sheep
on a motorcycle back home.
Big Black is a workaholic.
He takes at least 70 orders everyday
and can work for over 16 hours straight.
He only takes a nap on the bike.
He knows the roads well
and only needs a glimpse at the order
to decide the fastest route.
He has a secret notebook,
which he never shares with anyone.
Big Black has stomach problems
because he never eats on time.
Despite that,
he's still our hardest worker,
the biggest order-taker
and the fastest rider.
He never takes pass-on orders,
so he's very unpopular.
He has only one friend here.
Bad luck. Not a single number.
That's Stingie.
35 years old.
From Luhe, Nanjing.
He used to be a farmer back home.
Now the whole family has moved here.
He's called Stingie because he's stingy.
When his bike broke,
he patched it up with tape.
Same with his helmet
and his raincoat too.
It's said he even uses tape
to patch up torn underwear.
He orders plain rice and no dishes
at the restaurant.
But he knows
the best restaurants in this area.
They're not expensive.
- Cheapskate.
- Hurry.
He only drinks tap water
and saves the money to buy lottery.
He speaks bad Mandarin,
so he is hard to talk to.
Where is this "Cuocuo Ferry"?
What's the rush?
The front desk wouldn't take it.
You don't have time
to come get your coffee?
I don't understand your accent.
What is that?
Back home, I would've punched you.
He has thus received many complaints.
POOR SERVICE
What the hell?
Stingie.
This is Gao, he's new.
Hi.
You're close?
Not really.
What are you doing?
- Finished the paper work?
- In a minute.
Hurry, you've got work to do.
Mr. Zhu is from Shenyang.
He has a fierce look and a mean attitude.
But he's a nice guy.
He just wants a promotion badly.
He is quite experienced.
He worked as a foreman,
on an assembly line,
as a security guard
and a property manager.
He ended up as a delivery manager.
No matter what they deliver, stop them.
However mean the security guards are,
go past them.
You see that?
His performance and management skills
got him noticed.
He's since been promoted to manager.
Mr. Zhu focuses
on order count and reputation.
The Top Rider Ranking
is his way of boosting morale.
Raincoat. Holder. Badge.
Now you have everything,
except for one thing.
What?
Bike.
I'm taking you to a fancy place.
Bro.
If you want to make 15,000 a month,
you will need to bust your ass.
Now you're just a newbie.
You only get six RMB per order.
You need to level up to increase
your per-order commission, got it?
Don't just talk.
Watch the road.
I rode in Chongqing.
It's far easier here.
You're from Chongqing?
Zigong, actually.
I used to be a hair stylist.
Miss, your hair does seem a bit dry.
I was a temporary actor.
and a street promoter.
I worked as NPC too.
Delivering makes more money.
I also do live-streaming.
Guys, am I right?
Hi, delivery.
- Thanks.
- Do give me a good review.
I'm turning 25.
So I need to save some money.
For what?
For getting a wife. What else?
- Lu Meili, I miss you.
- You…
Make sure you miss me.
What is this place?
This underground tunnel
is in fact a riders' hub,
providing services to riders like us.
You can buy, rent and repair bikes,
change battery, fix your phone.
They do it all.
Our biggest rivals
are those blue fellows.
They are called Rapideliver.
- Boss.
- Hi.
You should get
a powerful bike that charges fast.
60 kilometers on a full charge.
- How much is that?
- 230 a month, but 200 just for you.
I'll throw in a new battery.
How about this one?
Slow down…
Slow down.
- Bro, log on first.
- Okay.
30 minutes left for this order.
Timer starts once you take it.
Don't be late.
There will be bad reviews,
and your pay gets cut.
Accept the order.
ORDER DETAIL
Order confirmed,
please head to pickup spot ASAP.
Time to set out.
I know this restaurant.
Stay close.
Coming.
It's a freezing day.
This 45-year-old local brother
has just joined us.
He's making his first delivery today.
If you ride like that, you'll get tickets.
Pull over there.
Wait!
Bro, wrong turn! This way!
- Go…
- Follow my rabbit ears.
Why would you go that way?
Catch up.
Once you're there, confirm it.
I'll get my order next door.
I'm here to pick up an order.
- What's the number?
- Number?
- 32, Foodie 32.
- Just a sec, not ready yet.
Hi, Mei.
- 35, hurry.
- Right away.
35.
- Mei.
- Hi!
37.
Hang on, coming.
Your rider has arrived at the shop.
Rapideliver 24 and 29.
24, ORDER PICKED UP
29, ORDER PICKED UP
31, ORDER PICKED UP
Xiaomin, here.
Okay, thanks.
Ma'am, when will number 32 be ready?
People after me have got theirs.
- 37! Foodie 37 is ready.
- Coming.
Bro, why are you still waiting?
- You're running late.
- I…
- Boss.
- Yes?
I'm training this new guy.
Please take care of him.
All right.
32, you need to come inside to take it.
32, ORDER PICKED UP
Your rider has picked up the order.
You are running out of time.
TIME RUNS OUT IN
DISTANCE TO CUSTOMER IS
Estimated time has run out.
OVERTIME
Oops. You're late.
Oops.
Did you order food?
- Yes.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- It's okay.
- Should you tap on this or should I?
What is this? Where's my food?
On, my!
- Sorry.
- Give it to me.
Anything else?
Nope.
A new order has been
automatically accepted for you.
Ma'am, is Foodie 27 ready?
- Hey! Are you new?
- 27…
Wait outside.
I'll tell you when it's ready.
Food is not ready yet.
Should I confirm pickup?
- Are you stupid?
- What?
Chop, chop.
You are running out of time.
You've run out of time.
You're late.
Please deliver the order ASAP.
Hi.
Food delivery.
Why did you even bother? It's too late.
My dad wanted to have wonton
before he left.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry for your loss.
My condolences.
What did you just say?
My dad was discharged.
- How can you talk like that?
- I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Where is Foodie 118?
Find it yourself.
No delivery bike on campus. Park there.
You are running out of time.
You have arrived at the destination.
Have fun delivering.
This is not right.
Do you know where Dormitory 4 is?
Dormitory 4 is…
- This way…
- That way.
Come back.
No delivery inside. Go out.
Call outside
and ask them to come downstairs.
The number you've dialed
cannot be connected.
Move aside.
Just holler if the call is not answered.
Oops. You're late.
Blooming Arse-ho.
Did you not eat?
Louder.
You will be fined soon.
Please deliver the order ASAP.
Bloom…Blooming Arse-ho.
Two boba tea.
Blooming Arse-ho.
Oops. Your pay has been cut.
Blooming Arse-ho!
Blooming Arse-ho…
Do you know this Arse-ho?
No.
Stop filming.
Your boba tea is here. Blooming Arse-ho.
What's your problem?
OVERTIME 16 MINUTES
Sir, is that my boba tea?
Are you Blooming Arse-ho?
Yeah.
Didn't you hear me yelling?
I was wearing headphones
and didn't hear it.
You should stay on your phone.
I've been calling you for 10 minutes.
Come on.
You should've brought it upstairs.
- The guard wouldn't let me in.
- It's never been a problem.
Why just you? Did you ask her nicely?
Why aren't you in class, kid?
You play games
and drink boba tea in your dorm.
How will you make a living?
By playing games!
- You skipped classes!
- It's weekend.
Without me, you'll be out of a job.
Lecturing me?
- Stop or I'll give you a bad review.
- Go ahead.
Unbelievable.
Arse-ho.
Oops. You've received a bad review.
BAD REVIEW: POOR SERVICE
Ew! That's gross.
Dad, what did you do?
Daddy ran a marathon.
I don't believe it.
Your dad did a city walk.
Have you prepared your English recital?
I see.
Put my uniform away.
Don't let Jiajia see it.
How many orders have you made?
ORDERS COMPLETED: 15
INCOME: -97 RMB
30 orders.
How much per order?
About 6 RMB.
It's 5,400 a month.
It's a far cry from 15,000.
I've just started.
It is easy. I'll get better soon.
Gao Zhilei,
I think you should be more realistic
and send out more resumes.
Gao Zhilei?
When facing a customer, always smile.
Smile. Don't fake it.
No creepy smile.
Smile naturally.
From the bottom of your heart.
Zhang.
Don't laugh out loud.
- It's from the bottom of my heart.
- Be cool.
This is Operation Smile.
We'll do random checks.
You will need to take a selfie.
When taking a photo,
make sure to show your helmet and uniform.
Those who fail will be fined 2-500 RMB,
and suspended for 3 days.
- Are we clear?
- Yes, sir.
Good.
Dismissed.
Use the staff entrance.
- I'm picking up an order.
- I know.
Delivery guys can't go in.
I shopped in this mall.
I was a consumer.
That was before.
When you wear this uniform,
you can only enter at the back.
Beat it.
Hurry, come on.
Pickup is that way.
Number 35.
Number 26.
Dude, this is Rapidelilver.
- Foodie is over there.
- I'm sorry.
- Foodie 36.
- Foodie 38.
Foodie 36 and 38.
Foodie 38.
- Foodie 52.
- Here!
Foodie 52.
That's me.
Hey, How can it…
Hey, please don't. I'm leaving.
You can't park here. Don't you know that?
Well, I don't.
I really don't.
You will after you get a ticket.
200 RMB.
- I'm sorry.
- Hello, comrade.
- Please don't give me a fine.
- Sure.
I'M LAW-ABIDING. I'M HONORABLE.
Huang, have some snack.
What is this? What do you want from me?
Can you see my bad reviews here?
Yeah.
Could you remove them for me?
Poor service.
I can't remove these.
It's not my fault.
Bad reviews about poor service
can't be removed.
When you guys argue with a customer,
there's no telling who's wrong.
It's complicated, right?
Don't bump into anything.
- Okay.
- Dude.
Take the trash out on your way out.
Give me an attitude?
We should just suck it up?
Exactly.
We're in the service industry.
Customers are always right.
Sorry, I can't remove those.
I made 3 deliveries this morning.
I made 21 RMB and the fine was 180.
Late delivery and poor service.
Two bad reviews, 100 each.
You bought coffee and rent a power bank.
I bring my own.
You should make some deliveries
in Chongqing.
You'll know how easy it is here.
- How many deliveries have you made?
- 28.
28?
I've got 40 to go.
Big Black, I want to get better.
What's your secret?
My secret is…
making more deliveries.
Hello?
What's the matter?
Don't you know you're running late?
This place is a maze.
I can't find 47.
Time is dictated by the system.
You're dragging us down.
I'll give you extra training tomorrow.
Chop, chop. You are running out of time.
You have arrived.
You're off route.
- You're off route.
- What's wrong with this?
Forty-seven…
You are running out of time.
Hi, Foodie Delivery.
Are you delivering my flowers or not?
I saw you going in circles.
- You're already late.
- I'm sorry.
This place is really hard to find.
I'll deliver your flowers
as soon as I can.
You're already half an hour late.
- Deliver it now.
- Yes.
- Hurry.
- Sure.
Lalamove guy.
Do you know where number 47 is?
I know this area. Follow me.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It's hard to find a place in the hood.
This is 47.
Okay.
- Thank you, sir.
- It's okay.
Hi.
Your food is here at the door.
I don't see you.
Huh?
I'm at the door.
Aren't you at Number 47,
Lane 201 in Wanhe Road?
That's right. Here I am.
You must have made a mistake.
You've run out of time.
But…
The address is correct.
I'll hang the bag on your doorknob.
Hello?
The customer of Order 47
put in the wrong address.
He's at a friend's place. Number 37.
It's not far. Bring it over.
But I already left.
Then go back.
It's the customer's mistake.
Why should I make it right?
Do you know
how many bad reviews you've got?
Do you want to keep the job?
Sorry. I put in the wrong address.
You need to give us the right address.
What's with the attitude?
Haven't I apologized?
I spent an hour delivering your order.
I've apologized. What more do you want?
My order.
Give it to me.
I've been waiting for a long time too.
All my following orders will be late now.
How is that my fault?
- Whose fault is it then?
- Who do you think?
What are you trying to say?
Do you want a bad review?
Who is it?
- Yes or no?
- What's going on?
Enough, let's go.
Don't snap at the delivery guy.
Yes or no?
No.
Say you're sorry then.
If you say you're sorry,
I won't give you a bad review.
How about it?
- I'm sorry.
- What?
I'm sorry.
Losers like you
should be delivering food for life.
Let's have dinner. Come.
Back to mahjong.
Hello?
Why did you turn back again?
It's a pre-paid order.
I've paid for it
and will surely deliver it.
Customer has canceled the order.
PRE-PAID ORDER: FENGZHI FLOWERS
RIDER HAS PICKED UP ORDER, DELIVERING
ORDER IS CANCELED AND UNPAID
NOT DELIVERED ON TIME
I FREAKING QUIT!
WIFE: INCOMING CALL
Hello.
Dad would be discharged today.
Weren't you supposed to pick him up?
Did you forget?
Zhilei.
Coming.
Why do we come to the store at this hour?
Dad, just one look.
You should go home
and rest for a few day first.
Dad.
You…
A Tongji graduate is delivering food?
What's wrong with that?
I didn't bust my ass
to put you through college
so you can end up being a coolie.
It's only a temporary job.
I'll find another one.
It's hard to find any jobs nowadays.
Zhilei wanted to make more money
so you can go to a rehabilitation center.
I'm not going.
It's not helpful to say stuff like this.
If you don't go,
people will say I'm a bad son.
Stop talking.
Does being a delivery man
make you a good son?
Why are you getting all worked up?
You want to go back to the hospital?
No more treatment. I'm done.
What about the clot in your head?
Stop, don't get him worked up.
He's getting me worked up.
I've already paid 300,000.
Enough already.
This house's to blame.
I told you it was too expensive.
Now we have no money.
What does that come from?
We agreed on buying the house together.
Mom and Dad sold the old house to chip in.
What do you want me to do?
Why are you yelling?
We'll work out a solution.
I'm out of solutions.
I'm such a loser.
I support the whole family.
I pay for all these bills.
I like being a delivery man?
I'm 45 already.
I've sent out 1,000 resumes.
No one wants to hire me.
Mommy, Daddy, stop fighting.
And you must go
to an international school.
It costs 200,000 a year.
We can't afford it.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you taking it out on the child?
Are you crazy?
So what? I can't get mad?
Why did you have to get sick?
Gao Zhilei.
Shut up.
MR. ZHU, I'D LIKE A DAY OFF TOMORROW.
You haven't paid the mortgage
for two months.
What if I sell the house?
I've done the math for you.
If you sell the house now,
you'll lose at least three million.
This can't be right.
Even worse, we may not be able
to sell the house.
Just do me a favor.
I approved your mortgage
when I started working
at this bank 5 years ago.
I really want to help you.
If you don't pay your mortgage,
it would affect me too.
Don't wait until your electricity is cut
and your doors all sealed up.
It'll be too late then.
I can pay a month's payment.
What?
My goodness.
Here's your pay stub.
It was too dark for me to see anything.
I can't ride fast.
Stop complaining to me.
When will the company
stop mandating this insurance?
My heart bleeds
when I pay for it every month.
You run red lights
and refuse to be insured?
You run red lights too.
That's why I buy insurance.
Big Black is ranked top again.
I'm no longer the last place.
It goes to Gao Zhilei.
Gao Zhilei is at the bottom.
The job is killing him.
He was late for the order,
so it got canceled
and a bad review was left.
Double click to like.
Like it.
Gao, you're back.
Your video went viral.
You should start your own account.
I got you a screen name too.
The Deflowerer.
Gao Zhilei.
Your pay stub.
Okay.
Is Li Yu here? Li Yu?
So?
I spent 300 on the uniform
and delivery box.
Another 500 on renting the scooter.
So, after a month of toiling,
I only earned 4,000 RMB.
What's the problem? Let me see.
Your basic salary is 1,800.
Commission for 500 orders is 3,700.
You fail to get any bonuses,
performance, timeliness and attendance.
You don't have tips.
300 for late delivery fines.
Another 1,100 for 11 bad reviews.
- It looks right to me.
- 11 bad reviews.
What about this 100?
It's monthly payment for insurance.
Bro, you even fail to get
the attendance bonus of 400 RMB.
I only had one day off.
So…
It's calculated based on backstage data.
You're only good at getting bad reviews.
You're dragging us down.
The bad reviews aren't all my fault.
I'll file an appeal.
Not your fault? So it's ours?
We're fairly tolerant to new riders.
I'll train you again later.
If it still doesn't work,
you can try Rapideliver.
Big Black, can I ask you something?
Here.
Here it is.
After I take an order,
can I cancel it?
Nope, you can only pass it on
to another rider.
I know you don't take pass-on orders.
But can you do me a favor?
Can you please take his order from me?
It's my old company.
Help me out here.
Just deliver it yourself.
I don't want see my old colleagues.
You feel embarrassed?
We're delivery guys, not drug dealers.
Deliver it yourself.
Hi, I'm at the front desk.
Can you come out and get it?
Sorry, you no longer work here.
Holy crap!
Gao?
Don't move.
It's really Gao.
Are you trying something new?
A delivery guy?
I'm trying something new.
Not bad.
- It's mine.
- Okay.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- Li, don't you know him?
He used to be the head
of our department, Mr. Gao.
- What did you order?
- Two Americano.
Holy crap.
Come on. Tip him.
Huh?
- It's okay.
- No, he should.
Only two RMB?
Do better, please.
- All right.
- Come on, a fiver.
It's done.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- I should go.
- Sit for a minute.
- No, you guys are busy.
- Everyone here misses you.
We need your guidance.
- No way.
- Gao.
Holy crap, he's a delivery guy now.
- I don't get it.
- Hasn't he started his own business?
You have a new order.
Auto-accept in 10 seconds.
Order accepted.
Auntie.
- I'll have a fish.
- Okay.
Thanks.
No problem.
Hello?
Where's my fish?
The fish has escaped.
Where?
- Suzhou…
- Are you on the train?
Suzhou Creek.
Suzhou Creek?
Are you fishing?
You don't have to pay
for the order. Sorry.
Hello…
Are you okay, young man?
- Do you need an ambulance?
- Yeah.
- Sugar.
- Low blood sugar.
Low blood sugar.
- Give us something sweet.
- I have Sprite.
Don't choke.
One more sip.
Operation Smile, warm up the city.
Take a photo of your smile
in 5 minutes to verify.
Operation Smile, warm up the city.
Take a photo of your smile
in 5 minutes to verify.
Son, you're in no condition
to be streaming.
Verification starts.
Open your mouth.
Shake your head.
Verification failed.
Please try again.
Verification starts.
Open your mouth.
Shake your head.
Keep smiling.
Verification failed.
Please try again.
Keep smiling.
Open your mouth.
Shake your head.
Keep smiling.
Workwear not up to standard.
Operation Smile verification failed.
You will be suspended for three days.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO GRANDPA
All set.
Dinner is ready.
Pour it…
That will do.
The other day,
it was…
my bad.
I'm sorry.
- Oh, no.
I've wet myself again.
I can't even feel it now.
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- It's fine.
It's okay.
Dad.
I talked to a rehab doctor.
He said it'd take four months to recover.
Don't worry.
You need the treatment.
My wife.
Zhilei.
I'm sorry.
The day before,
the rehabilitation center told me that…
I might have to spend
the rest of my life in a wheelchair.
I don't think you should…
waste any more money.
Zhilei is having a rough time lately.
My condition is getting worse too.
I've been thinking
I can't help you much,
but at least,
I can stop being a burden.
So…
it'd be a wise choice
for me to go now.
To live a full life
is not easy for anyone.
I used to support the whole family.
Right now,
it's Zhilei's crucial moment.
It will be tough,
but you must…
take good care of Jiajia.
I believe that…
your life…
will eventually…
get better and better.
Dad.
Our family has hit
rock bottom.
But it's nothing
compared to your youth.
At least we can still have braised pork.
Don't you worry.
I can do what you did in your youth.
I'll fight for our family
and work hard.
Dad, believe me.
If you give me a chance, I'll prove it.
If however,
I can't pull it off,
I'll go with you, okay?
Grandpa.
You haven't cut the birthday cake yet.
Big Black, I'd like your opinion.
Aren't you suspended?
I want to get better and you're the best.
Let me learn from you.
HOT PATCH FOR BELLY
What are these?
These are hot patches
for your stomach pain.
Put one on your belly for the pain.
Thanks.
I won't bother you then.
Hey!
How many orders did you made last month?
500.
So few?
- 11 bad reviews and 2 complaints.
- So many?
How did you do it?
I just did.
I'm sorry.
You know why you make less orders?
You've been taking lousy orders.
Why can you only take lousy orders?
Because you're a lousy rider.
You got that?
Lousy rider.
A lousy order is one
with longer distance and less pay.
It's harder to deliver.
How do I avoid them?
You need to level up.
The system categorizes riders
into 5 classes, bronze, silver,
gold, diamond and champion.
The higher the class,
the more pay per order.
You'll also get more orders.
If you want to earn more,
you need to be faster.
You must learn how to organize
your orders within seconds.
Prioritize some orders over the others
and work out your logistics.
Got it?
The platform only gives you
the default route.
I don't take it normally.
You must find the shortcut
between the pickup and the customer.
Organize your orders based on priority
and make deliveries accordingly.
- Delivery.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy it.
You need to know the neighborhood.
Is there a shortcut?
Every mall, residential area,
office building and apartment complex.
Each has
its own food delivery shelf or locker.
House numbers in the alleys
can be unsystematic.
You can only memorize them
by visiting them.
Hospitals and schools
are extremely challenging.
I don't normally take those orders.
Stingie.
I've got this used bike.
It's usually by the south gate.
You can ride it for deliveries on campus.
How much?
Nothing.
Can I have it when you quit?
Sure.
I'll show you how to suspend an order
when I have time.
You need two sets of batteries,
one as backup.
No delivery is too far.
I work for 14 hours a day.
Delivery is a race against time.
We ride through wind and rain,
day and night.
If you want faster pickups,
you need a good relationship
with the restaurants.
- Boss, try this tea.
- You're too kind.
I've got this.
- Zhilei.
- Hi.
Thanks, I'll confirm pickup.
Xiaomin, here.
Coffee for you.
Being a delivery rider
is all about attitude.
You may have shed off your elite pride,
but you're still not
the real working class.
You think you sit in the limo,
but in fact you're the chauffeur.
Isn't he a rider?
Security guards at the malls
are also key.
Hello, ma'am.
- Two packs of cigarettes.
- Sure.
- Hi.
- You can't come through here.
For your trouble.
Bye.
Ma'am, for your trouble.
- I'm in.
- Blooming Arse-ho.
Enjoy your meal.
Congratulations! You've got a tip.
Keep it going.
Always smile at the customers,
be they looking at you or cursing at you.
As the saying goes,
"One does not hit a smiling face."
Enjoy your meal.
Hi, Foodie 21 pickup.
I wish you a long life.
Have a swift recovery.
Enjoy your meal.
Please give me a good review.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal. I mean…
Happy lovemaking.
Should I take out the trash?
- I'll take out the trash for you.
- No.
- It's fine.
- Thanks, I'll give you a like.
Happy birthday…
- Whose birthday?
- Me.
Happy birthday.
You deserve a big bear hug.
Even the hardest order
must be delivered on time.
We working people
must look out for each other.
Enjoy it.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thanks.
I treat every customers as my children.
If I don't deliver food to them on time,
they'll starve to death.
I love you!
Jump.
Go ahead.
Are you stuck?
- I haven't received it.
- I transferred it.
I didn't even save money for food.
Got it now.
- Are you really a delivery rider?
- Yeah.
So cool.
Do you see me as a human?
- How do I not?
- Do you see me as a human?
Do you see me as a human?
Hi, Mr. Sun Fendou.
Your Foodie Delivery has arrived.
Enjoy your meal.
Please give me a good review.
In a minute.
Your healthy congee is on the shelf.
Food delivery.
- Enjoy it.
- Thanks.
TOP RIDER RANKING
24 GAO ZHILEI
GOLD RIDERS
ROUTE MASTER
Hey! Stingie.
Hi! How did it go today?
Not bad.
A big order for 30 people.
It took forever to prepare
and almost caused delay.
- Gotta go.
- All right.
- Stingie.
- Holy crap.
Are you injured?
You're bleeding.
- Let me take you to the hospital.
- Be careful.
- My phone.
- What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
- When will my food arrive?
- I'm on my way.
- Hey…
- Be there in a minute.
- I'll deliver it soon.
- Leave it.
- Stingie…
- What?
Stingie!
I'll make the delivery for you.
- Get him to the hospital.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- It's right around the corner.
- Hurry.
- I've got this.
- Don't run away.
- I won't.
I've got your plate.
- You must deliver it.
- I will.
Don't worry.
I'll collect the scooter parts.
Stingie!
Why are you running away?
Did you make the delivery? Any complaint?
They were nice when I got there.
Where's my scooter?
I took it to a garage.
My phone.
No. Wait.
You haven't been patched up yet. Go back.
Who needs bandages?
I'll wrap it with some tape.
Why should I pay others to do it?
- You lost your shoes.
- It's fine.
- Did the young man pay?
- Yeah.
How much?
15,000.
He agreed immediately.
Crap, I should've asked for 20,000.
- Not there yet?
- Keep going.
My mansion is right there.
Single-family home.
The one with lights on.
Here.
You call this a mansion?
I'm home.
Daddy.
Why are you home now?
I'm off the clock, so I'm home.
Gao, have a seat. Wherever you want.
Sit.
Yangyang.
Yangyang, greet our guest.
Uncle.
Wei, show some manners.
- Hello, Uncle.
- Hi.
- Sanyuan.
- Yes?
This is Gao from work.
He did me a big favor today.
My wife, Sanyuan.
- Sit, please.
- Okay.
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
Just bumped into a car.
I'm fine.
- Your leg is injured?
- It's nothing.
I said I'm fine.
Just a fender bender. I'm okay.
I got some masks for Yangyang
from the hospital.
Free.
Have some soup.
The place is small,
but it's cozy.
Let me tell you.
What?
How did you bump into someone again?
Not on purpose.
What do you think I am?
I got compensation.
15,000.
- One month earlier…
- 15,000!
How much is your life worth?
Don't start with me.
I got enough money for the surgery
one month earlier.
Am I not awesome?
I didn't plan it,
but sometimes a guy just gets lucky.
Give me a smile.
The kid…
Leukemia.
It's okay.
We have enough money now.
The bone marrow is a match.
You'll get a surgery
when there's vacancy at the hospital.
Daddy, look.
- What?
- I cut out this horse.
What is this?
You made this?
Attagirl.
Make another one for Daddy.
A horse with two horns.
I'll stick both on my scooter.
Okay?
Pick one. What other colors are there?
A yellow flower for you.
Thanks for the ride home.
Why are you being so nice to me?
You let me use your bike for free.
I once threw coffee at you.
And I spit at you, come on.
I gave you a bad review.
And you helped me deliver a big order.
Guess we're even now.
We're even.
I've been thinking
the wheel…
and my head…
were just an inch apart.
Such a narrow escape.
If I hadn't made it,
it'd have been a relief for me.
But what will happen to my family?
Damn it.
It's okay.
Bye.
Take care.
Your beard stings.
Did you drink?
I didn't.
I just wanted to give Jiajia a kiss
and give you a hug.
Look.
Daddy picked these wild flowers for you.
Are they pretty?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get you in Liu Yunong's class.
It's okay.
I can play with her on Sundays.
Daddy will work harder.
Daddy.
You've worked hard enough.
Then I must keep it up
and work even harder.
I'll become a Champion Rider.
When your dad becomes the champion,
I will perform a ballet dance
for you and him.
When Mommy dances, she will be a swan.
When I do,
I'm like a clumsy duck.
Dad, why are you up so early?
Your dad bought a watch.
It rings every two hours during the day
to remind him to go to the bathroom.
Do you know how long
it's been since I last wet the bed?
How long?
Ten days now.
That is impressive.
I'm not going
to the rehabilitation center,
but I'll do the rehabilitation myself.
I will get back on my feet again.
- Zhilei, don't worry.
- I'm not worried.
I'm not worried.
Your old man
is incredible.
He's not quitting.
I'll reopen the convenient store.
Our whole family will fight together.
Attention, everybody.
The more your orders,
the bigger your bonus.
The Champion Rider gets 2,000 per month.
Work harder, everyone.
Once you get started…
Sir.
I have an announcement to make.
I created this WeChat app.
It's called the Route Master.
I've put in all the residential areas,
schools, hospitals, shopping malls,
house numbers, apartment numbers,
all the delivery lockers and boxes
and marked them in the app.
Deliveries and pickups will be easier.
Let me scan it.
Scan the QR code with your WeChat
and you're in.
The more data we collect,
the more efficient it'll become.
The more data we collect…
GOOFISH
And he keeps counting.
Package pickup service.
Is it this one?
Yes, Liu Qianhua.
- Thanks, Uncle Gao.
- Thanks, Grandpa Gao.
Mommy will have
over 10,000 followers today.
Thank you, everyone.
Allow me to introduce.
This is my husband.
He just got into food delivery.
Come, say hello to everyone.
Hi, I'm the husband.
I am a delivery man,
but I'm also the husband.
Bye, everyone.
Push…
You can do it.
Okay.
Foodie Delivery!
Loved by all.
What do you think?
Enjoy your meal.
I bought you new shoes.
Gotta go now.
Ew!
Great…
That's wonderful.
Insulin shots.
Your insulin shots.
I don't seem to need these anymore.
Gotta go.
It's Big Black again.
He's made 18,000 this month.
So amazing.
I have two pieces of good news.
First, our station
has overtaken the one nearby
to become number one in this area.
Yay…
And, second, the Deflowerer,
who's been dragging us down,
has made 1,670 deliveries this month
and earned 10,002.
It looks like he knows
what he's doing, after all.
The Route Master is great.
Let's show him some love, okay?
Bravo!
Big Black.
You ride so fast.
Now they assume
everyone should be like you.
They're comparing us with you.
It's easy for you,
But I've been fined every day.
Serves you right.
You don't know your routes.
You should be fined,
and can't take shortcuts.
No, Big Black.
At my age,
I can't ride as fast.
If we don't run red lights
and violate some traffic rules,
- it's hard to be on time.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- We used to work for 12 hours a day.
Now we have to work for 14 hours.
If I own the company,
I'll give you good orders every day.
We are all riders here, aren't we?
- Yes.
- Shouldn't we help one another?
Yes.
Big Black,
how can you be so selfish?
What did you say?
You're selfish.
Who's selfish?
You should spend more time
memorizing the roads,
the routes and where the shortcuts are.
What's with all the whining?
Zhang, even you?
- No.
- Worthless losers.
Big Black, how could you say that?
What do you want?
Why don't you give us a peak
of your little notebook?
Yeah, let us see it.
What secrets do you have?
Come on, share with us.
Are you documenting
how many daddies you have?
Watch your fucking mouth.
So what?
I know what he drew.
It's his wife's tushy.
Sun Yao.
You think you're better? Do you?
Who's better now?
Stop fighting.
Still think you're better?
What is this?
Are you out of your mind?
Stingie.
You're fine…
- Is it my fault that I'm the fastest?
- No.
It's not your fault.
Is it my fault, Mr. Zhu?
You don't love money?
You don't want to earn more?
I just want to live
a better life each day.
I just want to turn my life around.
Sir.
I'm so tired.
I need a break.
Best of luck to you all.
The system gives more orders
to who can work more.
Big Black rides fast.
He's earned the privilege.
Sir, we should get more orders too.
Cut the bullshit.
Let me tell you something.
Rapideliver is introducing
a tiered pay system.
There's competition between platforms.
There are many riders.
Faster with lower pay is the trend.
The cake is cut into more slices now.
You see them?
They're young people in their early 20s.
If you want this job, do it.
Otherwise just fuck off.
Xiaomin.
Gao.
What are you doing here?
I've been riding all day.
I forgot to bring my raincoat.
Whose kid is this?
It's my son.
- You have a kid?
- Yeah.
Normally I take him with me at night.
But the rain caught me off guard.
We can't go home.
Take my raincoat.
No…
- No need.
- Take him home before he catches a cold.
What about you?
You said we should
help one another, right?
Ride slowly.
You should get back.
Take care.
- Get back.
- Slow down.
NO ORDER NOW
The Deflowerer fell asleep by the road.
Why were you sleeping here?
You could catch a cold.
Get up.
What are you guys doing here?
We're taking you somewhere.
Guess who I am.
Who?
Just a joke.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
You're stingier than me.
Drinking by yourself?
- We're all here. Let's drink together.
- Big Black.
Sorry for what I said earlier.
- Yeah…
- Can you forgive me?
It's all my fault.
If you don't forgive me,
I'll get down on my knees.
Zhang.
You…
I'll kowtow to you.
A toast
to congratulate the Deflowerer
for achieving Diamond Class.
- Diamond Class.
- Congratulations.
Thank you, guys.
Cheers…
Big Black, did you really quit?
Who said that?
I'm taking a break for a month.
Use the opportunity
to become the champion.
You won't stand a chance when I'm back.
Kai.
These are my friends from work.
Bring us more food.
Sure, right away.
Thanks.
What happened to his leg?
We used to work
at the same station together.
One day,
I passed on an order to him.
He was just leaving to deliver it,
a truck hit him and crushed his leg.
Did they compensate him?
He ran a red light.
He was fully liable.
He had to pay for the damaged cargo
and the surgery too.
Over 400,000 in total.
That's when I learned
he was saving up
for college.
That wrong turn
cost him his future.
No wonder you have to be the champion.
No wonder you never take pass-on orders.
After insurance paid out,
it's only 200,000.
I'm working hard…
to help him pay if off.
Just 40,000 to go.
Gao…
that hot patches you gave me are great.
I'm wondering
how's that app of yours coming along?
I've been working on it.
These are three years of notes.
You can have them.
I've marked out
some of the impossible routes.
I've collected the data myself.
I hope it can help you develop the app.
It might even benefit all riders.
It definitely will.
I've been too selfish.
Big Black,
we've never thought you are selfish.
Not for a second.
With these notes,
my app certainly will succeed.
Absolutely.
You can make it happen.
Thank you. A toast to you.
Is the cake I ordered ready?
Yes, be careful when carrying it.
Operation Smile, warm up the city.
Verification successful.
Hi, Xiao Ni.
Three more orders and I'll reach 15,000.
Are you ready to dance?
Dear Rider, you are running out of time.
Please deliver the order ASAP.
5,829.
It's loaded with cultural relics,
you know?
Ride more carefully in the future.
I'm sorry.
TRANSFER PAYOUT: 5,829
ACCOUNT BALANCE: 9,152
You're home.
Are you mad?
No.
I've been working
at the nail salon for a month.
I was going to tell you
when I get my first paycheck.
I'm not mad.
It must be tough for you.
I just flunk an order.
We won't be able
to pay mortgage this month.
I've failed to make 15,000 again.
Honey, I'm sorry.
I fear we might lose the house.
You bought a cake?
I thought I would give you a treat.
Open it.
Sorry.
I screwed up.
It's okay.
I like Pikachu.
When I was a child,
my whole family…
had to be crammed
into this shabby little apartment.
But I felt happy.
Before this…
I used to think
our bottom line was the house.
But now I know,
it's in fact our family.
Zhilei.
You are actually a great husband.
I just think…
you deserve a nice cake.
I'm sorry.
Zhilei.
- Zhilei.
- Dad.
What is it? The bathroom?
What is this?
Yesterday, your mom was tidying up things.
Then she found this photo.
It's me in 97,
when I was working in Guangzhou.
I spent three whole days
in the underground tunnel.
When I was young,
I worked really hard too.
Come to think of it now,
delivering food is not so bad.
Go.
Ride away.
Cui, I know my mortgage is due today.
I came to show you this, my pay stubs.
At first, I made only 4,000 a month.
It has since grown to 12,000 last month.
I actually had enough money,
but I lost it due to an accident.
What I'm trying to say is,
by the end of the month,
I will definitely have 15,000.
I'll be the champion.
Please believe me. Give me five days.
I promise I'll pay the mortgage.
What if you fail to be the champion?
If I can't,
I'll sell the house.
ROUTE MASTER
Attention, everyone.
Just got a notice from the HQ.
Bonus for the champion rider this month
has been increased to 2,500.
The winner will attend
the annual award ceremony.
Here's the current ranking.
- Dashan is at the top with 2,002 orders.
- Yes.
Let me through…
Sun Yao is in second place
with 1,999 orders.
Gao Zhilei is in third place
with 1,997 orders.
Stingie is also in third place.
Qiu Xiaomin is in fifth place
with 1,990 orders.
It's rainy and slippery.
Be safe out there.
It's 7:58 p.m. now.
We are 4 hours and 2 minutes away
from the birth of a new champion.
Dashan, you can do this.
Today, you will all witness me,
Yang Dashan, become the champion.
Go…
Good luck.
Riders, bring your A game.
Full throttle now!
I'll see you at 12 midnight.
Hi, everyone. Pikachu the Drummer here.
New comers, don't forget to hit like
and tap on the little red heart
to follow me.
Number 262.
Ever since I told you
my husband is a delivery guy,
I've got so much support from you.
Now I'm going to show you a solo.
It's my first performance
after seven years.
I hope you'd like it.
Quick, Foodie 120.
- Foodie 22.
- Foodie 167.
I will become the champion today.
Go for it!
Foodie Delivery 124.
Takeaway 106.
Is this Mr. Zhang? I'm on my way.
Don't worry.
CHOU XIAOMIN: 2,008 ORDERS
WANG LEI: 1,895 ORDERS
Coming through.
GAO ZHILEI: 2,011 ORDERS
STINGIE: 2,005 ORDERS
- Number 5002.
- Thanks.
- Careful with this.
- Okay, thanks.
- Hi. Food delivery.
- Thank you.
- Did you order this?
- Yes.
All right.
Please give me a good review.
Here's is your tea.
Foodie 101 is ready.
Xiaomin, go!
You can do this.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy it.
- Hi, food delivery. Enjoy it.
- Thanks.
Ms. Zhang, will this take long?
It might take a while.
Hi, hello.
Your place is far away
and hard to find.
Please wait patiently.
I will deliver it on time.
Here.
- This is yours.
- Thanks.
Foodie 95.
ROUTE MASTER: A SHORTCUT AHEAD!
Enjoy your meal.
65.
Thanks.
Please give me a good review.
I'm a deaf rider.
Enjoy your meal.
Zhang and the mute aren't giving up.
Hi, food delivery.
This isn't mine.
Oh, my! I'll refund you 26.9.
It's not about money.
Like, I need that 26.9.
I've refunded you, okay?
Look, Gao Zhilei is catching up.
My money is on Yang Dashan.
Another 5 orders done.
I can see the victory.
Number 18.
Number 72.
Hi, boss!
Foodie 121.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Sanyuan, speak.
- Honey, Yangyang is ready for surgery.
- They have a vacancy?
Yes.
When's the surgery?
Doctor says now. Come immediately.
Coming.
STINGIE IS OFFLINE
What's the update?
Sun Yao and Qiu Xiaomin are falling behind
and Stingie is offline.
The champion title
will go to either Gao Zhilei
or Yang Dashan.
Gao Zhilei is good.
- The doctor says he knows magic.
- You're doing well.
You'll be as good as new when you awake.
- We'll wait here.
- No family.
Please, Doc.
- Don't be afraid!
- You'll be fine.
The last order before 12 midnight.
Guys.
Tap on that little red heart.
Eighteenth floor?
Damn it.
Here I go! I'm all in.
Zhilei.
You're tied with Dashan now.
Whoever can deliver the order in hand
by 12 midnight
will become this month's champion.
Good luck!
Gao, go for it.
Okay.
Are you okay?
How could you come out from this side?
You're injured.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
No…
I don't have time.
I'm calling the police.
I have insurance.
Your leg's injured.
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm running late.
I don't have time.
Let's go to the hospital.
I must become the champion.
Lu Meili.
I'm coming to marry you.
Guys, I've finally got to the 18th floor.
The champion…
is definitely me.
Why are all the doors locked?
Where are you?
Can you speak louder?
What number?
Did you order this?
Where is my food?
Where are you?
Why are you still not here?
Can you raise your hands?
Can you put your hands up?
Put your hands up!
Hello, everyone!
Let's embrace tomorrow.
Ten.
I'm right in front of you.
Nine.
Delivery guy!
Come over here.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Let's make some noise.
CHAMPION, GAO ZHILEI
Xiao Ni.
I'm the champion.
We can keep the house now.
Where are you from?
Sir…
Sir, over here.
The camera.
We're recording a video.
Sir.
Let's congratulate the winners again.
Please step off the stage now.
Please stay.
Allow me to introduce.
This person here is this year's
oldest winner of the new rider award.
Mr. Gao Zhilei.
Let's give him a warm applause.
Please give us a speech.
Please tell us how you feel.
Yeah, how you feel.
I thought delivering food
would be easy enough.
I didn't expect it to be so tough.
Still, I'm grateful to this job.
When I hit rock bottom,
it helped me crawl.
I mean, stand on my feet.
Yes…
This is a fellow rider at my station,
Stingie.
Her daughter just went through
a successful leukemia surgery.
Yay…
Yes!
It's true.
We all work very hard.
Everyone I've seen and met…
works really hard.
We are all working hard
to build a better life,
fighting for our family
and running for a better tomorrow.
We've all tried our best.
And for that, we deserve respect
and we deserve a better life.
Right?
Yes.
- Right?
- Yes.
Bravo.
And the most important thing of all…
you must remember to be safe on the road.
Don't end up like me.
Come, put the drums here.
Hi, Rapideliver.
Hi, guys.
Let's take a break.
- Eat something first.
- Thank you.
Let's eat first.
All right, thank you.
You go ahead and eat.
Sorry, I'm new
and don't know the area well.
Please don't give me a bad review.
There you go.
I was late and you still gave me a tip?
I'm also a rider.
- Thanks.
After moving to a smaller place,
we have less stress.
I'm not sure if you like it here.
It's pretty nice.
It's smaller,
so the rooms are closer.
It's convenient.
What matters is
that you won't be so exhausted now.
You can't always be the champion.
Daddy will be the champion
and then the station manager.
You're flattering me.
You will be in charge
of your dad's future.
No problem.
I ran into Xie from the shipyard.
He lives in the next building.
Really?
I myself like it here.
It reminds me of my childhood.
It will be crowded in there.
Nonsense.
This is great.
It's true.
I love it.
Gao Zhilei.
How long have you gone
without an insulin shot?
It's April,
so five months.
I can tell you're different now.
I feel you can do anything.
You're good at flattering your husband.
You flatter your own husband.
Mr. Wei.
We found this app.
It was developed by one of our riders.
The interface is neat and simple.
It's got amazing feedback
from riders who have used it.
Should we offer him a job
at our computation center?
This is Lu Meili.
Hi, everyone.
She's my girlfriend. What do you mean?
I can't have a pretty girlfriend?
Fly away.
Slow down, Wangzi.
I will not allow anyone
to starve to death on my watch.
The food will be there soon.
I've got you.
Don't be scared.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Flowers.